<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>A Little Love</Title>
    <Artist>Yao Si Ting</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/5/b557eb964cc7986b6186f0d40799310b_1328010721.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;A Little Love&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Yao Si Ting&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjA0JTJGMjUlMkY5JTJGZCUyRjlkNmRmNmMyMWMzZmE2ODg5YjUwNDM2ODhhMzQ3NGY0Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Greatness as you&lt;br&gt; Smallest as me&lt;br&gt; You show me what is deep as sea&lt;br&gt; A little love, little kiss&lt;br&gt; A little hug, little gift&lt;br&gt; All of little something, these are memories&lt;br&gt; You make me cry, make me smile&lt;br&gt; Make me feel that love is true...&lt;br&gt; You always stand by my side&lt;br&gt; I dont want to say goodbye&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You make me cry, make me smile&lt;br&gt; Make me feel the joy of love.&lt;br&gt; Oh! kissing you...&lt;br&gt; Thank you for all the love you always give to me,&lt;br&gt; Oh! I love you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Greatnass as you&lt;br&gt; Smallest as me&lt;br&gt; You show me what is deep as sea&lt;br&gt; A little love, little kiss&lt;br&gt; Little hug, little gift&lt;br&gt; All of little something. These are our memories&lt;br&gt; You make me cry, make me smile&lt;br&gt; Make me feel the love is true&lt;br&gt; You always stand by my side&lt;br&gt; I dont want to say goodbye&lt;br&gt; You make me cry, make me smile&lt;br&gt; Make me feel the joy of love&lt;br&gt; Oh! Kissing you...&lt;br&gt; Thank you for all the love you always give to me&lt;br&gt; Oh! I love you&lt;br&gt; Yes I do . I always do&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Make me cry, male me smile&lt;br&gt; Make me feel the love is true&lt;br&gt; You always stand by my side&lt;br&gt; I dont want to say goodbye&lt;br&gt; You make me cry, male me smile&lt;br&gt; Make me feel the joy of love&lt;br&gt; Oh! Kissing you&lt;br&gt; Thank you for all the love you always give to me&lt;br&gt; Oh! I love you&lt;br&gt; To be with you...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh! I love you...</Lyrics>
</Song>
