<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Lost In The Echo</Title>
    <Artist>Linkin Park</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/f/4/f47fe8534f68254cc04d91e75d595e53_1332585127.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Lost In The Echo&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Linkin Park&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjA2JTJGMTYlMkZiJTJGMCUyRmIwYzllMzNhZTE3MDVhOTQzMjg4OTMxMDJkMTlmZTQ2Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Yeah&lt;br&gt; Yo&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You were that foundation&lt;br&gt; Never gonna be another one, no.&lt;br&gt; I followed, so taken&lt;br&gt; So conditioned I could never let go&lt;br&gt; Then sorrow, then sickness&lt;br&gt; Then the shock when you flip it on me&lt;br&gt; So hollow, so vicious&lt;br&gt; So afraid I couldn't let myself see&lt;br&gt; That I could never be held&lt;br&gt; Back or up no, I'll hold myself&lt;br&gt; Check the rep, yep you know mine well&lt;br&gt; Forget the rest let them know my hell&lt;br&gt; There and back yet my soul ain't sell&lt;br&gt; Kept respect up,the best they fell,&lt;br&gt; Let the rest be the tale they tell&lt;br&gt; That I was there saying…&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; In these promises broken&lt;br&gt; Deep below&lt;br&gt; Each word gets lost in the echo&lt;br&gt; So one last lie I can see through&lt;br&gt; This time I finally let you&lt;br&gt; Go, go, go.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Test my will, test my heart&lt;br&gt; Let me tell you how the odds gonna stack up&lt;br&gt; Y'all go hard, I go smart&lt;br&gt; How's that working out for y'all in the back, huh?&lt;br&gt; I've seen that frustration&lt;br&gt; Been crossed and lost and told &quot;No&quot;&lt;br&gt; And I've come back unshaken&lt;br&gt; Let down and lived and let go&lt;br&gt; So you can let it be known&lt;br&gt; I don't hold back, I hold my own&lt;br&gt; I can't be mapped, I can't be cloned&lt;br&gt; I can't C-flat / it ain't my tone&lt;br&gt; I can't fall back, I came too far&lt;br&gt; Hold myself up and love my scars&lt;br&gt; Let the bells ring wherever they are&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I was there saying...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; In these promises broken&lt;br&gt; Deep below&lt;br&gt; Each word gets lost in the echo&lt;br&gt; So one last lie I can see through&lt;br&gt; This time I finally let you go!!!&lt;br&gt; Go, go, go.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; No, you can tell 'em all now&lt;br&gt; I don't back up, I don't back down&lt;br&gt; I don't fold up, and I don't bow&lt;br&gt; I don't roll over, don't know how&lt;br&gt; I don't care where the enemies are&lt;br&gt; Can't be stopped, all I know; go hard&lt;br&gt; Won't forget how I got this far&lt;br&gt; For every time saying…&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; In these promises broken&lt;br&gt; Deep below&lt;br&gt; Each word gets lost in the echo&lt;br&gt; So one last lie I can see through&lt;br&gt; This time I finally let you&lt;br&gt; Go, go, go. (Go, go, go)&lt;br&gt; Go. go, go. (Go, go, go)</Lyrics>
</Song>
