<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>War Of Change</Title>
    <Artist>Thousand Foot Krutch</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://static.mp3.zdn.vn/skins/mp3_mobile/images/avatar_default_82x82.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;War Of Change&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Thousand Foot Krutch&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjA0JTJGMjElMkZlJTJGNSUyRmU1NGE5M2NmNzczNmU3OTJiODlmZmIyZTMzM2E5MGRkLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>t's a truth that in love and war,&lt;br&gt; World's collide and hearts get broken,&lt;br&gt; I want to live like I know I'm dying,&lt;br&gt; Take up my cross, not be afraid&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; Is it true what they say, that words are weapons?&lt;br&gt; And if it is,then everybody best stop steppin',&lt;br&gt; Cause I got ten in my pocket that'll bend ya locket,&lt;br&gt; I'm tired of all these rockers sayin' come with me, &lt;br&gt; Wait, it's just about to break, its more than I can take,&lt;br&gt; Everything's about to change,&lt;br&gt; I feel it in my veins, its not going away,&lt;br&gt; Everything's about to change.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It creeps in like a thief in the night,&lt;br&gt; Without a sign, without a warning,&lt;br&gt; But we are ready and prepared to fight,&lt;br&gt; Raise up your swords, don't be afraid,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; T his is a warning, like it or not,&lt;br&gt; I break down, like a record spinning,&lt;br&gt; Gotta get up,&lt;br&gt; So back off,&lt;br&gt; This is a warning, like it or not,&lt;br&gt; I'm tired of listenin', I'm warning you, don't try to get up,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There's a war going on inside of me tonight (don't be afraid) [x2]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wait, it's just about to break, its more than I can take,&lt;br&gt; Everything's about to change,&lt;br&gt; I feel it in my veins, its not going away,&lt;br&gt; Everything's about to change,&lt;br&gt; It's just about to break, its more than I can take,&lt;br&gt; Everything's about to change,&lt;br&gt; I feel it in my veins, its not going away,&lt;br&gt; Everything's about to change.</Lyrics>
</Song>
