<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Mean</Title>
    <Artist>Danielle Bradbery</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/a/aad1613f988b3297f8547fe9d0c4bbbc_1386754823.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Mean&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Danielle Bradbery&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjA2JTJGMTklMkYyJTJGNCUyRjI0NGQxN2VlOWUyOTliNjIzYTBhMzNjZTUxOWRmZGI0Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>You, with your words like knives&lt;br&gt; And swords and weapons that you use against me&lt;br&gt; You have knocked me off my feet again&lt;br&gt; Got me feeling like a nothing&lt;br&gt; You, with your voice like nails on a chalkboard&lt;br&gt; Calling me out when I'm wounded&lt;br&gt; You picking on the weaker man&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Well you can take me down with just one single blow&lt;br&gt; but you don't know, what you don't know...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Someday I'll be living in a big ol' city&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean&lt;br&gt; Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so mean?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You, with your switching sides&lt;br&gt; And your wildfire lies and your humiliation&lt;br&gt; You have pointed out my flaws again&lt;br&gt; As if I don't already see them&lt;br&gt; I walk with my head down&lt;br&gt; Trying to block you out 'cause I'll never impress you&lt;br&gt; I just wanna feel okay again&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I bet you got pushed around&lt;br&gt; Somebody made you cold&lt;br&gt; But the cycle ends right now&lt;br&gt; Cause you can't lead me down that road&lt;br&gt; And you don't know, what you don't know...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Someday I'll be living in a big ol' city&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean&lt;br&gt; Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so mean?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And I can see you years from now in a bar&lt;br&gt; Talking over a football game&lt;br&gt; With that same big loud opinion&lt;br&gt; But nobody's listening&lt;br&gt; Washed up and ranting about the same old bitter things&lt;br&gt; Drunk and grumbling on about how I can't sing&lt;br&gt; But all you are is mean&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; All you are is mean&lt;br&gt; And a liar, and pathetic, and alone in life&lt;br&gt; And mean, and mean, and mean, and mean&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; But someday I'll be living in a big ol' city&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean, yeah yeah&lt;br&gt; Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so mean?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Someday I'll be living in a big ol' city&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean, yeah yeah&lt;br&gt; Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me&lt;br&gt; And all you're ever going to be is mean&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so mean?</Lyrics>
</Song>
