<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Blurred Lines</Title>
    <Artist>Robin Thicke ft. T.I. ft. Pharell</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/c/bcdac8697e3c2c998b9a79818644c120_1404198844.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Blurred Lines&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Robin Thicke , T.I. , Pharell&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjA1JTJGMjQlMkZkJTJGYyUyRmRjMTczYTVmOWZiMjgyZTAyODkzNmQxMjI3MGE3MzAyLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Everybody get up&lt;br&gt; Everybody get up&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; If you can't hear what I'm trying to say&lt;br&gt; If you can't read from the same page&lt;br&gt; Maybe I'm going deaf, maybe I'm going blind&lt;br&gt; Maybe I'm out of my mind&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-chorus: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; OK now he was close, tried to domesticate you&lt;br&gt; But you're an animal, baby it's in your nature&lt;br&gt; Just let me liberate you&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; You don't need no papers&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; That man is not your maker&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; And that's why I'm gon' take a good girl&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; You're a good girl&lt;br&gt; Can't let it get past me&lt;br&gt; You're far from plastic&lt;br&gt; Talk about getting blasted&lt;br&gt; I hate these blurred lines&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; But you're a good girl&lt;br&gt; The way you grab me&lt;br&gt; Must wanna get nasty&lt;br&gt; Go ahead, get at me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; What do they make dreams for&lt;br&gt; When you got them jeans on&lt;br&gt; What do we need steam for&lt;br&gt; You the hottest bitch in this place&lt;br&gt; I feel so lucky&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; You wanna hug me&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; What rhymes with hug me?&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-chorus: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; OK now he was close, tried to domesticate you&lt;br&gt; But you're an animal, baby it's in your nature&lt;br&gt; Just let me liberate you&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; You don't need no papers&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; That man is not your maker&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; And that's why I'm gon' take a good girl&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; You're a good girl&lt;br&gt; Can't let it get past me&lt;br&gt; You're far from plastic&lt;br&gt; Talk about getting blasted&lt;br&gt; I hate these blurred lines&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I hate them lines&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I hate them lines&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; But you're a good girl&lt;br&gt; The way you grab me&lt;br&gt; Must wanna get nasty&lt;br&gt; Go ahead, get at me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 3: T.I.]&lt;br&gt; One thing I ask of you&lt;br&gt; Let me be the one you back that ass to&lt;br&gt; Yo, from Malibu, to Paribu&lt;br&gt; Yeah, had a bitch, but she ain't bad as you&lt;br&gt; So hit me up when you passing through&lt;br&gt; I'll give you something big enough to tear your ass in two&lt;br&gt; Swag on, even when you dress casual&lt;br&gt; I mean it's not almost unbearable&lt;br&gt; Then, honey you're not there when I'm&lt;br&gt; With my foresight bitch you pay me by&lt;br&gt; Nothing like your last guy, he too square for you&lt;br&gt; He don't smack that ass and pull your hair like that&lt;br&gt; So I just watch and wait for you to salute&lt;br&gt; But you didn't pick&lt;br&gt; Not many women can refuse this pimpin'&lt;br&gt; But I'm a nice guy, but you get it if you get with me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; Shake the vibe, get down, get up&lt;br&gt; Do it like it hurt, like it hurt&lt;br&gt; What you doing like word&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-chorus: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; Baby can you breathe? I got this from Jamaica&lt;br&gt; It always works for me Dakota to Decatur, uh huh&lt;br&gt; No more pretending&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; Cause now you winning&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; Here's our beginning&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus: Robin Thicke]&lt;br&gt; I always wanted a good girl&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; You're a good girl&lt;br&gt; Can't let it get past me&lt;br&gt; You're far from plastic&lt;br&gt; Talk about getting blasted&lt;br&gt; I hate these blurred lines&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; I know you want it&lt;br&gt; But you're a good girl&lt;br&gt; The way you grab me&lt;br&gt; Must wanna get nasty&lt;br&gt; Go ahead, get at me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro: Pharrell]&lt;br&gt; Everybody get up&lt;br&gt; Everybody get up&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey</Lyrics>
</Song>
