<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Royals</Title>
    <Artist>Lorde</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/b/ab0b62bb970b0cd797c7e1b963af07d6_1395199309.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Royals&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Lorde&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjA3JTJGMDclMkZkJTJGZCUyRmRkOGIxMzNiYzc1ODdmMDA4ZGJhNjc2MmNmNTRiOTFhLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Royals- Lorde&lt;br&gt; [Verse 1]&lt;br&gt; I've never seen a diamond in the flesh&lt;br&gt; I cut my teeth on wedding rings in the movies&lt;br&gt; And I'm not proud of my address,&lt;br&gt; In the torn-up town, no post code envy&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; But every song's like gold teeth, grey goose, trippin' in the bathroom&lt;br&gt; Blood stains, ball gowns, trashin' the hotel room,&lt;br&gt; We don't care, we're driving Cadillacs in our dreams.&lt;br&gt; But everybody's like Cristal, Maybach, diamonds on your time piece.&lt;br&gt; Jet planes, islands, tigers on a gold leash.&lt;br&gt; We don't care, we aren't caught up in your love affair.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And we'll never be royals (royals).&lt;br&gt; It don't run in our blood,&lt;br&gt; That kind of lux just ain't for us.&lt;br&gt; We crave a different kind of buzz.&lt;br&gt; Let me be your ruler (ruler),&lt;br&gt; You can call me queen Bee&lt;br&gt; And baby I'll rule, I'll rule, I'll rule, I'll rule.&lt;br&gt; Let me live that fantasy.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2]&lt;br&gt; My friends and I – we've cracked the code.&lt;br&gt; We count our dollars on the train to the party.&lt;br&gt; And everyone who knows us knows that we're fine with this,&lt;br&gt; We didn't come from money.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; But every song's like gold teeth, grey goose, trippin' in the bathroom.&lt;br&gt; Blood stains, ball gowns, trashin' the hotel room,&lt;br&gt; We don't care, we're driving Cadillacs in our dreams.&lt;br&gt; But everybody's like Cristal, Maybach, diamonds on your time piece.&lt;br&gt; Jet planes, islands, tigers on a gold leash&lt;br&gt; We don't care we aren't caught up in your love affair&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And we'll never be royals (royals).&lt;br&gt; It don't run in our blood&lt;br&gt; That kind of lux just ain't for us&lt;br&gt; We crave a different kind of buzz.&lt;br&gt; Let me be your ruler (ruler),&lt;br&gt; You can call me queen Bee&lt;br&gt; And baby I'll rule, I'll rule, I'll rule, I'll rule.&lt;br&gt; Let me live that fantasy.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oooh ooooh ohhh&lt;br&gt; We're bigger than we ever dreamed,&lt;br&gt; And I'm in love with being queen.&lt;br&gt; Oooooh ooooh ohhhhh&lt;br&gt; Life is game without a care&lt;br&gt; We aren't caught up in your love affair.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And we'll never be royals (royals).&lt;br&gt; It don't run in our blood&lt;br&gt; That kind of lux just ain't for us&lt;br&gt; We crave a different kind of buzz&lt;br&gt; Let me be your ruler (ruler),&lt;br&gt; You can call me queen Bee&lt;br&gt; And baby I'll rule, I'll rule, I'll rule, I'll rule.&lt;br&gt; Let me live that fantasy.</Lyrics>
</Song>
