<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Smack That</Title>
    <Artist>Akon ft. Eminem</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/3/a3a04658e84dd182ba00d123e35c2f12_1384157159.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Smack That&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Akon , Eminem&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjA4JTJGMzElMkYzJTJGMyUyRjMzMGY3NWU2YzlkMDlhNTQzYjI1ZWNmYzY5NGJkMzgzLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Akon:]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Shady&lt;br&gt; Konvi ct&lt;br&gt; Upfront&lt;br&gt; Akon&lt;br&gt; Slim Shady&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I see the one, because she be that lady! Hey!&lt;br&gt; I feel you creeping on, I can see from my shadow&lt;br&gt; Wanna jump up in my Lamborghini Gallardo&lt;br&gt; Maybe go to my place and just kick it like tabo&lt;br&gt; and posibbly bend you over look back and watch me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (2X)]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Smack that all on the floor&lt;br&gt; Smack that give me some more&lt;br&gt; Smack that 'till you get sore&lt;br&gt; Smack that oh-oooh!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Upfront style ready to attack now&lt;br&gt; pull in the parking lot slow with the lac down&lt;br&gt; Konvicts got the whole thing packed now&lt;br&gt; Step in the club now and wardobe intact now!&lt;br&gt; I feel it down and cracked now (ooh)&lt;br&gt; I see it dull and backed now&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna call her, than I pull the mack down&lt;br&gt; Money no problem, pocket full of that now!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I feel you creeping on, I can see from my shadow&lt;br&gt; Wanna jump up in my Lamborghini Gallardo&lt;br&gt; Maybe go to my place and just kick it like tabo&lt;br&gt; and posibbly bend you over look back and watch me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (2x)]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Eminem:]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oo h...Looks like another club banger&lt;br&gt; They better hang on when they throw this thing on&lt;br&gt; Get a lil drink on&lt;br&gt; They gonna flip for this Akon shit&lt;br&gt; You can bank on it!&lt;br&gt; Pedicure manicure kitty-cat claws&lt;br&gt; The way she climbs up and down them poles&lt;br&gt; Looking like one of them putty-cat dolls&lt;br&gt; Trying to hold my woodie back thru my drawers&lt;br&gt; Steps upstage didn't think I saw&lt;br&gt; Creeps up behind me, shes like &quot;your&quot;&lt;br&gt; I'm like ya I know lets cut to the chase&lt;br&gt; No time to waste back to my place&lt;br&gt; Starts from the club to the crib it's like a mile away&lt;br&gt; I'm more like a pal shall I say&lt;br&gt; Plus I got pal if your gal is game&lt;br&gt; In fact he is the one singing the song that's playing&lt;br&gt; &quot;Akon!&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Ak on:]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I feel you creeping on, I can see from my shadow&lt;br&gt; Wanna jump up in my Lamborghini Gallardo&lt;br&gt; Maybe go to my place and just kick it like tabo&lt;br&gt; and posibbly bend you over look back and watch me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Eminem is rollin', d and em rollin' bo&lt;br&gt; And all marvelous them rolling&lt;br&gt; Women just holding big booty rollin'&lt;br&gt; Soon I'll be on Eminem throwin &quot;D!&quot;&lt;br&gt; Hittin no less than &quot;Three!&quot;&lt;br&gt; Block wheel style like &quot;Whee!&quot;&lt;br&gt; Girl I can tell you want me because lately&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I feel you creeping on, I can see from my shadow&lt;br&gt; Wanna jump up in my Lamborghini Gallardo&lt;br&gt; Maybe go to my place and just kick it like tabo&lt;br&gt; and posibbly bend you over look back and watch me</Lyrics>
</Song>
