<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Talk Dirty</Title>
    <Artist>Jason DeRulo ft. 2 Chainz</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/a/3ac9682aa237b4ac1b0db6d04c463cbf_1397791653.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Talk Dirty&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Jason DeRulo , 2 Chainz&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjA5JTJGMjAlMkYyJTJGOCUyRjI4YjMzNmNkMmI1NTEyNmFhMTgzOWU2M2I3MjZiNWFkLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Jason&lt;br&gt; Jason Derulo&lt;br&gt; Get jazzy on it&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm that flight that you get on, international&lt;br&gt; First class seat on my lap girl, riding comfortable&lt;br&gt; Cause I know what the girl them need, New York - Tahiti&lt;br&gt; I got lipstick stamps for my passport, make it hard to leave&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Been around the world, don't speak the language&lt;br&gt; But your booty don't need explaining&lt;br&gt; All I really need to understand is&lt;br&gt; When you talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Get jazzy on it&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You know the words to my songs&lt;br&gt; No habla inglés&lt;br&gt; Our conversations ain't long&lt;br&gt; But you know what it is&lt;br&gt; I know what the girl them want, London to Taiwan&lt;br&gt; I got lipstick stamps for my passport&lt;br&gt; I think I need a new one&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Been around the world, don't speak the language&lt;br&gt; But your booty don't need explaining&lt;br&gt; All I really need to understand is&lt;br&gt; When you talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Uno, met a friend in Rio&lt;br&gt; Dos, she was all on me-o&lt;br&gt; Tres, we could ménage à three-o&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [2 Chainz:]&lt;br&gt; Dos Cadenas, clothes are genius&lt;br&gt; Sold out arenas, you can suck my penis&lt;br&gt; Get with arenas, guns on deck&lt;br&gt; Chest to chest, tongue on neck&lt;br&gt; International oral sex&lt;br&gt; Every picture I take, I pose a threat&lt;br&gt; Boat or jet, what do you expect?&lt;br&gt; Her pussy so good I bought her a pet&lt;br&gt; Anyway, every day I'm trying to get to it&lt;br&gt; Got her saved in my phone under &quot;Big Booty&quot;&lt;br&gt; Anyway, every day I'm trying to get to it&lt;br&gt; Got her saved in my phone under &quot;Big Booty&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Jason Derulo:]&lt;br&gt; Been around the world, don't speak the language&lt;br&gt; But your booty don't need explaining&lt;br&gt; All I really need to understand is&lt;br&gt; When you talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Talk dirty to me&lt;br&gt; Get jazzy on it&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What? I don't understand!</Lyrics>
</Song>
