<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Headlights</Title>
    <Artist>Eminem ft. Nate Ruess</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/0/a0538a67982e1ef3e3bd2922cb6dd9ce_1383013435.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Headlights&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Eminem , Nate Ruess&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjEwJTJGMzElMkY1JTJGYiUyRjViZDZhZWIzMmI4ZDUwY2Y5NmZjYWFmZmU2ODA2NzFiLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Intro: Nate Ruess]&lt;br&gt; Mom, I know I let you down&lt;br&gt; And though you say the days are happy&lt;br&gt; Why is the power off, and I'm fucked up?&lt;br&gt; And mom, I know he's not around&lt;br&gt; But don't you place the blame on me&lt;br&gt; As you pour yourself another drink&lt;br&gt; [Hook: Nate Ruess]&lt;br&gt; I guess we are who we are&lt;br&gt; Headlights shining in the dark night I drive on&lt;br&gt; Maybe we took this too far&lt;br&gt; [Verse 1: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; I went in headfirst&lt;br&gt; Never thinking about who what I said hurt, in what verse&lt;br&gt; My mom probably got it the worst&lt;br&gt; The brunt of it, but as stubborn as we are&lt;br&gt; Did I take it too far?&lt;br&gt; Cleaning out my closet and all them other songs&lt;br&gt; But regardless I don't hate you cause ma!&lt;br&gt; You're still beautiful to me, cause you're my mom&lt;br&gt; Though far be it for you to be calling, my house was Vietnam&lt;br&gt; Desert Storm and both of us put together can form an atomic bomb&lt;br&gt; Equivalent to Chemical warfare&lt;br&gt; And forever we can drag this on and on&lt;br&gt; But, agree to disagree&lt;br&gt; That gift for me up under the Christmas tree don't mean shit to me&lt;br&gt; You're kicking me out? It's 15 degrees and it's Christmas Eve&lt;br&gt; (little prick just leave) ma, let me grab my fucking coat&lt;br&gt; Anything to have each other's goats, why we always at each others throats?&lt;br&gt; Especially when dad, he fucked us both&lt;br&gt; We're in the same fucking boat&lt;br&gt; You'd think that it'd make us close (nope)&lt;br&gt; Further away that drove us, but together headlights shine&lt;br&gt; A car full of belongings&lt;br&gt; Still got a ways to go, back&lt;br&gt; To grandma's&lt;br&gt; House it's straight up the road&lt;br&gt; And I was the man of the house, the oldest&lt;br&gt; So my shoulders carried the weight&lt;br&gt; Of the load&lt;br&gt; Then Nate got taken away by the state at 8 years old, and&lt;br&gt; That's when I realized you were sick and it wasn't fixable or changable&lt;br&gt; And to this day we remained estranged and I hate it though, but&lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; [Verse 2: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; Cause to this day we remain estranged and I hate it though&lt;br&gt; Cause you ain't even get to witness your grand baby's growth&lt;br&gt; But I'm sorry mama for Cleaning Out My Closet, at the time I was angry&lt;br&gt; Rightfully maybe so, never meant that far to take it though, cause&lt;br&gt; Now I know it's not your fault, and I'm not making jokes&lt;br&gt; That song I no longer play at shows and I cringe every time it's on the radio&lt;br&gt; And I think of Nathan being placed in a home&lt;br&gt; And all the medicine you fed us&lt;br&gt; And how I just wanted you to taste your own, but&lt;br&gt; Now the medications taken over and your mental states deteriorating slow&lt;br&gt; And I'm way too old to cry, that shit's painful though&lt;br&gt; But ma, I forgive you, so does Nathan yo&lt;br&gt; All you did, all you said, you did your best to raise us both&lt;br&gt; Foster care, that cross you bare, few may be as heavy as yours&lt;br&gt; But I love you Debbie Mathers, oh what a tangled web we have, cause&lt;br&gt; One thing I never asked was where the fuck my deadbeat dad was&lt;br&gt; Fuck it I guess he had trouble keeping up with every address&lt;br&gt; But I'd have flipped every mattress, every rock and desert cactus&lt;br&gt; Own a collection of maps and followed my kids to the edge of the atlas&lt;br&gt; Someone ever moved them from me? That you could bet your ass's&lt;br&gt; If I had to come down the chimney dressed as Santa, kidnap them&lt;br&gt; And although one has only met their grandma&lt;br&gt; Once you pulled up in our drive one nights&lt;br&gt; As we were leaving to get some hamburgers&lt;br&gt; Me, her and Nate, we introduced you, hugged you&lt;br&gt; And as you left I had this overwhelming sadness come over me&lt;br&gt; As we pulled off to go our separate paths, and&lt;br&gt; I saw your headlights as I looked back&lt;br&gt; And I'm mad I didn't get the chance to thank you for being my Mom and my Dad&lt;br&gt; So Mom, please accept this as a tribute I wrote this on the jet&lt;br&gt; I guess I had to get this off my chest&lt;br&gt; I hope I get the chance to lay it before I'm dead&lt;br&gt; The stewardess said to fasten my seatbelt, I guess we're crashing&lt;br&gt; So if I'm not dreaming, I hope you get this message&lt;br&gt; That I'll always love you from afar, cause you're my mama...</Lyrics>
</Song>
