<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>The Fox</Title>
    <Artist>Ylvis</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/7/1/717f582d50a9389a483208e611757828_1379074216.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;The Fox&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Ylvis&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjA5JTJGMTQlMkY5JTJGNiUyRjk2MjVjNzljZjY2YzFlMDcwMGU2YjJlZDVmMzAyOGNmLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Verse 1]&lt;br&gt; Dog goes &quot;woof&quot;&lt;br&gt; Cat goes &quot;meow&quot;&lt;br&gt; Bird goes &quot;tweet&quot;&lt;br&gt; And mouse goes &quot;squeek&quot;&lt;br&gt; Cow goes &quot;moo&quot;&lt;br&gt; Frog goes &quot;croak&quot;&lt;br&gt; And the elephant goes &quot;toot&quot;&lt;br&gt; Ducks say &quot;quack&quot;&lt;br&gt; And fish go &quot;blub&quot;&lt;br&gt; And the seal goes &quot;ow ow ow&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-Chorus]&lt;br&gt; But there's one sound&lt;br&gt; That no one knows&lt;br&gt; What does the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus 1]&lt;br&gt; &quot;Ring-ding-ding-ding-dingeringeding!&lt;br&gt; Gering-ding-ding-ding-dingeringeding!&lt;br&gt; Gering-ding-ding-ding-dingeringeding!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &quot;Wa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow!&lt;br&gt; Wa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow!&lt;br&gt; Wa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &quot;Hatee-hatee-hatee-ho!&lt;br&gt; Hatee-hatee-hatee-ho!&lt;br&gt; Hatee-hatee-hatee-ho!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &quot;Joff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff!&lt;br&gt; Tchoff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff!&lt;br&gt; Joff-tchoff-tchoffo-tchoffo-tchoff!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2]&lt;br&gt; Big blue eyes&lt;br&gt; Pointy nose&lt;br&gt; Chasing mice&lt;br&gt; And digging holes&lt;br&gt; Tiny paws&lt;br&gt; Up the hill&lt;br&gt; Suddenly you're standing still&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-Chorus 2]&lt;br&gt; Your fur is red&lt;br&gt; So beautiful&lt;br&gt; Like an angel in disguise&lt;br&gt; But if you meet&lt;br&gt; A friendly horse&lt;br&gt; Will you communicate by&lt;br&gt; Mo-o-o-o-orse?&lt;br&gt; Mo-o-o-o-orse?&lt;br&gt; Mo-o-o-o-orse?&lt;br&gt; How will you speak to that&lt;br&gt; Ho-o-o-o-orse?&lt;br&gt; Ho-o-o-o-orse?&lt;br&gt; Ho-o-o-o-orse?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What does the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus 2]&lt;br&gt; &quot;Jacha-chacha-chacha-chow!&lt;br&gt; Chacha-chacha-chacha-chow!&lt;br&gt; Chacha-chacha-chacha-chow!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &quot;Fraka-kaka-kaka-kaka-kow!&lt;br&gt; Fraka-kaka-kaka-kaka-kow!&lt;br&gt; Fraka-kaka-kaka-kaka-kow!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &quot;A-hee-ahee ha-hee!&lt;br&gt; A-hee-ahee ha-hee!&lt;br&gt; A-hee-ahee ha-hee!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &quot;A-oo-oo-oo-ooo!&lt;br&gt; Woo-oo-oo-ooo!&quot;&lt;br&gt; What does the fox say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge]&lt;br&gt; The secret of the fox&lt;br&gt; Ancient mystery&lt;br&gt; Somewhere deep in the woods&lt;br&gt; I know you're hiding&lt;br&gt; What is your sound?&lt;br&gt; Will we ever know?&lt;br&gt; Will always be a mystery&lt;br&gt; What do you say?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro]&lt;br&gt; You're my guardian angel&lt;br&gt; Hiding in the woods&lt;br&gt; What is your sound?&lt;br&gt; (Wa-wa-way-do Wub-wid-bid-dum-way-do Wa-wa-way-do)&lt;br&gt; Will we ever know?&lt;br&gt; (Bay-budabud-dum-bam)&lt;br&gt; I want to&lt;br&gt; (Mama-dum-day-do)&lt;br&gt; I want to&lt;br&gt; I want to know!&lt;br&gt; (Abay-ba-da bum-bum bay-do)</Lyrics>
</Song>
