<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Crazy</Title>
    <Artist>Hoàng Thùy Linh</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/6/2/62d6c472ccad6b5e60ed06df735082ce_1422879836.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Crazy&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Ho\u00e0ng Th\u00f9y Linh&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjEyJTJGMDglMkZjJTJGZiUyRmNmODAyNmZkNDliODg2MGRjODYxMDAzZWMwZjBkNTAyLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Yeah, I'm talking about you baby, huh...&lt;br&gt; Here we go!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Sexy, feel it in the air so.&lt;br&gt; Naughty, I'll take it off the richter.&lt;br&gt; Maybe, if you treat me like a lady.&lt;br&gt; You might get something, a little something.&lt;br&gt; A little closer, put your hands on my hips.&lt;br&gt; A little closer, feel the touch of my lips.&lt;br&gt; Boy are you ready?&lt;br&gt; I wanna do it again, do it again, do it again.&lt;br&gt; Can't take it no more, can't take it no more tonight-i-ight.&lt;br&gt; I can't wait no more, can't wait no more to night.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Say goodbye to the world, the night has taken over me.&lt;br&gt; Are you ready tonight?&lt;br&gt; Will you say goodbye to the world, the little girl inside of me.&lt;br&gt; She's going crazy tonight.&lt;br&gt; Are you crazy, crazy, oh so crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; Oh so crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; Come a little closer baby, get a little closer baby.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Lately, I have had this feeling.&lt;br&gt; Take me, to another place.&lt;br&gt; No money, or diamond ring can buy my heart.&lt;br&gt; I'm stronger, stronger than you think, but.&lt;br&gt; A little closer, put your hands on my hips.&lt;br&gt; A little closer, feel the touch of my lips.&lt;br&gt; Boy are you ready?&lt;br&gt; I wanna do it again, do it again, do it again.&lt;br&gt; Can't take it no more, can't take it no more tonight-i-ight.&lt;br&gt; I can't wait no more, can't wait no more to night.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Say goodbye to the world, the night has taken over me.&lt;br&gt; Are you ready tonight?&lt;br&gt; Will you say goodbye to the world, the little girl inside of me.&lt;br&gt; She's going crazy tonight.&lt;br&gt; Are you crazy, crazy, oh so crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; Oh so crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; Come a little closer baby, get a little closer baby.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Get get get get get get crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; Get get get get get get crazy, yeah.&lt;br&gt; Get get get get get get crazy, yeah.&lt;br&gt; Get get get get get get crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Can't take it no more, no more tonight.&lt;br&gt; I can't wait no more, can't wait no more to night.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Say goodbye to the world, the night has taken over me.&lt;br&gt; Are you ready tonight?&lt;br&gt; Will you say goodbye to the world, the little girl inside of me.&lt;br&gt; She's going crazy tonight.&lt;br&gt; Are you crazy, crazy, oh so crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; Oh so crazy, crazy.&lt;br&gt; Come a little closer baby, get a little closer baby.</Lyrics>
</Song>
