<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Fancy</Title>
    <Artist>Iggy Azalea ft. Charli XCX</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/6/7/6745d62a9f9d06b8805720b174e0e9c5_1405054967.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Fancy&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Iggy Azalea , Charli XCX&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjAzJTJGMDIlMkYyJTJGMyUyRjIzZTRiMjg4MjMwNDhjNTMxZDU5ZmU3MzllZDU3MGJiLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Verse 1 - Iggy Azalea:]&lt;br&gt; First things first, I'm the realest&lt;br&gt; Drop this and let the whole world feel it&lt;br&gt; And I'm still in the Murda Bizness&lt;br&gt; I can hold you down, like I'm givin' lessons in physics&lt;br&gt; You should want a bad bitch like this&lt;br&gt; Drop it low and pick it up just like this&lt;br&gt; Cup of Ace, cup of Goose, cup of Cris&lt;br&gt; High heels, somethin' worth a half a ticket on my wrist&lt;br&gt; Takin' all the liquor straight, never chase that&lt;br&gt; Rooftop like we bringin' '88 back&lt;br&gt; Bring the hooks in, where the bass at?&lt;br&gt; Champagne spillin', you should taste that&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Charli XCX:]&lt;br&gt; I'm so fancy&lt;br&gt; You already know&lt;br&gt; I'm in the fast lane&lt;br&gt; From L.A. to Tokyo&lt;br&gt; I'm so fancy&lt;br&gt; Can't you taste this gold&lt;br&gt; Remember my name, 'bout to blow&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2 - Iggy Azalea:]&lt;br&gt; I said baby, I do this, I thought that, you knew this&lt;br&gt; Can't stand no haters and honest, the truth is&lt;br&gt; And my flow retarded, they speak it, depart it&lt;br&gt; Swagger on super, I can't shop at no department&lt;br&gt; Better get my money on time, if they not money, decline&lt;br&gt; And swear I meant that there so much that they give that line a rewind&lt;br&gt; So get my money on time, if they not money, decline&lt;br&gt; I just can't worry 'bout no haters, gotta stay on my grind&lt;br&gt; Now tell me, who that, who that? That do that, do that?&lt;br&gt; Put that paper over all, I thought you knew that, knew that&lt;br&gt; I be that I-G-G-Y, put my name in bold&lt;br&gt; I been working, I'm up in here with some change to throw&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Charli XCX]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 3 - Charli XCX:]&lt;br&gt; Trash the hotel&lt;br&gt; Let's get drunk on the mini bar&lt;br&gt; Make the phone call&lt;br&gt; Feels so good getting what I want&lt;br&gt; Keep on turning it up&lt;br&gt; Chandelier swinging, we don't give a fuck&lt;br&gt; Film star, yeah I’m deluxe&lt;br&gt; Classic, expensive, you don't get to touch&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge: Iggy Azalea]&lt;br&gt; Still stunting, how you love that&lt;br&gt; Got the whole world asking how I does that&lt;br&gt; Hot girl, hands off, don't touch that&lt;br&gt; Look at that I bet you wishing you could clutch that&lt;br&gt; Just the way you like it, huh?&lt;br&gt; You're so good, he's just wishing he could bite it, huh?&lt;br&gt; Never turn down money&lt;br&gt; Slaying these gold trigger on like&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Charli XCX]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro x2:]&lt;br&gt; Who that, who that, I-G-G-Y&lt;br&gt; That do that, do that, I-G-G-Y&lt;br&gt; Who that, who that, I-G-G-Y&lt;br&gt; (Blow...)&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
