<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>#Selfie</Title>
    <Artist>The Chainsmokers</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/1/b148c6598ae0b02874348504b2fe5002_1393919901.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;#Selfie&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;The Chainsmokers&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjAzJTJGMDQlMkZlJTJGNiUyRmU2N2IwNGIxNDFjMzUyNjM2YzMxYTA1NTc0Y2M1NGRiLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>When Jason was at the table&lt;br&gt; I kept on seeing him look at me when he was with that other girl&lt;br&gt; Do you think he was just doing that to make me jealous?&lt;br&gt; Because he was totally texting me all night last night&lt;br&gt; and I don't know if it's a booty call or not&lt;br&gt; Sooo... like what do you think?&lt;br&gt; Did you think that girl was pretty?&lt;br&gt; How did that girl even get in here?&lt;br&gt; Did you see her?&lt;br&gt; She's so short and that dress is so tacky&lt;br&gt; Who wears cheetah?&lt;br&gt; It's not even summer, why does the DJ keep on playing Summertime Sadness?&lt;br&gt; After we go to the bathroom, can we go smoke a cigarette?&lt;br&gt; I really need one&lt;br&gt; But first, &lt;br&gt; LET ME TAKE A SELFIE&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Beat Drops]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Can you guys help me pick a filter?&lt;br&gt; I don't know if I should go with XX Pro or Valencia&lt;br&gt; I wanna look tan&lt;br&gt; What should my caption be?&lt;br&gt; I want it to be clever&lt;br&gt; How about &quot;Livin' with my bitches, Hashtag LIVE&quot;&lt;br&gt; I only got 10 likes in the last 5 minutes&lt;br&gt; Do you think I should take it down?&lt;br&gt; LET ME TAKE ANOTHER SELFIE&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Beat Drops]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wait, pause, Jason just liked my selfie&lt;br&gt; What a creep&lt;br&gt; Is that guy sleeping over there?&lt;br&gt; Yeah, the one next to the girl with no shoes on&lt;br&gt; That's so ratchet&lt;br&gt; That girl is such a fake model&lt;br&gt; She definitely bought all her Instagram followers&lt;br&gt; Who goes out on Mondays?&lt;br&gt; OK, let's go take some shots&lt;br&gt; Oh no, I feel like I'm gonna throw up&lt;br&gt; Oh wait, nevermind I'm fine&lt;br&gt; Let's go dance&lt;br&gt; There's no vodka at this table&lt;br&gt; Do you know anyone else here?&lt;br&gt; Oh my god, Jason just texted me&lt;br&gt; Should I go home with him?&lt;br&gt; I guess I took a good selfie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Selfie on repeat]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; LET ME TAKE A SELFIE</Lyrics>
</Song>
