<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Loyal</Title>
    <Artist>Chris Brown ft. Lil Wayne ft. Tyga</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/1/f/1fe0516fe9ab44c75fc969c939c03e55_1341891567.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Loyal&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Chris Brown , Lil Wayne , Tyga&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjAyJTJGMTglMkY5JTJGNSUyRjk1MjliMjdkOTdlMTQ1NmI2MmMwOTY5MzA5ODFmY2JkLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Intro:Lil Wayne]&lt;br&gt; Young Mula, baby!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (You thought it was over?)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1: Lil Wayne]&lt;br&gt; I wasn't born last night&lt;br&gt; I know these hoes ain't right&lt;br&gt; But you was blowning up her phone last night&lt;br&gt; But she ain't have her ringer nor her ring on last night, oh&lt;br&gt; Nigga, that's that nerve&lt;br&gt; Why give a bitch your heart&lt;br&gt; When she rather have a purse?&lt;br&gt; Why give a bitch your inch&lt;br&gt; When she rather have nine?&lt;br&gt; You know how the game goes&lt;br&gt; She be mine by half time, I'm the shit, oh&lt;br&gt; Nigga, that's that nerve&lt;br&gt; You all about her, and she all about hers&lt;br&gt; Birdman Junior in this bitch, no flamingos&lt;br&gt; And I done did everything but trust these hoes&lt;br&gt; (CB fuck with me!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook: Chris Brown]&lt;br&gt; When a rich nigga want you&lt;br&gt; And your nigga can't do nothing for ya&lt;br&gt; These hoes ain't loyal&lt;br&gt; These hoes ain't loyal&lt;br&gt; Yeah, yeah, let me see.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge: Chris Brown]&lt;br&gt; Just got rich&lt;br&gt; Took a broke nigga's bitch&lt;br&gt; I can make a broke bitch rich&lt;br&gt; But I don't fuck with broke bitches.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2: Chris Brown]&lt;br&gt; Got a white girl with some fake titties&lt;br&gt; I took her to the bay with me&lt;br&gt; Eyes closed smoking marijuana&lt;br&gt; Rolling up the bomb molly I'm a rockstar&lt;br&gt; She wanna do drugs, smoke weed, get drunk&lt;br&gt; She wanna see a nigga trapped&lt;br&gt; She wanna fuck all the rappers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 3: Chris Brown]&lt;br&gt; Black girl with a big booty&lt;br&gt; If she a bad bitch, let's get to it (right away)&lt;br&gt; We up in this club&lt;br&gt; Bring me the bottles&lt;br&gt; I know girl, that you came in this bitch with your man&lt;br&gt; That's a no-no girl&lt;br&gt; All this money in the air&lt;br&gt; I wanna see you dance.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 4: Too Short]&lt;br&gt; A nigga fell in love&lt;br&gt; Turn into a woosy&lt;br&gt; Loyal (West Coast Version) lyrics on ChiaSeNhac.com&lt;br&gt; 24-7 he was eating that pussy&lt;br&gt; But these hoes ain't faithful&lt;br&gt; A nigga like me will have your bitch on tape though&lt;br&gt; I been knowing not to trust these hoes&lt;br&gt; I get bread, get head, and fuck these hoes&lt;br&gt; In that order&lt;br&gt; Don't switch it around&lt;br&gt; Relationships change, it's so different now&lt;br&gt; No high-school sweetheart&lt;br&gt; These bitches pimpin'&lt;br&gt; All these opinions&lt;br&gt; Women on women&lt;br&gt; Lickin' them titties&lt;br&gt; Sex in the city&lt;br&gt; Yelling &quot;Instagram likes&quot; but you ain't pretty&lt;br&gt; Bitch!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 5: Chris Brown]&lt;br&gt; Come on, come on, girl&lt;br&gt; Why you frontin'?&lt;br&gt; Baby show me something&lt;br&gt; When I call her, she gon' leave&lt;br&gt; And I bet that bottom dollar she gon' cheat&lt;br&gt; Come on, come on, girl&lt;br&gt; Why you frontin'?&lt;br&gt; Baby show me something&lt;br&gt; You just spent your ring on her&lt;br&gt; And it's all for nothing.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]</Lyrics>
</Song>
