<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Am I Wrong</Title>
    <Artist>Nico ft. Vinz</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/1/1/1167610aa17b0813233fe82d99403e41_1288963834.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Am I Wrong&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Nico , Vinz&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA1JTJGMTAlMkZkJTJGZSUyRmRlMTJjM2VlMjUxMTIzYmMyMjZjZTY0OGVmNzVmMTQ2Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Am I wrong for thinking out the box from where I stay?&lt;br&gt; Am I wrong for saying that I choose another way?&lt;br&gt; I ain't trying to do what everybody else doing&lt;br&gt; Just cause everybody doing what they all do&lt;br&gt; If one thing I know, I'll fall but I'll grow&lt;br&gt; I'm walking down this road of mine, this road that I call home&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So am I wrong?&lt;br&gt; For thinking that we could be something for real?&lt;br&gt; Now am I wrong?&lt;br&gt; For trying to reach the things that I can't see?&lt;br&gt; But that's just how I feel,&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; Trying to reach the things that I can't see&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Am I tripping for having a vision?&lt;br&gt; My prediction: I'ma be on the top of the world&lt;br&gt; Walk your walk and don't look back, always do what you decide&lt;br&gt; Don't let them control your life, that's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; Fight for yours and don't let go, don't let them compare you, no&lt;br&gt; Don't worry, you're not alone, that's just how we feel&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Am I wrong? (Am I wrong?)&lt;br&gt; For thinking that we could be something for real?&lt;br&gt; (Oh yeah yeah yeah)&lt;br&gt; Now am I wrong?&lt;br&gt; For trying to reach the things that I can't see?&lt;br&gt; (Oh yeah yeah yeah)&lt;br&gt; But that's just how I feel,&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; Trying to reach the things that I can't see&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If you tell me I'm wrong, wrong&lt;br&gt; I don't wanna be right, right&lt;br&gt; If you tell me I'm wrong, wrong&lt;br&gt; I don't wanna be right&lt;br&gt; [x2]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Am I wrong?&lt;br&gt; For thinking that we could be something for real?&lt;br&gt; Now am I wrong?&lt;br&gt; For trying to reach the things that I can't see?&lt;br&gt; But that's just how I feel,&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; Trying to reach the things that I can't see&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So am I wrong? (Am I wrong?)&lt;br&gt; For thinking that we could be something for real?&lt;br&gt; (Oh yeah yeah yeah)&lt;br&gt; Now am I wrong? (Am I wrong?)&lt;br&gt; For trying to reach the things that I can't see?&lt;br&gt; (Oh yeah yeah yeah)&lt;br&gt; But that's just how I feel,&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; That's just how I feel&lt;br&gt; Trying to reach the things that I can't see</Lyrics>
</Song>
