<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Wiggle</Title>
    <Artist>Jason DeRulo ft. Snoop Dogg</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/a/3ac9682aa237b4ac1b0db6d04c463cbf_1397791653.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Wiggle&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Jason DeRulo , Snoop Dogg&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA0JTJGMTclMkY1JTJGOCUyRjU4YTRmNmU4ZTk1OWEyNmZmYzVkOGNkNmQ3OWNjMzg3Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Hey, yo, Jason&lt;br&gt; Say somethin' to her&lt;br&gt; Holla at her&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [laughs]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I got one question&lt;br&gt; How do you fit all that in them jeans?&lt;br&gt; [laughs]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You know what to do with that big fat butt&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Just a little bit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Had that cake, had that cake&lt;br&gt; With no hands&lt;br&gt; Got me in this club making wedding plans&lt;br&gt; If I take picture while you do your dance&lt;br&gt; I can make you famous on Instagram&lt;br&gt; Hot damn it&lt;br&gt; Your booty lights two planets&lt;br&gt; Go head, and go ham sandwich&lt;br&gt; Woah&lt;br&gt; I can’t stand it&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Cause You know what to do with that big fat butt&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Just a little bit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Cadillac, Cadillac, pop that trunks&lt;br&gt; Let’s take a shot&lt;br&gt; Alley oops that dunk&lt;br&gt; Tired of forking that 9 to 5&lt;br&gt; Oh baby let me come and change your life&lt;br&gt; Hot damn it&lt;br&gt; Your booty lights two planets&lt;br&gt; Go head, and go ham sandwich&lt;br&gt; Woah&lt;br&gt; I can’t stand it&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Cause You know what to do with that big fat butt&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Just a little bit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Snoop Dogg:]&lt;br&gt; Shake what your mama gave you&lt;br&gt; Misbehave you&lt;br&gt; I just wanna strip you, dip you, flip you, bubble bath you&lt;br&gt; What they do&lt;br&gt; Taste my rain drop, ok boo&lt;br&gt; Now what you’re willing, what you wanting, what you may do&lt;br&gt; Completely sample rated, til my deeply penetrated&lt;br&gt; Then I take I out, and wipe it off&lt;br&gt; Eat it, ate it, love it, hate it&lt;br&gt; Overstated, underrated, everywhere I been king&lt;br&gt; You wiggle, wiggle for the D, O, double G, a king&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Come on baby&lt;br&gt; Turn around&lt;br&gt; You’re a star girl&lt;br&gt; Take a bow&lt;br&gt; It’s just one thing that’s killing me&lt;br&gt; How you get that in them jeans?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You know what to do with that big fat butt&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Just a little bit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Now make it clap&lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Now make it clap&lt;br&gt; Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle&lt;br&gt; Make it clap&lt;br&gt; Now make it clap&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Damn baby you got a bright future behind you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
