<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Rude</Title>
    <Artist>MAGIC!</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/f/f/ff42373e32663992b0aa2be97ac80425_1414754982.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Rude&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;MAGIC!&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA3JTJGMDIlMkZmJTJGZiUyRmZmY2I5NGVhNTI1YmViZmExOGNmOTI1ODcwZmQ3ODJlLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Saturday morning jumped out of bed and put on my best suit&lt;br&gt; Got in my car and raced like a jet, all the way to you&lt;br&gt; Knocked on your door with heart in my hand&lt;br&gt; To ask you a question&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I know that you're an old fashioned man yeah yeah&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'Can I have your daughter for the rest of my life? Say yes, say yes&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I need to know&lt;br&gt; You say I'll never get your blessing till the day I die&lt;br&gt; Tough luck my friend but the answer is no!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude?&lt;br&gt; Don't you know I'm human too&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna marry her anyway&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; Marry her anyway&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; Yeah no matter what you say&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; And we'll be a family&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I hate to do this, you leave no choice&lt;br&gt; Can't live without her&lt;br&gt; Love me or hate me we will be boys&lt;br&gt; Standing at that alter&lt;br&gt; Or we will run away&lt;br&gt; To another galaxy you know&lt;br&gt; You know she's in love with me&lt;br&gt; She will go anywhere I go&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Can I have your daughter for the rest of my life? Say yes, say yes&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I need to know&lt;br&gt; You say I'll never get your blessing till the day I die&lt;br&gt; Tough luck my friend cause the answer's still no!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude?&lt;br&gt; Don't you know I'm human too&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna marry her anyway&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; Marry her anyway&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; No matter what you say&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; And we'll be a family&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Can I have your daughter for the rest of my life? Say yes, say yes&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I need to know&lt;br&gt; You say I'll never get your blessing till the day I die&lt;br&gt; Tough luck my friend but no still means no!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude?&lt;br&gt; Don't you know I'm human too&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna marry her anyway&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; Marry her anyway&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; No matter what you say&lt;br&gt; Marry that girl&lt;br&gt; And we'll be a family&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude?&lt;br&gt; Why you gotta be so rude?</Lyrics>
</Song>
