<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Run This Town</Title>
    <Artist>Jay-Z ft. Rihanna</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/f/b/fb99c47e948491d78859930807a78f77_1289881708.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Run This Town&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Jay-Z , Rihanna&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjAzJTJGMTklMkYzJTJGZCUyRjNkNTg1NjhjMjE0M2JkODg2MTE2YTk4ZjBmMTQwOTc0Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Run This Town&quot;&lt;br&gt; (feat. Rihanna, Kanye West)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Intro - Rihanna]&lt;br&gt; Feel it comin' in the air&lt;br&gt; Hear the screams from everywhere&lt;br&gt; I'm addicted to the thrill&lt;br&gt; It's a dangerous love affair&lt;br&gt; Can't be scared when it goes down&lt;br&gt; Got a problem, tell me now&lt;br&gt; Only thing that's on my mind&lt;br&gt; Is who's gonna run this town tonight...&lt;br&gt; Is who's gonna run this town tonight...&lt;br&gt; We gonna run this town&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1 - Jay-Z]&lt;br&gt; We are&lt;br&gt; Yeah I said it&lt;br&gt; We are&lt;br&gt; This is Roc Nation&lt;br&gt; Pledge your allegiance&lt;br&gt; Get y'all black tees on&lt;br&gt; All black everything&lt;br&gt; Black cards, black cars&lt;br&gt; All black everything&lt;br&gt; And our girls are blackbirds&lt;br&gt; Ridin' with they dillingers&lt;br&gt; I'd get more in depth&lt;br&gt; If you boys really real enough&lt;br&gt; This is la familia&lt;br&gt; I'll explain later&lt;br&gt; But for now let me get back to this paper&lt;br&gt; I'm a couple bands down and I'm tryin' to get back&lt;br&gt; I gave Doug a grip, I lost a flip for five stacks&lt;br&gt; Yeah I'm talkin' five comma&lt;br&gt; six zeros&lt;br&gt; dot zero&lt;br&gt; Here it go...&lt;br&gt; Back to runnin' circles 'round niggas&lt;br&gt; Now we squared up&lt;br&gt; Hold up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Rihanna]&lt;br&gt; Life's a game but it's not fair&lt;br&gt; I break the rules so I don't care&lt;br&gt; So I keep doin' my own thing&lt;br&gt; Walkin' tall against the rain&lt;br&gt; Victory's within the mile&lt;br&gt; Almost there, don't give up now&lt;br&gt; Only thing that's on my mind&lt;br&gt; Is who's gonna run this town tonight&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; (Is who's gonna run this town tonight)&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2 - Jay-Z]&lt;br&gt; We are&lt;br&gt; Yeah I said it&lt;br&gt; We are&lt;br&gt; You can call me Cesar&lt;br&gt; In a dark Czar&lt;br&gt; Please follow the leader&lt;br&gt; So Eric B. we are&lt;br&gt; Microphone fiend&lt;br&gt; It's the return of the god&lt;br&gt; Peace god...&lt;br&gt; (Auh! Auh!)&lt;br&gt; And ain't nobody fresher&lt;br&gt; I'm in Mason&lt;br&gt; (Ah!)&lt;br&gt; Martin Margiela&lt;br&gt; On the tape we're screamin'&lt;br&gt; Fuck the other side, they jealous&lt;br&gt; We got a banquette full the broads&lt;br&gt; They got a table full of fellas... (?)&lt;br&gt; And they ain't spending no cake&lt;br&gt; They should throw they hand in&lt;br&gt; 'Cause they ain't got no spades...&lt;br&gt; My whole team got dough&lt;br&gt; So my banquette is lookin' like Millionaire's Row&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Rihanna]&lt;br&gt; Life's a game but it's not fair&lt;br&gt; I break the rules so I don't care&lt;br&gt; So I keep doin' my own thing&lt;br&gt; Walkin' tall against the rain&lt;br&gt; Victory's within the mile&lt;br&gt; Almost there, don't give up now&lt;br&gt; Only thing that's on my mind&lt;br&gt; Is who's gonna run this town tonight&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; (Is who's gonna run this town tonight)&lt;br&gt; Hey-hey-hey-hey&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 3 - Kanye West]&lt;br&gt; It's crazy how you can go from being Joe Blow&lt;br&gt; To everybody on your dick, no homo&lt;br&gt; I bought my whole family whips, no Volvos&lt;br&gt; Next time I'm in church, please no photos&lt;br&gt; Police escorts&lt;br&gt; Everybody passports&lt;br&gt; This the life that everybody ask for&lt;br&gt; This a fast life&lt;br&gt; We are on a crash course&lt;br&gt; What you think I rap for&lt;br&gt; To push a fucking Rav 4?&lt;br&gt; But I know that if I stay stun-ting&lt;br&gt; All these girls only gonna want one thing&lt;br&gt; I could spend my whole life good will hunting&lt;br&gt; Only good gon' come is as good when I'm cumming&lt;br&gt; She got a ass that'll swallow up a g-string&lt;br&gt; And up top, unh...&lt;br&gt; Two bee stings&lt;br&gt; And I'm beasting&lt;br&gt; Off the riesling&lt;br&gt; And my nigga just made it out the precinct&lt;br&gt; We give a damn about the drama that you do bring&lt;br&gt; I'm just tryin' to change the color on your mood ring&lt;br&gt; Reebok&lt;br&gt; Baby&lt;br&gt; You need to drop some new things&lt;br&gt; Have you ever had shoes without shoe strings?&lt;br&gt; What's that 'Ye?&lt;br&gt; Baby, these heels&lt;br&gt; Is that a may?&lt;br&gt; What?!&lt;br&gt; Baby, these wheels&lt;br&gt; You trippin' when you ain't sippin'&lt;br&gt; Have a refill&lt;br&gt; You feelin' like you runnin', huh?&lt;br&gt; Now you know how we feel&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro - Rihanna]&lt;br&gt; We gonna run this town tonight!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro - Jay-Z]&lt;br&gt; Wassup!</Lyrics>
</Song>
