<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Lost Stars</Title>
    <Artist>Adam Levine</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/1/b/1b54ef2c21f7d9e370ce6fa5fd41a21d_1285293883.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Lost Stars&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Adam Levine&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA3JTJGMDElMkZlJTJGYiUyRmViODdkYzIwNDc2M2U1ZTAzNjI0MGZkMjRmYjI4ZjdmLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Please don't see&lt;br&gt; Just a boy caught up in dreams and fantasies&lt;br&gt; Please see me&lt;br&gt; Reaching out for someone I can't see&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Take my hand, let's see where we wake up tomorrow&lt;br&gt; Best laid plans sometimes are just a one night stand&lt;br&gt; I'll be damned, Cupid's demanding back his arrow&lt;br&gt; So let's get drunk on our tears&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And God, tell us the reason youth is wasted on the young&lt;br&gt; It's hunting season and the lambs are on the run&lt;br&gt; Searching for meaning&lt;br&gt; But are we all lost stars trying to light up the dark?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Who are we?&lt;br&gt; Just a speck of dust within the galaxy?&lt;br&gt; Woe is me&lt;br&gt; If we're not careful turns into reality&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; But don't you dare let our best memories bring you sorrow&lt;br&gt; Yesterday I saw a lion kiss a deer&lt;br&gt; Turn the page, maybe we'll find a brand new ending&lt;br&gt; Where we're dancing in our tears&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And God, tell us the reason youth is wasted on the young&lt;br&gt; It's hunting season and the lambs are on the run&lt;br&gt; We're searching for meaning&lt;br&gt; But are we all lost stars trying to light up the dark?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; and I thought I saw you out there crying&lt;br&gt; and I thought I heard you call my name&lt;br&gt; and I thought I heard you out there crying&lt;br&gt; But just the same&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And God, give us the reason youth is wasted on the young&lt;br&gt; It's hunting season and the lambs are on the run&lt;br&gt; searching for meaning&lt;br&gt; But are we all lost stars trying to light up the dark?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And I thought I saw you out there crying&lt;br&gt; And I thought I heard you call my name&lt;br&gt; And I thought I heard you out there crying&lt;br&gt; But are we all lost stars trying to light up the dark?&lt;br&gt; Are we all lost stars trying to light up the dark?&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
