<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Amnesia</Title>
    <Artist>5 Seconds Of Summer</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/4/0/40bab9d507ccfebc667e41d26c465f4b_1400668953.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Amnesia&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;5 Seconds Of Summer&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA2JTJGMjclMkZmJTJGMyUyRmYzZmRhYmY2NzU4YjlmOTBjNGRkZjY2YzM5OTBkOGE3Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I drove by all the places we used to hang out getting wasted&lt;br&gt; I thought about our last kiss, how it felt the way you tasted&lt;br&gt; And even though your friends tell me you’re doing fine&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Are you somewhere feeling lonely even though he’s right beside you?&lt;br&gt; When he says those words that hurt you, do you read the ones I wrote you?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Sometimes I start to wonder, was it just a lie?&lt;br&gt; If what we had was real, how could you be fine?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; ‘Cause I’m not fine at all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I remember the day you told me you were leaving&lt;br&gt; I remember the make-up running down your face&lt;br&gt; And the dreams you left behind you didn’t need them&lt;br&gt; Like every single wish we ever made&lt;br&gt; I wish that I could wake up with amnesia&lt;br&gt; And forget about the stupid little things&lt;br&gt; Like the way it felt to fall asleep next to you&lt;br&gt; And the memories I never can escape&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; ‘Cause I’m not fine at all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The pictures that you sent me they’re still living in my phone&lt;br&gt; I admit I like to see them, I admit I feel alone&lt;br&gt; And all my friends keep asking why I’m not around&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It hurts to know you’re happy, yeah, it hurts that you’ve moved on&lt;br&gt; It’s hard to hear your name when I haven’t seen you in so long&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It’s like we never happened, was it just a lie?&lt;br&gt; If what we had was real, how could you be fine?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; ‘Cause I’m not fine at all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I remember the day you told me you were leaving&lt;br&gt; I remember the make-up running down your face&lt;br&gt; And the dreams you left behind you didn’t need them&lt;br&gt; Like every single wish we ever made&lt;br&gt; I wish that I could wake up with amnesia&lt;br&gt; And forget about the stupid little things&lt;br&gt; Like the way it felt to fall asleep next to you&lt;br&gt; And the memories I never can escape&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If today I woke up with you right beside me&lt;br&gt; Like all of this was just some twisted dream&lt;br&gt; I’d hold you closer than I ever did before&lt;br&gt; And you’d never slip away&lt;br&gt; And you’d never hear me say&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I remember the day you told me you were leaving&lt;br&gt; I remember the make-up running down your face&lt;br&gt; And the dreams you left behind you didn’t need them&lt;br&gt; Like every single wish we ever made&lt;br&gt; I wish that I could wake up with amnesia&lt;br&gt; And forget about the stupid little things&lt;br&gt; Like the way it felt to fall asleep next to you&lt;br&gt; And the memories I never can escape&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'Cause I’m not fine at all&lt;br&gt; No, I'm really not fine at all&lt;br&gt; Tell me this is just a dream&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I'm really not fine at all</Lyrics>
</Song>
