<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>All Of The Stars</Title>
    <Artist>Ed Sheeran</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/d/bddc4bc2c2c484086a724582d1243879_1422792513.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;All Of The Stars&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Ed Sheeran&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA2JTJGMjMlMkY0JTJGZSUyRjRlYTJlNGRkOWI0YTY5ZTc0NDBhYjZmZDY3ZmQxNTM2Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;All Of The Stars&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's just another night and I'm staring at the moon&lt;br&gt; I saw a shooting star and thought of you&lt;br&gt; I sang a lullaby by the waterside and knew&lt;br&gt; If you were here, I'd sing to you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You're on the other side&lt;br&gt; As the skyline splits in two&lt;br&gt; Miles away from seeing you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; But I can see the stars from America&lt;br&gt; I wonder, do you see them too?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So open your eyes and see&lt;br&gt; The way our horizons meet&lt;br&gt; And all of the lights will lead&lt;br&gt; Into the night with me&lt;br&gt; And I know these scars will bleed&lt;br&gt; But both of our hearts believe&lt;br&gt; All of these stars will guide us home&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can hear your heart on the radio beat&lt;br&gt; They're playing &quot;Chasing Cars&quot; and I thought of us&lt;br&gt; Back to the time you were lying next to me&lt;br&gt; I looked across and fell in love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So I took your hand&lt;br&gt; Back through lamp-lit streets and knew&lt;br&gt; Everything led back to you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So can you see the stars over Amsterdam?&lt;br&gt; Hear the song my heart is beating to&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So open your eyes and see&lt;br&gt; The way our horizons meet&lt;br&gt; And all of the lights will leave&lt;br&gt; Into the night with me&lt;br&gt; And I know these scars will bleed&lt;br&gt; But both of our hearts believe&lt;br&gt; All of these stars will guide us home&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And oh&lt;br&gt; And oh&lt;br&gt; And oh whoa&lt;br&gt; I can see the stars from America.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Nguồn: http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/edsheeran/allofthestars.html</Lyrics>
</Song>
