<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Hangover</Title>
    <Artist>PSY ft. Snoop Dogg</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/d/7/d79e59207e1648fb2dd85e6b7004f9c6_1345695966.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Hangover&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;PSY , Snoop Dogg&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA2JTJGMDklMkYyJTJGZiUyRjJmNzcyMzFkOTgxZDE2MDNiZGE2NWIzYmFhMjE4N2Y3Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>WoK Group: Hangover by PSY&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Party’s over, it ain’t over&lt;br&gt; Tryna’ make a bad memory over and over&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Party’s over, it ain’t over&lt;br&gt; Tryna find a single piece of me game over&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hangover. Hangover. Hangover. Hangover&lt;br&gt; Tryna find a single piece of me game over&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Drink til you drunk&lt;br&gt; Smoke like a broke’ stove&lt;br&gt; Don’t quit take flight&lt;br&gt; I can’t remember last night&lt;br&gt; It’s aight this the life of a superstar&lt;br&gt; Psy-fi with that boy trooping hard couping cars snoopy hard&lt;br&gt; In the paint drink another cup until i fall flat&lt;br&gt; All lead and then some 1-5-1 done dilly&lt;br&gt; Really for sure that&lt;br&gt; I’m tow back intoxicated&lt;br&gt; Change over, game over, hangover, faded&lt;br&gt; Body shit miss&lt;br&gt; Deche reoki yes kkoekkori moschajgesseu&lt;br&gt; I-i-inimanimo catch a lady by the toe&lt;br&gt; Anyeppeumyeon yeppeoboilttae kkaji pparabeorigo&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Drink it up and get sick&lt;br&gt; Bottoms up get wasted&lt;br&gt; Pour it up drink it up live it up give it up&lt;br&gt; Oh my god dammit there’s the fucking limit&lt;br&gt; Pour it up drink it up live it up give it up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Badeusio&lt;br&gt; But i can’t stop&lt;br&gt; Making bottles pop until the wheels fall off&lt;br&gt; Badeusio&lt;br&gt; And i can’t quit&lt;br&gt; I wake up in the morning do the same shit&lt;br&gt; Wake up in the morning do the same shit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hangover. Hangover. Hangover. Hangover&lt;br&gt; Tryna find a single piece of me game over&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Waking and baking, shaking the flees&lt;br&gt; Caking and baking, raking the cheese&lt;br&gt; Early in the morning in the bathroom on my knees&lt;br&gt; Tipping and dripping, flipping the flow&lt;br&gt; Whipping and dripping a drink on the floor&lt;br&gt; This it the only way that i was taught a long time ago&lt;br&gt; Seoul, korea, you’ll see a g-ah like me-ah&lt;br&gt; Never would there ever be another like he-ah&lt;br&gt; G-a-n-g-s-t-a, nothing left to say&lt;br&gt; I done smoked my whole day&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby nareul siheomhae&lt;br&gt; Eoseo na siheomhae&lt;br&gt; Geosigiga geosigihani geosigihago jjage geosigihae&lt;br&gt; Naeireun eopsda era&lt;br&gt; Moreugessda nae bae jjaera&lt;br&gt; Naeirui naneun oneurui neoreul baekpeuro molla&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Drink it up get sick&lt;br&gt; Bottoms up get wasted&lt;br&gt; Pour it up drink it up live it up give it up&lt;br&gt; Oh my god dammit there’t the fucking limit&lt;br&gt; Pour it up drink it up live it up give it up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Badeusio&lt;br&gt; But i can’t stop&lt;br&gt; Making bottles pop until the wheels fall off&lt;br&gt; Badeusio&lt;br&gt; And i can’t quit&lt;br&gt; I wake up in the morning do the same shit&lt;br&gt; Wake up in the morning do the same shit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Waking and baking, shaking the flees&lt;br&gt; Caking and baking, raking the cheese&lt;br&gt; Early in the morning in the bathroom&lt;br&gt; On my knees tipping and dripping, flipping the flow&lt;br&gt; Whipping and dripping a drink on the floor&lt;br&gt; This it the only way that i was taught a long time ago&lt;br&gt; Seoul, korea, you’ll see a g-a like me-ah&lt;br&gt; Never would there ever be another like he-ah&lt;br&gt; G-A-N-G-S-T-A, nothing left to say&lt;br&gt; I done smoked my whole day&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover&lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover&lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover&lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Drink it up get sick&lt;br&gt; Bottoms up get wasted&lt;br&gt; Pour it up drink it up live it up give it up&lt;br&gt; Oh my god dammit there’t the fucking limit&lt;br&gt; Pour it up drink it up live it up give it up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Badeusio&lt;br&gt; But i can’t stop&lt;br&gt; Making bottles pop until the wheels fall off&lt;br&gt; Badeusio&lt;br&gt; And i can’t quit&lt;br&gt; I wake up in the morning do the same shit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Party’s over, it ain’t over&lt;br&gt; Tryna’ make a bad memory over and over&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Hangover hangover hangover hangover (hangover)&lt;br&gt; Party’s over, it ain’t over&lt;br&gt; Tryna find a single piece of me game over</Lyrics>
</Song>
