<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Something In The Water</Title>
    <Artist>Carrie Underwood</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/2/32d3ca5e23f4ccf1e4c8660c40e75f33_1335323175.png</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Something In The Water&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Carrie Underwood&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjEwJTJGMDElMkY1JTJGMCUyRjUwNjFkNzQ5ZmI0NzU3ZjA3ZWJkNTg2ZWI1MDk1NWNiLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>He said, &quot;I've been where you've been before.&lt;br&gt; Down every hallway's a slamming door.&lt;br&gt; No way out, no one to come and save me.&lt;br&gt; Wasting a life that the Good Lord gave me.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Then somebody said what I'm saying to you,&lt;br&gt; Opened my eyes and told me the truth.&quot;&lt;br&gt; They said, &quot;Just a little faith, it'll all get better.&quot;&lt;br&gt; So I followed that preacher man down to the river and now I'm changed&lt;br&gt; And now I'm stronger&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There must've been something in the water&lt;br&gt; Oh, there must've been something in the water&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Well, I heard what he said and I went on my way&lt;br&gt; Didn't think about it for a couple of days&lt;br&gt; Then it hit me like a lightning late one night&lt;br&gt; I was all out of hope and all out of fight&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Couldn't fight back the tears so I fell on my knees&lt;br&gt; Saying, &quot;God, if you're there come and rescue me.&quot;&lt;br&gt; Felt love pouring down from above&lt;br&gt; Got washed in the water, washed in the blood and now I'm changed&lt;br&gt; And now I'm stronger&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There must be something in the water&lt;br&gt; Oh, there must be something in the water&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And now I'm singing along to amazing grace&lt;br&gt; Can't nobody wipe this smile off my face&lt;br&gt; Got joy in my heart, angels on my side&lt;br&gt; Thank God almighty, I saw the light&lt;br&gt; Gonna look ahead, no turning back&lt;br&gt; Live every day, give it all that I have&lt;br&gt; Trust in someone bigger than me&lt;br&gt; Ever since the day that I believed I am changed&lt;br&gt; And now I'm stronger&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There must be something in the water (amazing grace)&lt;br&gt; Oh, there must be something in the water (how sweet the sound)&lt;br&gt; Oh, there must be something in the water (that saved a wretch)&lt;br&gt; Oh, there must be something in the water (like me)&lt;br&gt; Oh, yeah&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I am changed (I once was lost)&lt;br&gt; Stronger (but now I'm found)&lt;br&gt; (was blind but now I see)</Lyrics>
</Song>
