<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Guts Over Fear</Title>
    <Artist>Eminem ft. Sia</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/0/a0538a67982e1ef3e3bd2922cb6dd9ce_1383013435.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Guts Over Fear&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Eminem , Sia&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA5JTJGMDIlMkYzJTJGOSUyRjM5MjkwMDE5NTgwMGJjNTRhNmRlM2UwZTc1MzNjNjRlLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Bridge: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; Feels like a close, it’s coming to&lt;br&gt; Fuck am I gonna do?&lt;br&gt; It's too late to start over&lt;br&gt; This is the only thing I, thing I know&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; Sometimes I feel like all I ever do is find different ways to word the same old song&lt;br&gt; Ever since I came along from the day the song called, ‘’Hi! My Name Is’’ dropped&lt;br&gt; Started thinking my name was Fault, cause any time things went wrong&lt;br&gt; I was the one who they would blame it on&lt;br&gt; The media made me the e-quivalent of a modern-day Genghis Khan&lt;br&gt; Tried to argue it was only entertainment, dawg&lt;br&gt; Gangsta? Naw, courageous balls&lt;br&gt; Had to change my style, they said I'm way too soft&lt;br&gt; And I sound like AZ and Nas, out came the claws&lt;br&gt; And the fangs been out since then&lt;br&gt; But up until the instant that I’ve went against it&lt;br&gt; It was ingrained in me that I wouldn’t amount to a shitstain I thought&lt;br&gt; No wonder I had to unlearn everything my brain was taught&lt;br&gt; Do I really belong in this game? I pondered&lt;br&gt; I just wanna play my part, should I make waves or not?&lt;br&gt; So back and forth in my brain the tug of war wages on&lt;br&gt; And I don’t wanna seem ungrateful or disrespect the artform I was raised upon&lt;br&gt; But sometimes you gotta take a loss&lt;br&gt; And have people rub it in your face before you get made pissed off&lt;br&gt; And keep pluggin’, it’s your only outlet&lt;br&gt; And your only outfit so you know they gonna talk about it&lt;br&gt; Better find a way to counter it quick and make it, ah&lt;br&gt; Feel like I’ve already said this a kabillion eighty times&lt;br&gt; How many times can I say the same thing different ways that rhyme?&lt;br&gt; What I really wanna say is, if there's anyone else that can relate to my story&lt;br&gt; Bet you feel the same way I felt when I was in the same place you are&lt;br&gt; When I was afraid to…&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook: Sia]&lt;br&gt; I was a...&lt;br&gt; Afraid to make a single sound&lt;br&gt; Afraid I would never find a way out, out, out&lt;br&gt; Afraid I'd never be found&lt;br&gt; I didn’t wanna go another round&lt;br&gt; An angry man's power will shut you up&lt;br&gt; Trip wires fill this house with tip-toe love&lt;br&gt; Run out of excuses with every word&lt;br&gt; So here I am and I will not run&lt;br&gt; Guts over fear, the time is here&lt;br&gt; Guts over fear, I shall not tear&lt;br&gt; For all the times I let you push me around&lt;br&gt; And let you keep me down&lt;br&gt; Now I got, guts over fear, guts over fear&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; It’s like I was there once, single parents&lt;br&gt; Hate your appearance, did you struggle to find your place in this world?&lt;br&gt; And the pain spawns all the anger on&lt;br&gt; But it wasn’t until I put the pain in songs learned who to aim it on&lt;br&gt; That I made a spark, started to spit hard as shit&lt;br&gt; Learned how to harness it while the reins were off&lt;br&gt; And there was a lot of bizarre shit, but the crazy part&lt;br&gt; Was soon as I stopped saying &quot;I gave a fuck&quot;&lt;br&gt; Haters started to appreciate my art&lt;br&gt; And it just breaks my heart to look at all the pain I’ve caused&lt;br&gt; But what am I gonna do when the rage is gone?&lt;br&gt; And the lights go out in that trailer park?&lt;br&gt; And the window is closing and there’s nowhere else that I can go with flows&lt;br&gt; And I’m frozen cause there’s no more emotion for me to pull from&lt;br&gt; Just a bunch of playful songs that I made for fun&lt;br&gt; So to the break of dawn here I go recycling the same, old song&lt;br&gt; But I’d rather make “Not Afraid 2” than make another mothafuckin’ “We Made You” uh&lt;br&gt; Now I don’t wanna seem indulgent when I discuss my lows and my highs&lt;br&gt; My demise and my uprise, pray to God&lt;br&gt; I just opened enough eyes later on&lt;br&gt; And gave you the supplies and the tools to hopefully use it to make you strong&lt;br&gt; Enough to lift yourself up when you feel like I felt&lt;br&gt; Cause I can’t explain to y’all how dang exhausted my legs felt&lt;br&gt; Just having to balance my dang self&lt;br&gt; But on eggshells I was made to walk&lt;br&gt; But thank you, ma, ‘cause that gave me the&lt;br&gt; Strength to cause Shady-mania, so when they empty that stadium&lt;br&gt; At least I made it out of that house and a found a place in this world when the day was done&lt;br&gt; So this is for every kid who all’s they ever did was dreamt of one day just getting accepted&lt;br&gt; I represent him or her, anyone similar, you are the reason that I made this song&lt;br&gt; And everything you're scared to say don't be afraid to say no more&lt;br&gt; From this day forward, just let them a-holes talk&lt;br&gt; Take it with a grain of salt and eat their fucking faces off&lt;br&gt; The legend of the angry blonde lives on through you when I’m gone&lt;br&gt; And to think I was... gone</Lyrics>
</Song>
