<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>No Good In Goodbye</Title>
    <Artist>The Script</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/a/3a6d0c0285b3a25a36b9c1f8fec8641d_1410865812.png</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;No Good In Goodbye&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;The Script&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA5JTJGMTYlMkY5JTJGZSUyRjllMWNmZWNhZWIyMjUwM2EwMjAxM2I0NjUyNjc1NDdhLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>All the things that we've lost&lt;br&gt; Breaking off comes at a cost&lt;br&gt; And know I miss this mistake&lt;br&gt; Every word I try to choose&lt;br&gt; Either way I'm gonna lose&lt;br&gt; Can't take the ache from our break&lt;br&gt; Oh but as you walk away&lt;br&gt; You don't hear me say&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;good&quot; in goodbye?&lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;nice&quot; in nice try?&lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;us&quot; in trust gone?&lt;br&gt; Where's the soul in &quot;soldier on&quot;?&lt;br&gt; I'm alone and lonely&lt;br&gt; Cause I don't own the only&lt;br&gt; I can take this mistake&lt;br&gt; But I can't take the ache from heartbreak&lt;br&gt; Can't take the ache from heartbreak&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; No matter how it falls apart&lt;br&gt; There's a &quot;not&quot; in breaking hearts&lt;br&gt; But there's no &quot;fair&quot; in farewell, no&lt;br&gt; When I see you in the street&lt;br&gt; Afraid to God&lt;br&gt; You don't see the silent hail and I wish you well&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh but as you walk away&lt;br&gt; You don't hear me say&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;good&quot; in goodbye?&lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;nice&quot; in nice try?&lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;us&quot; in trust gone?&lt;br&gt; Where's the soul in &quot;soldier on&quot;?&lt;br&gt; I'm alone and lonely&lt;br&gt; Cause I don't own the only&lt;br&gt; I can take this mistake&lt;br&gt; But I can't take the ache from heartbreak&lt;br&gt; I can't take the ache from heartbreak&lt;br&gt; I can't take the ache from heartbreak&lt;br&gt; I can't take the ache from heartbreak&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If I could turn back time then I would re-write those lines&lt;br&gt; If I could turn back time then I would re-write those lines&lt;br&gt; If I could turn back time then I would re-write those lines&lt;br&gt; If I could turn back time then I would re-write those lines&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;good&quot; in goodbye?&lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;nice&quot; in nice try?&lt;br&gt; Where's the &quot;us&quot; in trust gone?&lt;br&gt; Where's the soul in &quot;soldier on&quot;?&lt;br&gt; I'm alone and lonely&lt;br&gt; Cause I don't own the only&lt;br&gt; I can take this mistake&lt;br&gt; But I can't take the ache from heartbreak&lt;br&gt; I can't take the ache from heartbreak</Lyrics>
</Song>
