<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Love Me Harder</Title>
    <Artist>Ariana Grande ft. The Weeknd</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/6/56fe58c5fed8a94d99bb42eafd978159_1418481381.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Love Me Harder&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Ariana Grande , The Weeknd&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjA4JTJGMjclMkY1JTJGMSUyRjUxMjYxN2IyZWY3MGQ5YzAwOGExNGM0MTBlNDkwOThmLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Ariana Grande:]&lt;br&gt; Tell me something I need to know&lt;br&gt; Then take my breath and never let it go&lt;br&gt; If you just let me invade your space&lt;br&gt; I'll take the pleasure, take away the pain&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And if in the moment I bite my lip&lt;br&gt; Baby, in the moment, you'll know this is&lt;br&gt; Something bigger than us and beyond bliss&lt;br&gt; Give me a reason to believe it&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'Cause if you want to keep me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder&lt;br&gt; And if you really need me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder&lt;br&gt; Gotta love me harder&lt;br&gt; Love me, love me, love me&lt;br&gt; Harder, harder, harder&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [The Weeknd:]&lt;br&gt; I know your motives and you know mine&lt;br&gt; The ones that love me, I tend to leave behind&lt;br&gt; If you know about me and choose to stay&lt;br&gt; Then take this pleasure and take away the pain&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And if in the moment you bite your lip&lt;br&gt; When I get you moaning you know it's real&lt;br&gt; Can you feel the pressure between your hips?&lt;br&gt; I'll make it feel like the first time&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Ariana Grande &amp;amp; The Weeknd:]&lt;br&gt; 'Cause if you want to keep me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder (Imma love you harder)&lt;br&gt; And if you really need me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder (love me harder)&lt;br&gt; Love me, love me, love me&lt;br&gt; Harder, harder, harder&lt;br&gt; Love me, love me, love me&lt;br&gt; Harder, harder, harder&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So what would I do if I can't figure it out?&lt;br&gt; You got to try, try, try again&lt;br&gt; So what would I do if I can't figure it out?&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna leave, leave, leave again&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'Cause if you want to keep me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder (Imma love you, love you, love you)&lt;br&gt; And if you really need me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder (love me, love me, baby)&lt;br&gt; 'Cause if you want to keep me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder (love me harder)&lt;br&gt; And if you really need me, you gotta gotta gotta gotta got to love me harder (Imma love you harder)&lt;br&gt; Love me, love me, love me&lt;br&gt; Harder, harder, harder&lt;br&gt; (love me, love me, baby)&lt;br&gt; Love me, love me, love me&lt;br&gt; (just a little bit, just a little bit harder, babe)&lt;br&gt; Harder, harder, harder</Lyrics>
</Song>
