<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Anaconda</Title>
    <Artist>Nicki Minaj</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/5/5594ce2fe757f686980333c67f8d4ee7_1416805932.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Anaconda&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Nicki Minaj&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjEyJTJGMTUlMkYyJTJGYSUyRjJhNDI0NjMyYjM4ZDgzNTgxYmZlNGUwYzYyMTM4M2ZlLm1wMyU3QzEz&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't want none unless you got buns, hun&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boy toy named troy, used to live in Detroit&lt;br&gt; Big dope dealer money, he was getting some coins&lt;br&gt; Was a shooter with the law, but he live in a palace&lt;br&gt; Bought me Alexander McQueen, he was keeping my stylish&lt;br&gt; Now thats r-r-real, gun in my purse, bitch I came for us to kill&lt;br&gt; Who wanna go first? I had them push daffodils&lt;br&gt; I'm high as hell, I only took a half of pill&lt;br&gt; I'm on some dumb shit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; By the way, what he say?&lt;br&gt; He can tell I ain't missing no meals&lt;br&gt; Come through and fuck em in my automobile&lt;br&gt; And I'm hitting it with his girls, and he telling me to chill&lt;br&gt; And he telling me it's real, that he love my sex appeal&lt;br&gt; Say he don't like em boney, he want something he can grab&lt;br&gt; So I pulled up in the Jag, and I hit em with the jab like&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't want none unless you got buns, hun&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Look at her butt (look at her butt)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This dude named Michael used to buy motorcycles&lt;br&gt; Dick bigger than a tower, I ain't talking about Eiffel&lt;br&gt; Real country ass nigga, let me play with his rifle&lt;br&gt; Pussy put his ass to sleep, now he calling me NyQuil&lt;br&gt; Now that bang bang bang, I let him hit it cause he slang cocaine&lt;br&gt; He toss my salad like his name Romaine&lt;br&gt; And when we done, I make him buy me romaine&lt;br&gt; I'm on some dumb shit&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; By the way, what he say?&lt;br&gt; He can tell I ain't missing no meals&lt;br&gt; Come through and fuck em in my automobile&lt;br&gt; And I'm hitting it with his girls, and he telling me to chill&lt;br&gt; And he telling me it's real, that he love my sex appeal&lt;br&gt; Say he don't like em boney, he want something he can grab&lt;br&gt; So I pulled up in the Jag, Mayweather with the jab like&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't want none unless you got buns, hun&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Look at her butt (Look at her butt)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; My anaconda don't want none unless you got bunsm hun&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't don't don't, my anaconda don't&lt;br&gt; Don't want none unless you got buns, hun&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh, look at her butt&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah, he love this fat ass&lt;br&gt; Yeah, this one is for my bitches with a fat ass in the fucking club&lt;br&gt; I said, where my fat ass big bitches in the club?&lt;br&gt; Fuck the skinny bitches, fuck the skinny bitches in the club&lt;br&gt; I wanna see all the big fat ass bitches in the motherfucking club&lt;br&gt; Fuck you if you skinny bitches WHAT?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I got a big fat ass&lt;br&gt; Come on</Lyrics>
</Song>
