<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Feeling Myself</Title>
    <Artist>Nicki Minaj ft. Beyoncé</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/5/5594ce2fe757f686980333c67f8d4ee7_1416805932.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Feeling Myself&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Nicki Minaj , Beyonc\u00e9&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjEyJTJGMTUlMkZmJTJGOCUyRmY4YTExZWVhYjBkMDI1NzBlMmIyZjRmZGQ3ZDkzMTJhLm1wMyU3QzEz&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Intro - Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; Yo B, they ready&lt;br&gt; Let's go&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Beyoncé:]&lt;br&gt; I'm feelin' myself, I'm feelin' myself&lt;br&gt; I'm feelin' my, feelin' myself&lt;br&gt; I'm feelin' myself, I'm feelin' my, feelin' my, feelin' myself&lt;br&gt; I'm feelin' myself, I'm feelin' my, feelin' myself&lt;br&gt; I'm feelin' myself, I'm feelin' my&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1 - Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; I'm with some hood girls lookin' back at it&lt;br&gt; And a good girl in my tax bracket&lt;br&gt; Got a black card that let Saks have it&lt;br&gt; These Chanel bags is a bad habit&lt;br&gt; I-I do balls, Dal Mavericks, my Maybach, black magnet&lt;br&gt; Bitch, never left but I'm back at it&lt;br&gt; And I'm feelin' myself, jack rabbit&lt;br&gt; Feelin' myself, back off, cause I'm feelin' myself, jack off&lt;br&gt; Heard he thinks about me when he whacks off&lt;br&gt; Whacks on? Wax off&lt;br&gt; National anthem hats off, then I curve that nigga, like a bad toss&lt;br&gt; Lemme get a number 2, with some Mac sauce&lt;br&gt; On The Run Tour, with my mask off&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Beyoncé]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge 1 - Beyoncé:]&lt;br&gt; Changed the game with that digital drop&lt;br&gt; Know where you was when that digital popped&lt;br&gt; I stopped the world&lt;br&gt; Male or female, it make no difference&lt;br&gt; I stop the world, world stop...&lt;br&gt; Carry on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2 - Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; Kitty on pink, pretty on fleek&lt;br&gt; Pretty gang, always keep them niggas on geek&lt;br&gt; Ridin' through Texas, fearin' for his breakfast&lt;br&gt; Everytime I whip it, I be talkin' so reckless&lt;br&gt; He said &quot;Damn Nicki it's tight,&quot; I say &quot;Yeah nigga you right&quot;&lt;br&gt; He say &quot;Damn, bae, you so little, but you be really takin' that pipe&quot;&lt;br&gt; I say &quot;Yes daddy I do, gimme brain like NYU&quot;&lt;br&gt; I said &quot;Teach me, nigga, teach me. All this learnin' here is by you&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-Chorus - Beyoncé:]&lt;br&gt; I'm whippin' that work, he diggin' that work&lt;br&gt; I got it, tiny sips of that 36 of that real&lt;br&gt; Hank full of that bounce baby&lt;br&gt; Come get you some of that bounce baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Beyoncé]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge 2 - Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; Cookin' up the base, lookin' like a kilo&lt;br&gt; He just wanna taste, buildin' up my ego&lt;br&gt; Ego, ego, ego, ego, ego, ego, ego, ego&lt;br&gt; Ridin' through Texas, smokin' all off&lt;br&gt; Talkin' bout that high-grade, baby hold up&lt;br&gt; I can heal your migraine&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 3 - Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; Bitches ain't got punchlines or flow&lt;br&gt; I have both and an empire also&lt;br&gt; He gettin' gifts from Santa Claus at the North Pole&lt;br&gt; Today I'm icy, but I'm prayin' for some more snow&lt;br&gt; Let that ho ho, let that ho know, he in love with that coco&lt;br&gt; Why these bitches don't never be learnin'&lt;br&gt; You bitches will never get what I be earnin'&lt;br&gt; I'm still gettin' plaques, from my records that's urban&lt;br&gt; Ain't gotta rely on top 40&lt;br&gt; I am a rap legend, just go ask the kings of rap&lt;br&gt; Who is the queen and things of that&lt;br&gt; Nature, look at my finger, that is a glacier, hits like a lazer&lt;br&gt; Trippin' on that work, trippin' off that purp&lt;br&gt; Flippin' up my skirt and I be whippin' all that work&lt;br&gt; Takin' trips with all them ki's, car keys got b's&lt;br&gt; Stingin' with the Queen B and we be whippin' all that D&lt;br&gt; Cause we dope girls we flawless, we the poster girls for all this&lt;br&gt; We run around with them ballers, only real niggas on my call list&lt;br&gt; I'm the big kahuna, go let them whores know&lt;br&gt; Just on this song alone, bitch is on her fourth flow&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro - Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; You like it don't you? Snitches!&lt;br&gt; Young money</Lyrics>
</Song>
