<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Take Me To Church</Title>
    <Artist>Hozier</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/f/f/ff97ec949e594dbd521125b06a498941_1417060417.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Take Me To Church&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Hozier&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjEwJTJGMTclMkZiJTJGNiUyRmI2NmUyOGIyZTk2Yzk3MzAzYmI3MjllZDU1MzQyNmQ5Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Take Me To Church&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My lover's got humour&lt;br&gt; She's the giggle at a funeral&lt;br&gt; Knows everybody's disapproval&lt;br&gt; I should've worshiped her sooner&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If the heavens ever did speak&lt;br&gt; She's the last true mouthpiece&lt;br&gt; Every Sunday's getting more bleak&lt;br&gt; A fresh poison each week&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'We were born sick,' you heard them say it&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My Church offers no absolutes.&lt;br&gt; She tells me, 'Worship in the bedroom.'&lt;br&gt; The only heaven I'll be sent to&lt;br&gt; Is when I'm alone with you—&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I was born sick,&lt;br&gt; But I love it&lt;br&gt; Command me to be well&lt;br&gt; Amen. Amen. Amen. Amen.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus 2x:]&lt;br&gt; Take me to church&lt;br&gt; I'll worship like a dog at the shrine of your lies&lt;br&gt; I'll tell you my sins and you can sharpen your knife&lt;br&gt; Offer me that deathless death&lt;br&gt; Good God, let me give you my life&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If I'm a pagan of the good times&lt;br&gt; My lover's the sunlight&lt;br&gt; To keep the Goddess on my side&lt;br&gt; She demands a sacrifice&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Drain the whole sea&lt;br&gt; Get something shiny&lt;br&gt; Something meaty for the main course&lt;br&gt; That's a fine looking high horse&lt;br&gt; What you got in the stable?&lt;br&gt; We've a lot of starving faithful&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; That looks tasty&lt;br&gt; That looks plenty&lt;br&gt; This is hungry work&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus 2x:]&lt;br&gt; Take me to church&lt;br&gt; I'll worship like a dog at the shrine of your lies&lt;br&gt; I'll tell you my sins so you can sharpen your knife&lt;br&gt; Offer me my deathless death&lt;br&gt; Good God, let me give you my life&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; No Masters or Kings&lt;br&gt; When the Ritual begins&lt;br&gt; There is no sweeter innocence than our gentle sin&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; In the madness and soil of that sad earthly scene&lt;br&gt; Only then I am Human&lt;br&gt; Only then I am Clean&lt;br&gt; Amen. Amen. Amen. Amen.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus 2x:]&lt;br&gt; Take me to church&lt;br&gt; I'll worship like a dog at the shrine of your lies&lt;br&gt; I'll tell you my sins and you can sharpen your knife&lt;br&gt; Offer me that deathless death&lt;br&gt; Good God, let me give you my life</Lyrics>
</Song>
