<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Night Changes</Title>
    <Artist>One Direction</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/3/33c66a251c290a2fc4d6bc546922479e_1375756197.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Night Changes&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;One Direction&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjExJTJGMTclMkZiJTJGZCUyRmJkNDZlNDc4YjlhOTg2ZWJiN2E4MjEyNmRiY2U3OTdjLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Night Changes&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Going out tonight&lt;br&gt; Changes into something red&lt;br&gt; Her mother doesn't like that kind of dress&lt;br&gt; Everything she never had she's showing off&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Driving too fast&lt;br&gt; Moon is breaking through her hair&lt;br&gt; She said it was something that she won't forget&lt;br&gt; Having no regrets is all that she really wants&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We're only getting older baby&lt;br&gt; And I've been thinking about it lately&lt;br&gt; Does it ever drive you crazy&lt;br&gt; Just how fast the night changes?&lt;br&gt; Everything that you've ever dreamed of&lt;br&gt; Disappearing when you wake up&lt;br&gt; But there's nothing to be afraid of&lt;br&gt; Even when the night changes&lt;br&gt; It will never change me and you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Chasing it tonight,&lt;br&gt; Doubts are running ‘round her head&lt;br&gt; He's waiting, hides behind a cigarette&lt;br&gt; Heart is beating loud, she doesn't want it to stop&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Moving too fast&lt;br&gt; Moon is lighting up her skin&lt;br&gt; She's falling, doesn't even know it yet&lt;br&gt; Having no regrets is all that she really wants&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We're only getting older baby&lt;br&gt; And I've been thinking about it lately&lt;br&gt; Does it ever drive you crazy&lt;br&gt; Just how fast the night changes?&lt;br&gt; Everything that you've ever dreamed of&lt;br&gt; Disappearing when you wake up&lt;br&gt; But there's nothing to be afraid of&lt;br&gt; Even when the night changes&lt;br&gt; It will never change me and you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Going out tonight&lt;br&gt; Changes into something red&lt;br&gt; Her mother doesn't like that kind of dress&lt;br&gt; Reminds her of a missing piece of innocence she lost&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We're only getting older baby&lt;br&gt; And I've been thinking about it lately&lt;br&gt; Does it ever drive you crazy&lt;br&gt; Just how fast the night changes?&lt;br&gt; Everything that you've ever dreamed of&lt;br&gt; Disappearing when you wake up&lt;br&gt; But there's nothing to be afraid of&lt;br&gt; Even when the night changes&lt;br&gt; It will never change, baby&lt;br&gt; It will never change, baby&lt;br&gt; It will never change me and you</Lyrics>
</Song>
