<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Uptown Funk</Title>
    <Artist>Mark Ronson ft. Bruno Mars</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/6/5/65027fbabf28e67900b16abb8f757433_1386224159.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Uptown Funk&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Mark Ronson , Bruno Mars&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNSUyRjAxJTJGMTMlMkY4JTJGMyUyRjgzYTU1NWZhMmZmN2ZmMmExZjVlOTI5ODM5ZDUzMDY5Lm1wMyU3QzEz&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh duh (Aaaaaaow!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This hit&lt;br&gt; That ice cold&lt;br&gt; Michelle Pfeiffer&lt;br&gt; That white gold&lt;br&gt; This one, for them hood girls&lt;br&gt; Them good girls&lt;br&gt; Straight masterpieces&lt;br&gt; Stylin', while in&lt;br&gt; Livin' it up in the city&lt;br&gt; Got Chucks on with Saint Laurent&lt;br&gt; Gotta kiss myself I'm so pretty&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Called a police and a fireman&lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Make a dragon wanna retire, man&lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Say my name you know who I am&lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Am I bad 'bout that money&lt;br&gt; Break it down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Girls hit you hallelujah (whuoo)&lt;br&gt; Girls hit you hallelujah (whuoo)&lt;br&gt; Girls hit you hallelujah (whuoo)&lt;br&gt; 'Cause Uptown Funk gon' give it to you&lt;br&gt; 'Cause Uptown Funk gon' give it to you&lt;br&gt; 'Cause Uptown Funk gon' give it to you&lt;br&gt; Saturday night and we in the spot&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch (Come on)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh (Hah!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh (Hah!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey, oh!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Stop&lt;br&gt; Wait a minute&lt;br&gt; Fill my cup put some liquor in it&lt;br&gt; Take a sip, sign a check&lt;br&gt; Julio! Get the stretch!&lt;br&gt; Ride to Harlem, Hollywood, Jackson, Mississippi&lt;br&gt; If we show up, we gon' show out&lt;br&gt; Smoother than a fresh jar o' Skippy&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Called a police and a fireman&lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Make a dragon wanna retire, man&lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn) (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Bitch, say my name you know who I am&lt;br&gt; I'm too hot (hot damn)&lt;br&gt; Am I bad 'bout that money&lt;br&gt; Break it down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Girls hit your hallelujah (whuoo)&lt;br&gt; Girls hit your hallelujah (whuoo)&lt;br&gt; Girls hit your hallelujah (whuoo)&lt;br&gt; 'Cause Uptown Funk gon' give it to you&lt;br&gt; 'Cause Uptown Funk gon' give it to you&lt;br&gt; 'Cause Uptown Funk gon' give it to you&lt;br&gt; Saturday night and we in the spot&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch (come on)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh (Hah!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh (Hah!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey, oh!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Before we leave&lt;br&gt; Let me tell y'all a lil' something&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; I said Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Come on, dance&lt;br&gt; Jump on it&lt;br&gt; If you sexy then flaunt it&lt;br&gt; If you freaky then own it&lt;br&gt; Don't brag about it, come show me&lt;br&gt; Come on, dance&lt;br&gt; Jump on it&lt;br&gt; If you sexy then flaunt it&lt;br&gt; Well it's Saturday night and we in the spot&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch (come on)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh (Hah!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Doh&lt;br&gt; Doh doh doh, doh doh doh, doh doh (Hah!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Don't believe me, just watch&lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey, oh!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up (say whaa?!)&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up (say whaa?!)&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up (say whaa?!)&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up, Uptown Funk you up (say whaa?!)&lt;br&gt; Uptown Funk you up&lt;br&gt; Aaaaaaow!</Lyrics>
</Song>
