<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Lips Are Movin</Title>
    <Artist>Meghan Trainor</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/8/5/85175de757e36e4d6b9008bc0dd08b09_1413891522.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Lips Are Movin&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Meghan Trainor&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNSUyRjAxJTJGMTElMkZiJTJGMCUyRmIwZDdlYTRlYjhiOWMwMmNlMTMzMTQ1NzQ3M2IxNjk0Lm1wMyU3QzEz&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>If your lips are moving, if your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, then you're lyin', lyin', lyin', baby&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, if your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, i said you're lyin', lyin', lyin', baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boy, look at me in my face&lt;br&gt; Tell me that you're not just about this bass&lt;br&gt; You really think I could be replaced&lt;br&gt; Nah, I come from outer space&lt;br&gt; And I'm a classy girl, I'mma hold it up&lt;br&gt; You're full of something but it ain't love&lt;br&gt; And what we got, straight overdue&lt;br&gt; Go find somebody new&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can buy me diamond earrings and deny-ny-ny, ny-ny-ny, deny-ny&lt;br&gt; But I smell her on your collar so goodbye-bye-bye, bye-bye-bye&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I know you lie&lt;br&gt; 'Cause your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; Tell me do you think I'm dumb?&lt;br&gt; I might be young, but I ain't stupid&lt;br&gt; Talking around in circles with your tongue&lt;br&gt; I gave you bass, you gave me sweet talk&lt;br&gt; Saying how I'm your number one&lt;br&gt; But I know you lie&lt;br&gt; 'Cause your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; Baby, don't you know I'm done&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, if your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, then you're lyin', lyin', lyin', baby&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, if your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, then you're lyin', lyin', lyin', baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hey, baby, don't you bring them tears&lt;br&gt; 'Cause it's too late, too late, baby&lt;br&gt; You only love me when you're here&lt;br&gt; You're so two-faced, two-faced, babe&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can buy me diamond earrings and deny-ny-ny, ny-ny-ny, deny-ny&lt;br&gt; But I smell her on your collar so goodbye-bye-bye, bye-bye-bye&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I know you lie&lt;br&gt; 'Cause your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; Tell me do you think I'm dumb?&lt;br&gt; I might be young, but I ain't stupid&lt;br&gt; Talking around in circles with your tongue&lt;br&gt; I gave you bass, you gave me sweet talk&lt;br&gt; Saying how I'm your number one&lt;br&gt; But I know you lie&lt;br&gt; 'Cause your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; Baby, don't you know I'm done&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Come on, say!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, if your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving, then you're lyin', lyin', lyin', baby&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving (Alright now)&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving (I wanna hear ya'll singing with me)&lt;br&gt; If your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; Then you're lyin', lyin', lyin', baby (Here we go)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I know you lie&lt;br&gt; 'Cause your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; Tell me do you think I'm dumb?&lt;br&gt; I might be young, but I ain't stupid&lt;br&gt; Talking around in circles with your tongue&lt;br&gt; I gave you bass, you gave me sweet talk&lt;br&gt; Saying how I'm your number one&lt;br&gt; But I know you lie&lt;br&gt; 'Cause your lips are moving&lt;br&gt; Baby, don't you know I'm done</Lyrics>
</Song>
