<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Bed Of Lies</Title>
    <Artist>Nicki Minaj ft. Skylar Grey</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/5/5594ce2fe757f686980333c67f8d4ee7_1416805932.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Bed Of Lies&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Nicki Minaj , Skylar Grey&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjEyJTJGMTUlMkYwJTJGZCUyRjBkZTgxZWZlNDZkNmIzYzA2OGZmNzU5N2YwMDE0ODM0Lm1wMyU3QzEz&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Hook - Skylar Grey:]&lt;br&gt; Do you ever think of me when you lie,&lt;br&gt; Lie down in your bed, your bed of lies?&lt;br&gt; And I knew better than to look in your eyes&lt;br&gt; They only pretend you would be mine&lt;br&gt; And oh how you made me believe&lt;br&gt; You had me caught in every web that you weave&lt;br&gt; But do you ever think of me when you lie,&lt;br&gt; Lie down in your bed, your bed of lies?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; You could never make eye contact&lt;br&gt; Everything you got was based off of my contacts&lt;br&gt; You a fraud, but I'mma remain icon-stat&lt;br&gt; Balenciaga's on my boots with the python strap&lt;br&gt; You was caught up in the rush, and you was caught up in the thrill of it&lt;br&gt; You was with me way before I hit a quarter mil' in it&lt;br&gt; Put you in the crib and you ain't never pay a bill in it&lt;br&gt; I was killin' it, man you got me poppin' pills in it&lt;br&gt; I told Baby hit you, I said this nigga buggin'&lt;br&gt; Cause I was doing it for us, I told 'em fuck the public&lt;br&gt; Couldn't believe that I was home alone contemplating&lt;br&gt; Overdosin', no more coastin', no more toastin' over oceans&lt;br&gt; They say you don't know what you got 'til it's gone&lt;br&gt; They say that your darkest hour comes before your dawn&lt;br&gt; But there was something I should've asked all along&lt;br&gt; I'mma ask on the song&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Skylar Grey:]&lt;br&gt; Do you ever think of me when you lie,&lt;br&gt; Lie down in your bed, your bed of lies?&lt;br&gt; And I knew better than to look in your eyes&lt;br&gt; They only pretend you would be mine&lt;br&gt; And oh how you made me believe&lt;br&gt; You had me caught in every web that you weave&lt;br&gt; But do you ever think of me when you lie,&lt;br&gt; Lie down in your bed, your bed of lies?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Nicki Minaj:]&lt;br&gt; I just figured if you saw me, if you looked in my eyes&lt;br&gt; You'd remember our connection and be freed from the lies&lt;br&gt; I just figured I was something that you couldn't replace&lt;br&gt; But there was just a blank stare and I couldn't relate&lt;br&gt; I just couldn't understand and I couldn't defend&lt;br&gt; What we had, what we shared, and I couldn't pretend&lt;br&gt; When the tears roll down it's like you ain't even notice em&lt;br&gt; If you had a heart, I was hoping you that would've showed it some&lt;br&gt; What the fuck you really telling me, what you telling me&lt;br&gt; I could tell you lying, get the fuck out, don't yell at me&lt;br&gt; I ain't mean to cut you, I ain't wanna catch a felony&lt;br&gt; This ain't How To Be A Player, you ain't Bill Bellamy&lt;br&gt; They say you don't know what you got 'til it's gone&lt;br&gt; They say that your darkest hour come before your dawn&lt;br&gt; But there was something that I should've asked all along&lt;br&gt; I'mma ask on the song&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Skylar Grey:]&lt;br&gt; So does she know I've been in that bed before&lt;br&gt; A thousand count, and not a single thread of truth&lt;br&gt; If I was just another girl&lt;br&gt; Then I'm ashamed to say that I'm not over you&lt;br&gt; There's one thing I need to know&lt;br&gt; So call me, when you're not so busy just thinking of yourself&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Skylar Grey:]&lt;br&gt; Do you ever think of me when you lie,&lt;br&gt; Lie down in your bed, your bed of lies?&lt;br&gt; And I knew better than to look in your eyes&lt;br&gt; They only pretend you would be mine&lt;br&gt; And oh how you made me believe&lt;br&gt; You had me caught in every web that you weave&lt;br&gt; But do you ever think of me when you lie,&lt;br&gt; Lie down in your bed, your bed of lies?</Lyrics>
</Song>
