<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>The Days</Title>
    <Artist>Avicii</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/f/bfa21f99ddb0c6c23b8f5e42213bb2e0_1375154566.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;The Days&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Avicii&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxNCUyRjEyJTJGMDYlMkZkJTJGZCUyRmRkZjU5NmY2N2JjMThmNTVjYjM0ODc4YWVkZGMzMzQ1Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Under the tree where the grass don't grow&lt;br&gt; We made a promise to never get old&lt;br&gt; You had a chance and you took it on me&lt;br&gt; And I made a promise that I couldn't keep.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Heart ache, heart break&lt;br&gt; All over town&lt;br&gt; But something flipped like a switch when you came around&lt;br&gt; And I'm in pieces, pick me up and put me together&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; These are the days we've been waiting for&lt;br&gt; On days like these who could ask for more?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Leave them coming 'cause we're not done yet&lt;br&gt; These are the days we won't regret&lt;br&gt; These are the days we won't forget&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; These are the days we've been waiting for&lt;br&gt; Rattle the cage and slam that door&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And the world is calling us but not just yet&lt;br&gt; These are the days we won't regret&lt;br&gt; These are the days we won't forget&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Out on the midnight the wild ones howl&lt;br&gt; The last of the lost boys have thrown in the towel&lt;br&gt; We used to believe we were stars aligned&lt;br&gt; You made a wish and I fell out of&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Time flew, cut through&lt;br&gt; All over town&lt;br&gt; You made me bleed when I look up and you're not around&lt;br&gt; But I'm in pieces, pick me up and put me together&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; These are the days we've been waiting for&lt;br&gt; On days like these who could ask for more?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Leave them coming 'cause we're not done yet&lt;br&gt; These are the days we won't regret&lt;br&gt; These are the days we won't forget&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; These are the days we've been waiting for&lt;br&gt; Neither of us knows what's in store,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You just roll your window down and place your bets&lt;br&gt; These are the days we won't regret&lt;br&gt; These are the days we will never forget!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And these are the days (and these are the days)&lt;br&gt; And these are the days (and these are the days)</Lyrics>
</Song>
