<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Super Bass</Title>
    <Artist>Nicki Minaj</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/5/5594ce2fe757f686980333c67f8d4ee7_1416805932.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Super Bass&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Nicki Minaj&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjA3JTJGMTclMkY4JTJGYSUyRjhhN2I2N2M5ODNmNjI3Y2VlNWQwNGNkMWVlMTEzMjI2Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>This one is for the boys with the boomin' system&lt;br&gt; Top down, AC with the coolin' system&lt;br&gt; When he come up in the club, he be blazin' up&lt;br&gt; Got stacks on deck like he savin' up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And he ill, he real, he might got a deal&lt;br&gt; He pop bottles and he got the right kind of build&lt;br&gt; He cold, he dope, he might sell coke&lt;br&gt; He always in the air, but he never fly coach&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; He a muthafuckin trip, trip, sailor of the ship, ship&lt;br&gt; When he make it drip, drip kiss him on the lip, lip&lt;br&gt; That's the kind of dude I was lookin' for&lt;br&gt; And yes you'll get slapped if you're lookin' ho&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I said, excuse me you're a hell of a guy&lt;br&gt; I mean my, my, my, my you're like pelican fly&lt;br&gt; I mean, you're so shy and I'm loving your tie&lt;br&gt; You're like slicker than the guy with the thing on his eye, oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yes I did, yes I did&lt;br&gt; Somebody please tell him who the eff I is&lt;br&gt; I am Nicki Minaj, I mack them dudes up&lt;br&gt; Back coupes up, and chuck the deuce up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boy you got my heartbeat runnin' away&lt;br&gt; Beating like a drum and it's coming your way&lt;br&gt; Can't you hear that boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; He got that super bass&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass&lt;br&gt; Yeah that's that super bass&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom, he got that super bass&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom, yeah that's that super bass&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This one is for the boys in the Polos&lt;br&gt; Entrepreneur niggas in the moguls&lt;br&gt; He could ball with the crew, he could solo&lt;br&gt; But I think I like him better when he dolo&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And I think I like him better with the fitted cap on&lt;br&gt; He ain't even gotta try to put the mac on&lt;br&gt; He just gotta give me that look, when he give me that look&lt;br&gt; Then the panties comin' off, off, unh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Excuse me, you're a hell of a guy&lt;br&gt; You know I really got a thing for American guys&lt;br&gt; I mean, sigh, sickenin' eyes&lt;br&gt; I can tell that you're in touch with your feminine side, oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yes I did, yes I did&lt;br&gt; Somebody please tell him who the eff I is&lt;br&gt; I am Nicki Minaj, I mack them dudes up&lt;br&gt; Back coupes up, and chuck the deuce up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boy you got my heartbeat runnin' away&lt;br&gt; Beating like a drum and it's coming your way&lt;br&gt; Can't you hear that boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; He got that super bass&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass&lt;br&gt; Yeah that's that super bass&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom, he got that super bass&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom, yeah that's that super bass&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; See I need you in my life for me to stay&lt;br&gt; No, no, no, no, no I know you'll stay&lt;br&gt; No, no, no, no, no don't go away&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boy you got my heartbeat runnin' away&lt;br&gt; Don't you hear that heartbeat comin' your way?&lt;br&gt; Oh it be like, boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass&lt;br&gt; Can't you hear that boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boy you got my heartbeat runnin' away&lt;br&gt; Beating like a drum and it's coming your way&lt;br&gt; Can't you hear that boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; He got that super bass&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom bass&lt;br&gt; Yeah that's that super bass&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom, he got that super bass&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom&lt;br&gt; Boom, badoom, boom, yeah that's that super bass</Lyrics>
</Song>
