<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Payphone</Title>
    <Artist>Maroon 5 ft. Wiz Khalifa</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/e/1/e1b9354eb2baf21f844023e5c526b479_1406601346.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Payphone&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Maroon 5,Wiz Khalifa&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjA4JTJGMjUlMkYzJTJGZSUyRjNlN2NmZTkxM2M4ZDMzYjMyZDQ5NmZmZTg3NzNiNTY3Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I'm at a payphone trying to call home&lt;br&gt; All of my change I spent on you&lt;br&gt; Where have the times gone, baby it's all wrong&lt;br&gt; Where are the plans we made for two?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah, I, I know it's hard to remember,&lt;br&gt; The people we used to be...&lt;br&gt; It's even harder to picture,&lt;br&gt; That you're not here next to me.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You say it's too late to make it,&lt;br&gt; But is it too late to try?&lt;br&gt; And in our time that you wasted&lt;br&gt; All of our bridges burned down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I've wasted my nights,&lt;br&gt; You turned out the lights&lt;br&gt; Now I'm paralyzed,&lt;br&gt; Still stuck in that time,&lt;br&gt; When we called it love,&lt;br&gt; But even the sun sets in paradise&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm at a payphone trying to call home&lt;br&gt; All of my change I spent on you&lt;br&gt; Where have the times gone, baby it's all wrong&lt;br&gt; Where are the plans we made for two?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If &quot;Happy Ever After&quot; did exist,&lt;br&gt; I would still be holding you like this&lt;br&gt; All those fairy tales are full of it.&lt;br&gt; One more stupid love song, I'll be sick&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh, you turned your back on tomorrow&lt;br&gt; Cause you forgot yesterday.&lt;br&gt; I gave you my love to borrow,&lt;br&gt; But you just gave it away.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can't expect me to be fine,&lt;br&gt; I don't expect you to care&lt;br&gt; I know I've said it before,&lt;br&gt; But all of our bridges burned down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I've wasted my nights,&lt;br&gt; You turned out the lights&lt;br&gt; Now I'm paralyzed,&lt;br&gt; Still stuck in that time,&lt;br&gt; When we called it love,&lt;br&gt; But even the sun sets in paradise&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm at a payphone trying to call home&lt;br&gt; All of my change I spent on you.&lt;br&gt; Where have the times gone, baby it's all wrong&lt;br&gt; Where are the plans we made for two?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If &quot;Happy Ever After&quot; did exist,&lt;br&gt; I would still be holding you like this&lt;br&gt; All those fairy tales are full of it.&lt;br&gt; One more stupid love song, I'll be sick&lt;br&gt; Now I'm at a payphone.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah, Yeah, Now baby don't hang up,&lt;br&gt; So I can tell you what you need to know,&lt;br&gt; Baby I'm begging you just please don't go,&lt;br&gt; So I can tell you what you need to know&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm at a payphone trying to call home&lt;br&gt; All of my change I spent on you&lt;br&gt; Where have the times gone, baby it's all wrong&lt;br&gt; Where are the plans we made for two?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If &quot;Happy Ever After&quot; did exist,&lt;br&gt; I would still be holding you like this&lt;br&gt; All those fairy tales are full of it.&lt;br&gt; One more stupid love song, I'll be sick&lt;br&gt; Now I'm at a payphone....</Lyrics>
</Song>
