<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Turn Me On</Title>
    <Artist>David Guetta ft. Nicki Minaj</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/c/4/c47da26125e495941ea93a424139b059_1408348759.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Turn Me On&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;David Guetta,Nicki Minaj&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjA3JTJGMTglMkY4JTJGMyUyRjgzOGFjMTk0NGI0OTk2ZTZiNmNmZmYxOTljYjA5ZGFkLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Doctor, doctor need you back home, baby.&lt;br&gt; Doctor, doctor where you at? Give me something.&lt;br&gt; I need your love, I need your love, I need your loving.&lt;br&gt; You got that kind of medicine that keep me coming.&lt;br&gt; My body needs a hero come and save me.&lt;br&gt; Something tells me you know how to save me.&lt;br&gt; I have been some we know.&lt;br&gt; Oh! I need you! To come and rescue me.&lt;br&gt; Oooooooooooooooo oooh!&lt;br&gt; Make me come alive, come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; Touch me, save my life come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; I’m too young to die, come on and turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on.&lt;br&gt; Make me come alive, come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; Touch me, save my life come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; I’m too young to die, come on and turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh you make it make it right.&lt;br&gt; My temp-era-ture is super high.&lt;br&gt; If I scream, if I cry.&lt;br&gt; It’s only ‘cause I feel alive&lt;br&gt; My body needs a hero come and save me.&lt;br&gt; Something tells me you know how to save me.&lt;br&gt; I have been some we know.&lt;br&gt; Oh! I need you! To come and rescue me.&lt;br&gt; Oooooooooooooooo oooh!&lt;br&gt; Make me come alive, come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; Touch me, save my life come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; I’m too young to die, come on and turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on.&lt;br&gt; Make me come alive, come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; Touch me, save my life come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; I’m too young to die, come on and turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on.&lt;br&gt; You’ve got my life in the palm of your hands.&lt;br&gt; Come and save me now. I know you can.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Uh! Uh! Dat dat dat dat don’t let me die young.&lt;br&gt; I just want you to father my young.&lt;br&gt; I just want you to be my doctor.&lt;br&gt; We could get it crac-kin’ chiro-prac-tor.&lt;br&gt; I I I I I I I I I, I know you can save me and make me feel alive.&lt;br&gt; Make me come alive, come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; Touch me, save my life come on and turn me on.&lt;br&gt; I’m too young to die, come on and turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on, turn me on.</Lyrics>
</Song>
