<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>How You Remind Me</Title>
    <Artist>Avril Lavigne</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/1/5/1596daf09fa4cd0ac2f9d017025ac2a4_1416279641.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;How You Remind Me&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Avril Lavigne&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjEyJTJGMTElMkYwJTJGNyUyRjA3OThlYzM1NWQ5YTI1OWExM2JiOWYyYTkwNzNlZjdmLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Never made it as a wise man&lt;br&gt; I couldn't cut it as a poor man stealing&lt;br&gt; Tired of living like a blind man&lt;br&gt; I'm sick of sight without a sense of feeling&lt;br&gt; And this is how you remind me&lt;br&gt; This is how you remind me&lt;br&gt; Of what I really am&lt;br&gt; This is how you remind me&lt;br&gt; Of what I really am&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's not like you to say sorry&lt;br&gt; I was waiting on a different story&lt;br&gt; This time I'm mistaken&lt;br&gt; for handing you a heart worth breaking&lt;br&gt; and I've been wrong, i've been down,&lt;br&gt; been to the bottom of every bottle&lt;br&gt; these five words in my head&lt;br&gt; scream &quot;are we having fun yet?&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; yeah, yeah, yeah, no, no&lt;br&gt; yeah, yeah, yeah, no, no&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; it's not like you didn't know that&lt;br&gt; I said I love you and I swear I still do&lt;br&gt; And it must have been so bad&lt;br&gt; Cause living with me must have damn near killed you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And this is how, you remind me&lt;br&gt; Of what I really am&lt;br&gt; This is how, you remind me&lt;br&gt; Of what I really am&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's not like you to say sorry&lt;br&gt; I was waiting on a different story&lt;br&gt; This time I'm mistaken&lt;br&gt; for handing you a heart worth breaking&lt;br&gt; and I've been wrong, i've been down,&lt;br&gt; been to the bottom of every bottle&lt;br&gt; these five words in my head&lt;br&gt; scream &quot;are we having fun yet?&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; yet, yet, yet, no, no&lt;br&gt; yet, yet, yet, no, no&lt;br&gt; yet, yet, yet, no, no&lt;br&gt; yet, yet, yet, no, no&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Never made it as a wise man&lt;br&gt; I couldn't cut it as a poor man stealing&lt;br&gt; And this is how you remind me&lt;br&gt; This is how you remind me&lt;br&gt; This is how you remind me&lt;br&gt; Of what i really am&lt;br&gt; This is how you remind me&lt;br&gt; Of what i really am&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's not like you to say sorry&lt;br&gt; I was waiting on a different story&lt;br&gt; This time I'm mistaken&lt;br&gt; for handing you a heart worth breaking&lt;br&gt; and I've been wrong, i've been down,&lt;br&gt; been to the bottom of every bottle&lt;br&gt; these five words in my head&lt;br&gt; scream &quot;are we having fun yet?&quot;&lt;br&gt; yet, yet&lt;br&gt; are we having fun yet [3x]</Lyrics>
</Song>
