<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>When I Was Your Man</Title>
    <Artist>Bruno Mars</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/a/aa00aea7d1c04ba40897d8b80ac6eea4_1415154852.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;When I Was Your Man&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Bruno Mars&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjEyJTJGMDYlMkYyJTJGYiUyRjJiODhhYWY2YjQ3ZDA1ZGQyY2MwODMyODJkMGNiYzAxLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Same bed, but it feels just a little bit bigger now&lt;br&gt; Our song on the radio, but it don't sound the same&lt;br&gt; When our friends talk about you all that it does is just tear me down&lt;br&gt; Cause my heart breaks a little when I hear your name&lt;br&gt; And it all just sound like uh, uh, uh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hmmm too young, too dumb to realize&lt;br&gt; That I should have bought you flowers and held your hand&lt;br&gt; Should have gave you all my hours when I had the chance&lt;br&gt; Take you to every party cause all you wanted to do was dance&lt;br&gt; Now my baby is dancing, but she's dancing with another man.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My pride, my ego, my needs and my selfish ways&lt;br&gt; Caused a good strong woman like you to walk out my life&lt;br&gt; Now I never, never get to clean up the mess I made&lt;br&gt; And it haunts me every time I close my eyes&lt;br&gt; It all just sounds like uh, uh, uh, uh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Too young, too dumb to realize&lt;br&gt; That I should have bought you flowers and held your hand&lt;br&gt; Should have gave all my hours when I had the chance&lt;br&gt; Take you to every party cause all you wanted to do was dance&lt;br&gt; Now my baby is dancing, but she's dancing with another man.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Although it hurts I'll be the first to say that I was wrong&lt;br&gt; Oh, I know I'm probably much too late&lt;br&gt; To try and apologize for my mistakes&lt;br&gt; But I just want you to know&lt;br&gt; I hope he buys you flowers, I hope he holds your hand&lt;br&gt; Give you all his hours when he has the chance&lt;br&gt; Take you to every party cause I remember how much you loved to dance&lt;br&gt; Do all the things I should have done when I was your man!&lt;br&gt; Do all the things I should have done when I was your man!</Lyrics>
</Song>
