<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>I Got A Boy</Title>
    <Artist>SNSD</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/4/a/4a47f28a243f21d3b0914f77b41e071a_1396584957.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;I Got A Boy&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;SNSD&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjAxJTJGMDElMkY5JTJGMiUyRjkyYWM2NTc2NGRiOWM0ZDUxOTNlMmE1NDliYzhkZjY5Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I Got A Boy- SNSD &lt;br&gt; English Translation:&lt;br&gt; Ayo! GG! Yeah Yeah, shall we start?&lt;br&gt; Uh-muh! Look at her, look. What happened to her that she cut her hair? huh?&lt;br&gt; Uh-muh! Again look at her, look! From head to toe, her style has changed&lt;br&gt; Why did she do that? I’m curious to death, why did she do that? Tell me&lt;br&gt; Ha ha! Let me introduce myself! Here comes trouble! Follow after me!&lt;br&gt; Oh oh oh yeah oh, oh oh yeah oh, you really are something else!&lt;br&gt; Who is she? Ridiculous&lt;br&gt; Do you know you’re too self-assertive? She thinks I’m average&lt;br&gt; Yeah, I guess she really liked him!&lt;br&gt; No way! No way!&lt;br&gt; She became so pretty and sexy, it’s because of him, right?&lt;br&gt; I almost asked her what her new makeup was&lt;br&gt; Truthfully, I’ve seen it for the first time&lt;br&gt; The deep eyes, like a scarred beast&lt;br&gt; I was dizzy by just talking to him!&lt;br&gt; You really are something else! You really are something else!&lt;br&gt; Oh oh oh yeah oh, oh oh yeah oh, You really are something else!&lt;br&gt; Oh oh oh yeah oh, oh oh yeah oh, You really are something else!&lt;br&gt; Ayo! Stop! Let me put it down another way.&lt;br&gt; I got a boy, a handsome one! I got a boy, a kind one! I got a boy handsome boy, who took all my heart&lt;br&gt; I got a boy, a handsome one! I got a boy, a kind one! I got a boy awesome boy, I must have really fallen for him&lt;br&gt; Ah, my prince! When are you gonna come save me?&lt;br&gt; Will you lift me in your arms and fly, like a white dream?&lt;br&gt; I’m like, surprised, mental collapse! He wants to see my face without makeup. I really like him, would it be okay to show it to him?&lt;br&gt; Oh! Never! Right? Right?&lt;br&gt; Let’s keep what needs to be kept, right! right!&lt;br&gt; Don’t ever forget this until you take all of his heart!&lt;br&gt; Oh oh oh yeah oh, oh oh yeah oh, even if I stay up all night, it’s not enough, everything everything&lt;br&gt; Oh oh oh yeah oh, oh oh yeah oh, our biggest interest, everything everything&lt;br&gt; Listen to me, you all know him, right? He’s a bit young but he’s full inside&lt;br&gt; Sometimes he is as reliable as an oppa but when he acts charming, he is so cute&lt;br&gt; Oh oh oh yeah oh, oh oh yeah oh, you’re crazy, crazy&lt;br&gt; Oh oh oh yeah oh, oh oh yeah oh, you’re crazy, crazy&lt;br&gt; I’m really angry, my boy doesn’t look at me as a girl&lt;br&gt; What should I do when I feel hopeless? Should I make him feel jealous? I’m so upset! What do I do?&lt;br&gt; No way! No way!&lt;br&gt; Don’t stop! Let’s bring it back to 140&lt;br&gt; I got a boy, a handsome one! I got a boy, a kind one! I got a boy handsome boy, who took all my heart&lt;br&gt; I got a boy, a handsome one! I got a boy, a kind one! I got a boy awesome boy, I must have really fallen for him&lt;br&gt; Always next to me, it’s you, who’s on my side and listens to me, you- you-&lt;br&gt; I’m happy as it is right now, cause everything will work&lt;br&gt; I got a boy, a handsome one! I got a boy, a kind one! I got a boy handsome boy, who took all my heart&lt;br&gt; I got a boy, a handsome one! I got a boy, a kind one! I got a boy awesome boy, I must have really fallen for him&lt;br&gt; I got a boy, a handsome one!</Lyrics>
</Song>
