<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Cruise</Title>
    <Artist>Florida Georgia Line</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/c/6/c6b115c5a5969a7a12771db6026c71f8_1352088309.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Cruise&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Florida Georgia Line&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjEwJTJGMTklMkY5JTJGNCUyRjk0MDhjOWMzNmMxNTczNjc3N2JlOWQ5NmM2MDA5NWQ5Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Baby you a song&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hey Baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; When I first saw that bikini top on her,&lt;br&gt; She's poppin' right out of the south Georgia water.&lt;br&gt; Thought, &quot;Oh good Lord!&quot; she had them long tan legs&lt;br&gt; Couldn't help myself so I walked up and said:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Well baby you a song,&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise...&lt;br&gt; Down a back road blowin' stop signs through the middle,&lt;br&gt; Every little farm town,&lt;br&gt; With you.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &amp;amp; this brand new chevy with a lift kit,&lt;br&gt; Would look a helluva lot better with you up in it!&lt;br&gt; So Baby you a song,&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yea she was sippin' on Southern' and singin' Marshall Tucker,&lt;br&gt; We were falling in love in the sweet heart of summer.&lt;br&gt; She hopped right up,&lt;br&gt; Into the cab of my truck&lt;br&gt; And said, &quot;Fire it up! Let's go get this thing stuck!&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby you a song,&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise...&lt;br&gt; Down a back road blowin' stop signs through the middle,&lt;br&gt; Every little farm town,&lt;br&gt; With you.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &amp;amp; this brand new chevy with a lift kit,&lt;br&gt; Would look a helluva lot better with you up in it!&lt;br&gt; So Baby you a song,&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; When that summer sun fell to it's knees,&lt;br&gt; I looked at her and she looked at me,&lt;br&gt; And I turned on those KC lights and drove all night,&lt;br&gt; Cuz it felt so right,&lt;br&gt; Her and I man we felt so right.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I put it in park,&lt;br&gt; and grabbed my guitar,&lt;br&gt; and strummed a couple chords,&lt;br&gt; and sang from the heart.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Girl you sure got the beat in my chest bumpin'&lt;br&gt; Hell I can't get you out of my head!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby you a song,&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise...&lt;br&gt; Down a back road blowin' stop signs through the middle,&lt;br&gt; Every little farm town with you!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby you a song,&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise...&lt;br&gt; Down a back road blowin' stop signs through the middle,&lt;br&gt; Every little farm town with you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And in this brand new chevy with a lift kit,&lt;br&gt; Would Look a HELLUVA lot better with you up in it!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Come on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby you a song,&lt;br&gt; You make me wanna roll my windows down and cruise!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Come on girl!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Get those windows down and cruise!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ahhh yea</Lyrics>
</Song>
