<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Hero</Title>
    <Artist>Skillet</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/c/7/c74e539b4a03b48b400291b66fae1e50_1288498225.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Hero&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Skillet&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjAzJTJGMjElMkY2JTJGYSUyRjZhYTNlN2RiYzU4MzhjOWZjNmJmMzk3NjY1YjI0NGJjLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I'm just a step away,&lt;br&gt; I'm a just a breath away;&lt;br&gt; Losin my faith today,&lt;br&gt; Falling off the edge today!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I am just a man,&lt;br&gt; Not superhuman;&lt;br&gt; I'm not superhuman!&lt;br&gt; Someone save me from the hate&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's just another war,&lt;br&gt; Just another family torn;&lt;br&gt; I'm falling from my faith today!&lt;br&gt; Just a step from the edge,&lt;br&gt; Just another day in the world we live;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need a Hero,&lt;br&gt; To save me now!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; Save me now!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero,&lt;br&gt; To save my life!&lt;br&gt; A Hero'll save me!&lt;br&gt; Just in time!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I gotta fight today,&lt;br&gt; To live another day;&lt;br&gt; Speakin' my mind today,&lt;br&gt; My voice will be heard today!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I've gotta make a stand,&lt;br&gt; But I am just a man;&lt;br&gt; I'm not superhuman!&lt;br&gt; My voice will be heard today!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's just another war,&lt;br&gt; Just another family torn;&lt;br&gt; My voice will be heard today!&lt;br&gt; It's just another kill,&lt;br&gt; The countdown begins to destroy ourselves!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need a Hero,&lt;br&gt; To save me now!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; Save me now!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero,&lt;br&gt; To save my life!&lt;br&gt; A Hero'll save me!&lt;br&gt; Just in time!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need a Hero,&lt;br&gt; To save my life!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; Just in time!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Save me just in time...&lt;br&gt; Save me just in time...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Who's gonna fight for what's right,&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna help us survive,&lt;br&gt; We're in the fight of our lives!&lt;br&gt; And we're not ready to die!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Who's gonna fight for the weak,&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna make 'em believe,&lt;br&gt; I've got a Hero!&lt;br&gt; I've got a Hero!&lt;br&gt; Livin' in me!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm gonna fight for what's right,&lt;br&gt; Today I'm speaking my mind,&lt;br&gt; And if it kills me tonight,&lt;br&gt; I will be ready to die!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; A Hero's not afraid to give His life,&lt;br&gt; A Hero's gonna save me just in time!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need a Hero,&lt;br&gt; To save me now!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; Save me now!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero,&lt;br&gt; To save my life!&lt;br&gt; A Hero'll save me!&lt;br&gt; Just in time!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna fight for what's right,&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna help us survive!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna fight for the weak,&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna make 'em believe!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; I need a Hero!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; A Hero's gonna save me,&lt;br&gt; Just in time!</Lyrics>
</Song>
