<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Highway Don't Care</Title>
    <Artist>Tim McGraw</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/3/b35b030e58a0ab1b7258a2e8ef7754ca_1286356038.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Highway Don't Care&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Tim McGraw&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjAyJTJGMjMlMkY3JTJGMiUyRjcyNDNiZWI3MWFmMDc4MGJmN2I3MmJkOTI1MGFmMTI0Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Bet your window's rolled down and your hair's pulled back&lt;br&gt; And I bet you got no idea you're going way too fast&lt;br&gt; You're trying not to think about what went wrong&lt;br&gt; Trying not to stop 'til you get where you goin'&lt;br&gt; You're trying to stay awake so I bet you turn on the radio&lt;br&gt; And the song goes&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can't live without you, I can't live without you, baby&lt;br&gt; I can't live without you, I can't live without you, baby, baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The highway won't hold you tonight&lt;br&gt; The highway don't know you're alive&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care if you're all alone&lt;br&gt; But I do, I do.&lt;br&gt; The highway won't dry your tears&lt;br&gt; The highway don't need you here&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care if you're coming home&lt;br&gt; But I do, I do.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I bet you got a dead cell phone in your shotgun seat&lt;br&gt; Yeah, I bet you're bending God's ear talking 'bout me.&lt;br&gt; You're trying not to let the first tear fall out&lt;br&gt; Trying not to think about turning around&lt;br&gt; You're trying not to get lost in the sound but that song is always on&lt;br&gt; So you sing along&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can't live without you, I can't live without you, baby&lt;br&gt; I can't live without I can't live without you baby, oh baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The highway won't hold you tonight&lt;br&gt; The highway don't know you're alive&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care if you're all alone&lt;br&gt; But I do, I do.&lt;br&gt; The highway won't dry your tears&lt;br&gt; The highway don't need you here&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care if you're coming home&lt;br&gt; But I do, I do.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can't live without you, I can't live without you, baby&lt;br&gt; I can't live without I can't live without you, baby, oh baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The highway don't care&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care&lt;br&gt; But I do, I do.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can't live without you, I can't live without you, baby&lt;br&gt; I can't live without I can't live without you, baby, oh baby&lt;br&gt; (The highway don't care&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care&lt;br&gt; The highway don't care&lt;br&gt; But I do, I do) [x3]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can't live without you, I can't live without you, baby</Lyrics>
</Song>
