<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>If I Let You Go</Title>
    <Artist>Westlife</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/1/b/1b90dcb5c89d1ba88ae61be57129166a_1341548481.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;If I Let You Go&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Westlife&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMzElMkY5JTJGMiUyRjkyMjBlZjRjM2EzMThhOTYzYmQ0ZTE1Y2Y0MmFlYzAwLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Shane:]&lt;br&gt; Day after day&lt;br&gt; Time passed away &lt;br&gt; And I just can't get you off my mind &lt;br&gt; Nobody knows, I hide it inside &lt;br&gt; I keep on searching but I can't find &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Mark:]&lt;br&gt; The courage to show to letting you know&lt;br&gt; I've never felt so much love before&lt;br&gt; [All (Shane lead):]&lt;br&gt; And once again I'm thinking about &lt;br&gt; Taking the easy way out &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [All:]&lt;br&gt; But if I let you go I will never know &lt;br&gt; What my life would be holding you close to me &lt;br&gt; Will I ever see you smiling back at me? ([Shane:] oh yeah) &lt;br&gt; How will I know &lt;br&gt; [Shane:] if I let you go? &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bryan:]&lt;br&gt; Night after night I hear myself say &lt;br&gt; Why can't this feeling just fade away &lt;br&gt; There's no one like you (no one like you) &lt;br&gt; You speak to my heart (speak to my heart) &lt;br&gt; It's such a shame we're worlds apart &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Shane:]&lt;br&gt; I'm too shy to ask, I'm too proud to lose &lt;br&gt; But sooner or later I gotta choose &lt;br&gt; And once again I'm thinking about &lt;br&gt; Taking the easy way out &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [All:]&lt;br&gt; But if I let you go I will never know &lt;br&gt; What my life would be, holding you close to me &lt;br&gt; Will I ever see you smiling back at me? (oh yeah) &lt;br&gt; How will I know&lt;br&gt; [Shane:] if I let you go ? &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Shane:]&lt;br&gt; If I let you go ooooh baby &lt;br&gt; Ooooooooohhhhh &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bryan:]&lt;br&gt; Once again I'm thinking about &lt;br&gt; Taking the easy way out &lt;br&gt; Ooooooooohhhhh &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [All:]&lt;br&gt; But if I let you go I will never know &lt;br&gt; What my life would be, holding you close to me&lt;br&gt; ([Mark:] close to me)&lt;br&gt; Will I ever see you smiling back at me?&lt;br&gt; ([Shane:] oh yeah) &lt;br&gt; How will I know&lt;br&gt; ([Bryan:] if I let you go?) &lt;br&gt; But if I let you go I will never know &lt;br&gt; ([Mark:] oh baby) &lt;br&gt; Will I ever see you smiling back at me?&lt;br&gt; ([Shane:] oh yeah) &lt;br&gt; How will I know&lt;br&gt; [Shane:] if I let you go ? &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
