<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>OMG</Title>
    <Artist>Usher ft. will.i.am</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/e/a/ea7cdf84cee1b07e64f919ae05d5e774_1349886331.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;OMG&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Usher,will.i.am&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDklMkYyJTJGNiUyRjI2ZmExNmI3MGIxMThhYzYyNmU0YjM0NWUyMWI0N2QyLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>(feat. Will.I.Am)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Will.I.Am:]&lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh&lt;br&gt; Baby let me......&lt;br&gt; I did it again, so I'm gone let the beat drop&lt;br&gt; Oh my&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; Baby let me love you down&lt;br&gt; There's so many ways to love ya&lt;br&gt; Baby I can break you down&lt;br&gt; There's so many ways to love ya&lt;br&gt; Got me like, ooh myy gosh I'm soo in love&lt;br&gt; I found you finally, it make me want to say&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh , oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,&lt;br&gt; Ohh my gosh&lt;br&gt; ..&lt;br&gt; You make me want to say&lt;br&gt; ..&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1:]&lt;br&gt; I fell in love with shawty when I seen her on the dance floor&lt;br&gt; She was dancing sexy, pop, pop, popping, dropping, dropping low&lt;br&gt; Never ever has a lady hit me on the first sight&lt;br&gt; This was something special; this was just like dynamite&lt;br&gt; Honey got a booty like pow, pow, pow&lt;br&gt; Honey got some boobies like wow, oh wow&lt;br&gt; Girl you know I'm loving your, loving your style&lt;br&gt; Check, check, check, check, check, checking you out like,&lt;br&gt; Ooh (oooh) she got it allll&lt;br&gt; Sexy from her head to toes&lt;br&gt; &amp;amp; I want it all, it all, it all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; Baby let me love you down&lt;br&gt; There's so many ways to love ya&lt;br&gt; Baby I can break you down&lt;br&gt; There's so many ways to love ya&lt;br&gt; Got me like, ooh myy gosh I'm soo in love&lt;br&gt; I found you finally, it make me want to say&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh , oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,&lt;br&gt; Ohh my gosh&lt;br&gt; ..&lt;br&gt; You make me want to say [repeat 2x]&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Will.I.Am:]&lt;br&gt; Feel so hard for honey out of all the girls up in this club&lt;br&gt; This one got me whipped, just off one look, yep I fell in love&lt;br&gt; This one something special, this one just like dynamite&lt;br&gt; You're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're, you're out of sight&lt;br&gt; Fell in love with honey like my, oh my&lt;br&gt; Honey looking wonderful; fly, so fly&lt;br&gt; Honey like a supermodel; my, oh my&lt;br&gt; Baby how you do that, make a grown man cry?&lt;br&gt; Ooh (oooh) baby, you got it alll&lt;br&gt; Sexy from her head to the toes&lt;br&gt; &amp;amp; I want it all, it all, it all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; So, honey let me love you down&lt;br&gt; There's so many ways to love ya&lt;br&gt; Baby I can break it down&lt;br&gt; There's so many ways to love ya&lt;br&gt; Got me like, ooh myy gosh I'm soo in love I found you finallyy,&lt;br&gt; You make me want to say..&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh , oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,&lt;br&gt; Oh My Gosh!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh my gosh&lt;br&gt; Oh my&lt;br&gt; Oh my&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh my gosh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Will.I.Am:]&lt;br&gt; Oh myy gosh&lt;br&gt; I did it again&lt;br&gt; So I'm gone let the beat drop&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Usher:]&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh, oh myy&lt;br&gt; Oh, oh, oh my, my, my, my, my, my&lt;br&gt; Ooh my gosh [x3]&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
