<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>One Less Lonely Girl</Title>
    <Artist>Justin Bieber</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/8/b8903886038c34761df8dc86d3d951ba_1366022708.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;One Less Lonely Girl&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Justin Bieber&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDIlMkY4JTJGMyUyRjgzMTYzZjgxNmFhYWJkY2I5OWQ1MzJiYWE5ZjExMmEwLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;One Less Lonely Girl&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Alright let's go&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; How many &quot;I told you&quot;s and &quot;Start over&quot;s and shoulders have you cried on before?&lt;br&gt; How many promises? Be honest girl&lt;br&gt; How many tears you let hit the floor?&lt;br&gt; How many bags you packed&lt;br&gt; Just to take them back?&lt;br&gt; Tell me that how many either &quot;or&quot;s?&lt;br&gt; But no more if you let me inside of your world&lt;br&gt; There'll be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (Oh oh) Saw so many pretty faces before I saw you (you)&lt;br&gt; Now all I see is you&lt;br&gt; I'm coming for you (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (No no) Don't need these other pretty faces like I need you&lt;br&gt; And when you're mine, in the world&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm coming for you, one less lonely girl [x3]&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna put you first&lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'll show you what you're worth&lt;br&gt; That's what I'm gonna do&lt;br&gt; If you let me inside of your world&lt;br&gt; There'll be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Christmas wasn't merry, 14th of February not one of them spent with you&lt;br&gt; How many dinner dates, set dinner plates&lt;br&gt; And he didn't even touch his food&lt;br&gt; How many torn photographs are you taping back?&lt;br&gt; Tell me that you couldn't see an open door&lt;br&gt; But no more, if you let me inside or your world&lt;br&gt; There'll be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (Oh oh) Saw so many pretty faces before I saw you, (you)&lt;br&gt; Now all I see is you&lt;br&gt; I'm coming for you (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (No no) Don't need these other pretty faces like I need you&lt;br&gt; And when you're mine in this world&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm coming for you, one less lonely girl [x3]&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna put you first&lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'll show you what you're worth&lt;br&gt; That's what I'm gonna do&lt;br&gt; If you let me inside of your world&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can fix up your broken heart (heart)&lt;br&gt; I can give you a brand new start (start)&lt;br&gt; I can make you believe (ya)&lt;br&gt; I just wanna set one girl free to fall (free to fall)&lt;br&gt; She's free to fall (fall in love)&lt;br&gt; With me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Her heart's locked and know what i got the key&lt;br&gt; I'll take her and leave the world with one less lonely&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; One less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm coming for you, one less lonely girl [x3]&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna put you first&lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'll show you what you're worth&lt;br&gt; That's what I'm gonna do&lt;br&gt; If you let me inside of your world&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm coming for you, one less lonely girl (yeah yea) [x2]&lt;br&gt; I'm coming for you, one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna put you first&lt;br&gt; (I'm coming for you)&lt;br&gt; I'll show you what you're worth&lt;br&gt; That's what I'm gonna do&lt;br&gt; If you let me inside of your world&lt;br&gt; There's gonna be one less lonely girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Only you shawty (haha)</Lyrics>
</Song>
