<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Unbreak My Heart</Title>
    <Artist>Toni Braxton</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/0/0/009ebb7306d8ae1887b09626bc9401a9_1328287218.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Unbreak My Heart&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Toni Braxton&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMTYlMkY0JTJGZSUyRjRlODE4MTAyYzYxZTg3YWE2MWE4YTZiMGNmYmU2MTIzLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Don't leave me in all this pain. Don't leave me out in the rain. Come back and bring back my smile. Come and take these tears away. I need your arms to hold me now. The night are so unkind. Bring back those night. When I held you beside me. Unbreak my heart.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Say you'll love me again.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Undo this hurt you caused. When you walked out the door. And walked out my life. Uncry these tears. I cried so many nights. Unbreak my heart, my heart.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Take back that sad word good bye. Bring back the joy to my life. Don't leave me here with these tears. Come and kiss this pain away. I can't forget the days you left. Time is so unkind. And life is so cruel without you here beside me. Unbreak my heart. Say you love'll me again. Undo this hurt you caused. When you walked out the door. And walked out my life. Uncry these tears. I cried so many night. Unbreak my heart.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't leave me in all this pain. Don't leave me out in the rain. Bring back the nights. When I held you beside me. Unbreak my heart. Say you 'll love me again. Undo this hurt you caused. When you walked out the door. And walk out my life. Uncry these tears. I cried so many nights. Unbreak my heart. How baby come back and say you love me. Unbreak my heart. Sweet darling. Without you, I just can't go on .&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Say to love…….&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Can't go on.</Lyrics>
</Song>
