<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Still Loving You</Title>
    <Artist>Scorpions</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/1/b/1b35031311e6c55f404df4e31274ec40_1346821421.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Still Loving You&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Scorpions&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMTYlMkYwJTJGYiUyRjBiODU3ZTVhZjE2ZmM4ODIxM2NjOTNhMThmMDk4N2RlLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Time, it needs time&lt;br&gt; To win back your love again.&lt;br&gt; I will be there, I will be there.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Love, only love&lt;br&gt; Can bring back your love someday.&lt;br&gt; I will be there, I will be there.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Fight, babe, I'll fight&lt;br&gt; To win back your love again.&lt;br&gt; I will be there, I will be there.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Love, only love&lt;br&gt; Can break down the walls someday.&lt;br&gt; I will be there, I will be there.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If we'd go again&lt;br&gt; All the way from the start,&lt;br&gt; I would try to change&lt;br&gt; The things that killed our love.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Your pride has build a wall, so strong&lt;br&gt; That I can't get through.&lt;br&gt; Is there really no chance&lt;br&gt; To start once again?&lt;br&gt; I'm loving you.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Try, baby try&lt;br&gt; To trust in my love again.&lt;br&gt; I will be there, I will be there.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Love, your love&lt;br&gt; Just shouldn't be thrown away.&lt;br&gt; I will be there, I will be there.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If we'd go again&lt;br&gt; All the way from the start,&lt;br&gt; I would try to change&lt;br&gt; The things that killed our love.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Your pride has build a wall, so strong&lt;br&gt; That I can't get through.&lt;br&gt; Is there really no chance&lt;br&gt; To start once again?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If we'd go again&lt;br&gt; All the way from the start,&lt;br&gt; I would try to change&lt;br&gt; The things that killed our love.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yes I've hurt your pride, and I know&lt;br&gt; What you've been through.&lt;br&gt; You should give me a chance&lt;br&gt; This can't be the end.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm still loving you.&lt;br&gt; I'm still loving you,&lt;br&gt; I need your love.&lt;br&gt; I'm still loving you.&lt;br&gt; Still loving you, baby...</Lyrics>
</Song>
