<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>What Goes Around.../...Comes Around</Title>
    <Artist>Justin Timberlake</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/8/6/86ee8117664b8d96ae27f7465704f731_1393307832.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;What Goes Around...\/...Comes Around&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Justin Timberlake&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDIlMkY2JTJGNSUyRjY1NGFlZmJmNzNkMDY3OWFiNWU0Y2ZkYmMyMDhiMTk0Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Hey Girl&lt;br&gt; Is he everything you wanted in a man?&lt;br&gt; You know I gave you the world&lt;br&gt; You had me in the palm of your hand&lt;br&gt; Why your love went away&lt;br&gt; I just can't seem to understand&lt;br&gt; Thought it was me and you baby&lt;br&gt; Me and you until the end&lt;br&gt; But I guess I was wrong&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't wanna think about it&lt;br&gt; Don't wanna talk about it&lt;br&gt; I'm just so sick about it&lt;br&gt; Can't believe it's ending this way&lt;br&gt; Just so confused about it&lt;br&gt; Feeling the blues about it&lt;br&gt; I can't do without ya&lt;br&gt; Tell me is this fair&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Is this the way it's really going down?&lt;br&gt; Is this how we say goodbye?&lt;br&gt; Should've known better when you came around&lt;br&gt; That you were gonna make me cry&lt;br&gt; It's breaking my heart to watch you run around&lt;br&gt; Knowing that you're living a lie&lt;br&gt; That's OK cause in time you will find...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What goes around, goes around, goes around, comes all the way back around&lt;br&gt; What goes around, goes around, goes around, comes all the way back around&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Now Girl&lt;br&gt; I remember everything that you claimed&lt;br&gt; You said that you were moving on now&lt;br&gt; Maybe I should do the same&lt;br&gt; The funny thing about that is&lt;br&gt; I was ready to give you my name&lt;br&gt; Thought it was me and you baby&lt;br&gt; And now, it's all just a shame&lt;br&gt; That I guess I was wrong&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't wanna think about it&lt;br&gt; Don't wanna talk about it&lt;br&gt; I'm just so sick about it&lt;br&gt; Can't believe it's ending this way&lt;br&gt; Just confused about it&lt;br&gt; Feeling the blues about it(yeah)&lt;br&gt; I can't do without ya&lt;br&gt; Tell me is this fair&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Is this the way it's really going down?&lt;br&gt; Is this how we say goodbye?&lt;br&gt; Should've known better when you came around&lt;br&gt; That you were gonna make me cry&lt;br&gt; It's breaking my heart to watch you run around&lt;br&gt; Knowing that you're living a lie&lt;br&gt; But that's OK cause in time you will find&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What goes around, goes around, goes around, comes all the way back around&lt;br&gt; What goes around, goes around, goes around, comes all the way back around&lt;br&gt; What goes around, goes around, goes around, comes all the way back around&lt;br&gt; What goes around, goes around, goes around, comes all the way back around&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What goes around comes around&lt;br&gt; What goes around comes around</Lyrics>
</Song>
