<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Hello</Title>
    <Artist>Lionel Richie</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/4/7/47cb8c933fc0d04ff43bc4aef77f03a3_1336242883.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Hello&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Lionel Richie&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMTMlMkY5JTJGMSUyRjkxYzFmYzk5N2Y3MGRjMDA1ZDIwZTUzZmM4YzljZjIyLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>HELLO&lt;br&gt; I've been alone with you inside my mind &lt;br&gt; And in my dreams I've kissed your lips a thousand times &lt;br&gt; I sometimes see you pass outside my door &lt;br&gt; Hello, is it me you're looking for? &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can see it in your eyes &lt;br&gt; I can see it in your smile &lt;br&gt; You're all I've ever wanted, (and) my arms are open wide &lt;br&gt; 'Cause you know just what to say &lt;br&gt; And you know just what to do &lt;br&gt; And I want to tell you so much, I love you ... &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I long to see the sunlight in your hair &lt;br&gt; And tell you time and time again how much I care &lt;br&gt; Sometimes I feel my heart will overflow &lt;br&gt; Hello, I've just got to let you know &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'Cause I wonder where you are &lt;br&gt; And I wonder what you do &lt;br&gt; Are you somewhere feeling lonely, or is someone loving you? &lt;br&gt; Tell me how to win your heart &lt;br&gt; For I haven't got a clue &lt;br&gt; But let me start by saying, I love you ... &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hello, is it me you're looking for? &lt;br&gt; 'Cause I wonder where you are &lt;br&gt; And I wonder what you do &lt;br&gt; Are you somewhere feeling lonely or is someone loving you? &lt;br&gt; Tell me how to win your heart &lt;br&gt; For I haven't got a clue &lt;br&gt; But let me start by saying ... I love you</Lyrics>
</Song>
