<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Nobody</Title>
    <Artist>Wonder Girls</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/a/ba55d9df8bc55f7c6dd1221d96e0d444_1343982945.png</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Nobody&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Wonder Girls&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDklMkY5JTJGMCUyRjkwNjE3YzNjMTliOTIxZTY2ZTY0ZTIyNWYxMDlkZjVkLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Spoken]&lt;br&gt; You know I still love you baby&lt;br&gt; And that will never change&lt;br&gt; Not a single thing about you&lt;br&gt; Every day in my life&lt;br&gt; Oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; I want nobody, nobody but you&lt;br&gt; I want nobody, nobody but you&lt;br&gt; I don’t want nobody else&lt;br&gt; Love you more than my own self&lt;br&gt; I want nobody nobody, nobody nobody.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1]&lt;br&gt; How come you try to push me away?&lt;br&gt; Why don't you want to stay,&lt;br&gt; Take some time for what I'd say?&lt;br&gt; How come you think that it's me you don't deserve?&lt;br&gt; There's no one I'd prefer&lt;br&gt; You are so much better.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge]&lt;br&gt; Remember all those kisses through the night&lt;br&gt; Remember all the times we had a fight&lt;br&gt; We've been through together&lt;br&gt; Let's do this forever&lt;br&gt; Don't tell me who I am supposed to love.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Repeat Chorus&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2]&lt;br&gt; Satisfaction is all guaranteed&lt;br&gt; No money in the world&lt;br&gt; Can compare to you girl&lt;br&gt; So why would you feel you're not good enough?&lt;br&gt; It's you I think of&lt;br&gt; Just you I am in love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Repeat Bridge&lt;br&gt; Repeat Chorus&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; I don’t want nobody, body&lt;br&gt; I don’t want nobody, body&lt;br&gt; Baby it's you&lt;br&gt; Nobody but you&lt;br&gt; Why don't you feel it too, the way I do?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Rap]&lt;br&gt; Back in the day when we were so young and wild and free&lt;br&gt; We were always in the treehouse, just you and me&lt;br&gt; Talkin' bout our dreams, and how our future would be&lt;br&gt; Laughing on the way, life is just a cup of tea&lt;br&gt; So why'd you tryna leave and push me away, way?&lt;br&gt; It is not just a game to play, play&lt;br&gt; You might see you're nothing special but hey, hey&lt;br&gt; We can be more than friends and it'll make my day, day</Lyrics>
</Song>
