<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Just Dance</Title>
    <Artist>Lady Gaga ft. Colby O'Donis</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/4/d/4d1ba90ca9b0cc67f174808499827790_1395722641.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Just Dance&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Lady Gaga,Colby O'Donis&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDIlMkZmJTJGNCUyRmY0ZDRhYTM5MjFiNDMyYjJmYzA0MWEwYzU4MDg4MTI1Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Just Dance&quot;&lt;br&gt; (feat. Colby O'Donis)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Red One&lt;br&gt; Konvict&lt;br&gt; Gaga&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I've had a little bit too much&lt;br&gt; All of the people start to rush.&lt;br&gt; Start to rush babe.&lt;br&gt; A dizzy twister dance&lt;br&gt; Can't find my drink or man.&lt;br&gt; Where are my keys, I lost my phone.&lt;br&gt; What's going on on the floor?&lt;br&gt; I love this record baby, but I can't see straight anymore.&lt;br&gt; Keep it cool what's the name of this club?&lt;br&gt; I can't remember but it's alright, alright.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; Just dance. Gonna be okay.&lt;br&gt; Da-doo-doo-doo&lt;br&gt; Just dance. Spin that record babe.&lt;br&gt; Da-doo-doo-doo&lt;br&gt; Just dance. Gonna be okay.&lt;br&gt; Duh-duh-duh-duh&lt;br&gt; Dance. Dance. Dance. Just dance.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wish I could shut my playboy mouth.&lt;br&gt; How'd I turn my shirt inside out? Inside out babe.&lt;br&gt; Control your poison babe&lt;br&gt; Roses with thorns they say.&lt;br&gt; And we're all gettin' hosed tonight.&lt;br&gt; What's going on on the floor?&lt;br&gt; I love this record baby, but I can't see straight anymore.&lt;br&gt; Keep it cool what's the name of this club?&lt;br&gt; I can't remember but it's alright, alright.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Colby O'Donis]&lt;br&gt; When I come through on the dance floor checking out that catalogue.&lt;br&gt; Can't believe my eyes so many women without a flaw.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And I ain't gonna' give it up, steady tryna pick it up like a call&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna hit it, I'm gonna hit it and flex and do it until tomorrow, yeah&lt;br&gt; Shorty i can see that you got so much energy&lt;br&gt; The way you twirling up them hips round and round&lt;br&gt; There's no reason at all why you can't leave here with me&lt;br&gt; In the meantime stay, let me watch you break it down.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Half psychotic, sick hypnotic got my blueprint it's symphonic.&lt;br&gt; Half psychotic, sick hypnotic got my blueprint electronic.&lt;br&gt; Half psychotic, sick hypnotic got my blueprint it's symphonic.&lt;br&gt; Half psychotic, sick hypnotic got my blueprint electronic.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Go. Use your muscle, carve it out, work it, hustle&lt;br&gt; I got it, just stay close enough to get it&lt;br&gt; Don't slow! Drive it, clean it lysol, bleed it&lt;br&gt; Spend the last dough&lt;br&gt; (I got it)&lt;br&gt; In your Pocko&lt;br&gt; (I got it)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus] &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
