<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Telephone</Title>
    <Artist>Lady Gaga ft. Beyoncé</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/4/d/4d1ba90ca9b0cc67f174808499827790_1395722641.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Telephone&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Lady Gaga , Beyonc\u00e9&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDElMkY2JTJGMCUyRjYwMThmNWM5MzZjOWU3ZWEzODU4M2Y5YzE4ODVmNjA4Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Telephone&quot;&lt;br&gt; (feat. Beyonce)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Lady Gaga]&lt;br&gt; Hello hello baby you called&lt;br&gt; I can't hear a thing&lt;br&gt; I have got no service&lt;br&gt; In the club, you say? say?&lt;br&gt; Wha-wha-what did you say huh?&lt;br&gt; You're breakin' up on me&lt;br&gt; Sorry I cannot hear you&lt;br&gt; I'm kinda busy&lt;br&gt; K-kinda busy&lt;br&gt; K-kinda busy&lt;br&gt; Sorry I cannot hear you I'm kinda busy&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Just a second&lt;br&gt; It's my favorite song they're gonna play&lt;br&gt; And I cannot text you with a drink in my hand, eh?&lt;br&gt; You shoulda made some plans with me&lt;br&gt; You knew that I was free&lt;br&gt; And now you won't stop calling me&lt;br&gt; I'm kinda busy&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; Stop callin'&lt;br&gt; Stop callin'&lt;br&gt; I don't wanna think anymore&lt;br&gt; I left my head and my heart on the dancefloor&lt;br&gt; Stop callin'&lt;br&gt; Stop callin'&lt;br&gt; I don't wanna talk anymore&lt;br&gt; I left my head and my heart on the dancefloor&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; E-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e&lt;br&gt; Stop telephonin'&lt;br&gt; Me-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e&lt;br&gt; I'm busy e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e&lt;br&gt; Stop telephonin'&lt;br&gt; Me-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e&lt;br&gt; Can call all you want but there's no one home&lt;br&gt; And you're not gonna reach my telephone&lt;br&gt; Out in the club&lt;br&gt; And I'm sippin that bubb&lt;br&gt; And you're not gonna reach my telephone&lt;br&gt; Call all you want, but there's no one home&lt;br&gt; And you're not gonna reach my telephone&lt;br&gt; Out in the club&lt;br&gt; And I'm sippin that bubb&lt;br&gt; And you're not gonna reach my telephone&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Beyonce]&lt;br&gt; Boy the way you blowing up my phone&lt;br&gt; Won't make me leave no faster&lt;br&gt; Put my coat on faster&lt;br&gt; Leave my girls no faster&lt;br&gt; I shoulda left my phone at home&lt;br&gt; 'Cuz this is a disaster&lt;br&gt; Calling like a collector&lt;br&gt; Sorry, I cannot answer&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Lady Gaga]&lt;br&gt; Not that I don't like you&lt;br&gt; I'm just at a party&lt;br&gt; And I am sick and tired of my phone r-ringing&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Beyonce]&lt;br&gt; Sometimes I feel like I live in grand central station&lt;br&gt; Tonight I'm not takin' no calls&lt;br&gt; 'Cuz I'll be dancin'&lt;br&gt; I'll be dancin'&lt;br&gt; I'll be dancin'&lt;br&gt; Tonight I'm not takin' no calls&lt;br&gt; Cuz I'll be dancin'&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Pre-Chorus x2]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [x3]&lt;br&gt; My telephone&lt;br&gt; Ma ma ma telephone&lt;br&gt; 'Cuz I'm out in the club&lt;br&gt; And I'm sippin that bubb&lt;br&gt; And you're not gonna reach my telephone&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (We're sorry, we're sorry&lt;br&gt; The number you have reached&lt;br&gt; Is not in service at this time&lt;br&gt; Please check the number, or try your call again)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
