<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Happy</Title>
    <Artist>Leona Lewis</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/7/7/7750c1dcfca03ff49dbf560f4a976c12_1386220115.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Happy&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Leona Lewis&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDQlMkZlJTJGYiUyRmViM2I1NzkzZjEyYWM5MTE5NjdiZjA4YmUyODQ5ZjRlLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Verse 1:]&lt;br&gt; Someone once told me that you have to choose&lt;br&gt; What you win or lose&lt;br&gt; You can't have everything&lt;br&gt; Don't you take chances&lt;br&gt; Might feel the pain&lt;br&gt; Don't you love in vain&lt;br&gt; Cause love won't set you free&lt;br&gt; I can't stand by the side&lt;br&gt; And watch this life pass me by&lt;br&gt; So unhappy&lt;br&gt; But safe as could be&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; So what if it hurts me?&lt;br&gt; So what if I break down?&lt;br&gt; So what if this world just throws me off the edge&lt;br&gt; My feet run out of ground&lt;br&gt; I gotta find my place&lt;br&gt; I wanna hear my sound&lt;br&gt; Don't care about all the pain in front of me&lt;br&gt; Cause i'm just trying to be happy, yeah&lt;br&gt; Just wanna be happy, yeah&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2:]&lt;br&gt; Holding on tightly&lt;br&gt; Just can't let it go&lt;br&gt; Just trying to play my role&lt;br&gt; Slowly disappear, ohh&lt;br&gt; But all these days, they feel like they're the same&lt;br&gt; Just different faces, different names&lt;br&gt; Get me out of here&lt;br&gt; I can't stand by your side, ohh no&lt;br&gt; And watch this life pass me by, pass me by&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; So what if it hurts me?&lt;br&gt; So what if I break down?&lt;br&gt; So what if this world just throws me off the edge&lt;br&gt; My feet run out of ground&lt;br&gt; I gotta find my place&lt;br&gt; I wanna hear my sound&lt;br&gt; Don't care about all the pain in front of me&lt;br&gt; Cause i'm just trying to be happy, ohh, happy, ohh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge:]&lt;br&gt; So any turns that I can't see,&lt;br&gt; like I'm a stranger on this road&lt;br&gt; But don't say victim&lt;br&gt; Don't say anything&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; So what if it hurts me?&lt;br&gt; So what if I break down?&lt;br&gt; So what if this world just throws me off the edge&lt;br&gt; My feet run out of ground&lt;br&gt; I gotta find my place&lt;br&gt; I wanna hear my sound&lt;br&gt; Don't care about all the pain in front of me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro:]&lt;br&gt; I just wanna be happy&lt;br&gt; Ohh, yeah, happy, ohh, happy&lt;br&gt; I just wanna be, ohh&lt;br&gt; I just wanna be happy&lt;br&gt; Ohh, happy&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
