<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Yeah!</Title>
    <Artist>Usher ft. Lil Jon ft. Ludacris</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/e/a/ea7cdf84cee1b07e64f919ae05d5e774_1349886331.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Yeah!&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Usher,Lil Jon,Ludacris&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDglMkYxJTJGMCUyRjEwMjJkNDc0ZjU1ZGNjNGU0YWIyMmRmMzYxYTFkMWVlLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Usher:] &lt;br&gt; Peace up! A Town Down! &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Lil' Jon:] &lt;br&gt; Yeah, (Yeah!) OK!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (Usher! Usher! Usher! Usher!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Lil' Jon:] &lt;br&gt; Lil' Jon!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Usher:]&lt;br&gt; Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! Yeah, Yeah! Yeaah!&lt;br&gt; Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! Yeah, Yeah! Yeaah!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Usher (Verse 1):]&lt;br&gt; Up in the club with my homies, tryna get a lil' V-I, but keep it down on the low key, 'cause you know how it is.&lt;br&gt; I saw shorty she was checkin' up on me, from the game she was spittin' in my ear you would think that she knew me.&lt;br&gt; So we decided to chill &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Conversation got heavy, she had me feelin' like she's ready to blow!&lt;br&gt; (Watch Out! Oh! Watch Out!)&lt;br&gt; She's saying &quot;Come get me! Come get me&quot;,&lt;br&gt; So I got up and followed her to the floor, she said &quot;Baby, let's go&quot;,&lt;br&gt; That's when I told her I said &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Usher (Chorus):]&lt;br&gt; Yeah (yeah) Shorty got down low and said come and get me &lt;br&gt; Yeah (yeah) I got so caught up I forgot she told me &lt;br&gt; Yeah (yeah) Her and my girl used to be the best of homies&lt;br&gt; Yeah (yeah) Next thing I knew she was all up on me screaming: &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! Yeah, Yeah! Yeaah!&lt;br&gt; Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! Yeah, Yeah! Yeaah!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Usher (Verse 2):]&lt;br&gt; So she's all up in my head now, got me thinking that it might good idea to take her with me,&lt;br&gt; 'Cause she's ready to leave (ready to leave)&lt;br&gt; But I gotta keep it real now, 'cause on a one to ten she's a certified twenty, but that just ain't me. Hey.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Because I don't know if I take that chance just where it's gonna lead,&lt;br&gt; But what I do know is the way she dance makes shorty alright with me.&lt;br&gt; The way she (get low!)&lt;br&gt; I'm like yeah, just work that out for me.&lt;br&gt; She asked for one more dance and I'm&lt;br&gt; Like yeah, how the hell am I supposed to leave?&lt;br&gt; And I said &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Lil' Jon:]&lt;br&gt; Hey, Luda! &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Ludacris (Verse 3):]&lt;br&gt; Watch out!&lt;br&gt; My outfit's ridiculous, in the club lookin' so conspicuous.&lt;br&gt; And Rowl! These women all on the prowl, if you hold the head steady I'm a milk the cow.&lt;br&gt; Forget about the game, I'm a spit the truth, I won't stop till I get 'em in they birthday suits. &lt;br&gt; So gimmie the rhythm and it'll be off with their clothes, then bend over to the front and touch your toes.&lt;br&gt; I left the Jag and I took the Rolls, if they aint cutting then I put em on foot patrol.&lt;br&gt; How you like me now, when my pinky's valued over three hundred thousand,&lt;br&gt; Lets drank you the one to please, Ludacris fill cups like double D's.&lt;br&gt; Me and Ursh once more and we leave 'em dead, we want a lady in the street but a freak in the bed to say &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Ludacris (Bridge):]&lt;br&gt; Take that and rewind it back, Lil' Jon got the beat to make ya booty go (clap) &lt;br&gt; Take that and rewind it back, Ursher got the voice to make ya booty go (clap) &lt;br&gt; Take that and rewind it back, Ludacris got the flow to make ya booty go (clap) &lt;br&gt; Take that and rewind it back, Lil' Jon got the beat to make ya booty go (clap)</Lyrics>
</Song>
