<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Hotel California</Title>
    <Artist>Eagles</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/f/aff3e7b6c439ac9535d8d79a5c2828cc_1336059287.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Hotel California&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Eagles&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjEwJTJGMjQlMkZjJTJGMSUyRmMxNWEzZmY0Njg5NDM3NDBiNGE1NzYxOTY3YjNjNTcxLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>On a dark desert highway, cool wind in my hair&lt;br&gt; Warm smell of colitas, rising up through the air &lt;br&gt; Up ahead in the distance, I saw a shimmering light &lt;br&gt; My head grew heavy and my sight grew dim &lt;br&gt; I had to stop for the night. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There she stood in the doorway; &lt;br&gt; I heard the mission bell &lt;br&gt; And I was thinking to myself &lt;br&gt; 'This could be heaven or this could be Hell' &lt;br&gt; Then she lit up a candle and she showed me the way &lt;br&gt; There were voices down the corridor, &lt;br&gt; I thought I heard them say &lt;br&gt; Welcome to the Hotel California &lt;br&gt; Such a lovely place (such a lovely place) &lt;br&gt; Such a lovely face. &lt;br&gt; Plenty of room at the Hotel California &lt;br&gt; Any time of year (any time of year) you can find it here &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Her mind is Tiffany-twisted, she got the Mercedes benz &lt;br&gt; She got a lot of pretty, pretty boys, that she calls friends &lt;br&gt; How they dance in the courtyard, sweet summer sweat &lt;br&gt; Some dance to remember, some dance to forget &lt;br&gt; So I called up the Captain, &lt;br&gt; 'Please bring me my wine' &lt;br&gt; He said, 'we haven't had that spirit here since nineteen sixty-nine' &lt;br&gt; And still those voices are calling from far away, &lt;br&gt; Wake you up in the middle of the night &lt;br&gt; Just to hear them say&quot; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Welcome to the Hotel California &lt;br&gt; Such a lovely place (such a lovely place) &lt;br&gt; Such a lovely face. &lt;br&gt; They livin' it up at the Hotel California &lt;br&gt; What a nice surprise (what a nice surprise), bring your alibis &lt;br&gt; Mirrors on the ceiling, &lt;br&gt; The pink champagne on ice &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And she said, 'we are all just prisoners here, of our own device' &lt;br&gt; And in the master's chambers, &lt;br&gt; They gathered for the feast &lt;br&gt; They stab it with their steely knives, &lt;br&gt; But they just can't kill the beast &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Last thing I remember, I was &lt;br&gt; Running for the door &lt;br&gt; I had to find the passage back to the place I was before &lt;br&gt; 'Relax' said the night man, &lt;br&gt; 'We are programmed to receive. &lt;br&gt; You can check out any time you like, &lt;br&gt; But you can never leave</Lyrics>
</Song>
