<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>You'll Be In My Heart</Title>
    <Artist>Phil Collins</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/7/4/74bb3d3e973662b682a9e6e52034b385_1286767914.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;You'll Be In My Heart&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Phil Collins&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA1JTJGMDYlMkYxJTJGOCUyRjE4MWZhNTM5YTViYTY3ZTgyYThjYmM5OWFiNDU1MDBhLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Come stop your crying&lt;br&gt; It will be all right&lt;br&gt; Just take my hand&lt;br&gt; Hold it tight&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I will protect you&lt;br&gt; From all around you&lt;br&gt; I will be here &lt;br&gt; Don't you cry&lt;br&gt; For one so small&lt;br&gt; You seem so strong&lt;br&gt; My arms will hold you&lt;br&gt; Keep you safe and warm&lt;br&gt; This bond between us&lt;br&gt; Can't be broken&lt;br&gt; I will be here&lt;br&gt; Don't you cry&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; 'Cause you'll be in my heart&lt;br&gt; Yes, you'll be in my heart&lt;br&gt; From this day on&lt;br&gt; Now and forever more&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You'll be in my heart&lt;br&gt; No matter what they say&lt;br&gt; You'll be here in my heart,&lt;br&gt; Always&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Why can't they understant&lt;br&gt; The way we feel?&lt;br&gt; They just don't trush&lt;br&gt; What they can't explain&lt;br&gt; I know we're different but,&lt;br&gt; Deep inside us&lt;br&gt; We're not that different at all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Repeat Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Don't listen to them &lt;br&gt; 'Cause what do they know?&lt;br&gt; We need each other&lt;br&gt; To have, to hold&lt;br&gt; They'll see in time&lt;br&gt; I know&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; When destiny calls you&lt;br&gt; You must be strong&lt;br&gt; I may not be with you&lt;br&gt; But you've got to hold on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; They'll see in time&lt;br&gt; I know&lt;br&gt; We'll show them together&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Repeat Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh, you'll be in my heart (You'll be here in my heart)&lt;br&gt; No matter what they say&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (I'll be with you)&lt;br&gt; You'll be here in my heart,&lt;br&gt; I'll be there always&lt;br&gt; Always&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'll be with you&lt;br&gt; I'll be there for you always&lt;br&gt; Always and always&lt;br&gt; Just look over your shoulder (x3)&lt;br&gt; I'll be there always</Lyrics>
</Song>
