<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>All The Right Moves</Title>
    <Artist>OneRepublic</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/4/f/4f982e2c106089dcfd59a222aab1ac3c_1363925216.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;All The Right Moves&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;OneRepublic&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjA5JTJGMjQlMkY4JTJGZiUyRjhmYzk5ZjNiYjU4ZjgyODVlYjFkZThiNmVmYmI4NTE5Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Paint a picture of a perfect place&lt;br&gt; They've got it better than what anyone's told you&lt;br&gt; We'll be the King of Hearts, you be the Queen of Spades&lt;br&gt; And we'll fight for you like we were your soliders&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I know we've got it good&lt;br&gt; But they've got it made&lt;br&gt; And the grass is getting greener each day&lt;br&gt; I know things are looking up&lt;br&gt; But soon they'll take us down&lt;br&gt; before everybody's knowing our name.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; They've got all the right things in all the wrong places&lt;br&gt; Someday, we're going down&lt;br&gt; They've got all the right moves and all the wrong faces&lt;br&gt; Someday, we're going down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Everybody knows, everybody knows where we're going&lt;br&gt; Yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; Everybody knows, everybody knows where we're going&lt;br&gt; Yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Do you think i'm special?&lt;br&gt; Do you think i'm nice?&lt;br&gt; Am I bright enough to shine in your spaces?&lt;br&gt; Between the noise you hear&lt;br&gt; And the sound you like&lt;br&gt; Are we just sinking in an ocean of faces?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It can be possible to make you fall,&lt;br&gt; Only when it's over our heads&lt;br&gt; The sun is shining everyday, but it's far away&lt;br&gt; All the world is dead, they've got they've got&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; They've got all the right things in all the wrong places&lt;br&gt; Someday, we're going down&lt;br&gt; They've got all the right moves and all the wrong faces&lt;br&gt; Someday, we're going down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Everybody knows, everybody knows where we're going&lt;br&gt; Yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; Everybody knows, everybody knows where we're going&lt;br&gt; http://www.elyricsworld.com/all_the_right_moves_lyrics_one_republic.html&lt;br&gt; Yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It don't matter what you see.&lt;br&gt; I know i could never be&lt;br&gt; Someone that looks like you.&lt;br&gt; Doesn't matter what you say&lt;br&gt; I know i could never fake&lt;br&gt; someone that could sound like you.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; All the right things in all the wrong places,&lt;br&gt; So yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; They've got all the right moves and all the wrong faces&lt;br&gt; So yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; All the right things in all the wrong places,&lt;br&gt; So yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; They've got all the right moves in all the wrong faces&lt;br&gt; So yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Everybody knows everybody knows where we're going&lt;br&gt; Yeah we're going down&lt;br&gt; Everybody knows everybody knows where we're going&lt;br&gt; Yeah we're going down&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; All the right moves&lt;br&gt; Yeah, we're going down&lt;br&gt; All the right moves&lt;br&gt; Yeah, we're going down</Lyrics>
</Song>
