<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Love To Be Loved By You</Title>
    <Artist>Marc Terenzi</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/a/5a5be1df1e7eedebe38707d26bc241d5_1288363002.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Love To Be Loved By You&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Marc Terenzi&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA3JTJGMjAlMkZiJTJGYiUyRmJiZGM2ZTA0Zjg1Njc0MWIyNWJmZTc1ZWNlZDRlZGQ0Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I can't believe I'm standing here&lt;br&gt; Been waiting for so many years and&lt;br&gt; Today I found the queen to reign my heart.&lt;br&gt; You changed my life so patiently&lt;br&gt; And turned it into something good and real&lt;br&gt; I feel just like I felt in all my dreams&lt;br&gt; There are questions hard to answer, can't you see...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [chorus]&lt;br&gt; Baby, tell me how can I tell you&lt;br&gt; That I love you more than life?&lt;br&gt; Show me how can I show you&lt;br&gt; That I'm blinded by your light.&lt;br&gt; When you touch me, I can touch you&lt;br&gt; To find out the dream is true.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I love to be loved by you.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You're looking kinda scared right now,&lt;br&gt; You're waiting for the wedding vows.&lt;br&gt; But I don't know if my tongue's able to talk&lt;br&gt; Your beauty is just blinding me,&lt;br&gt; Like sunbeams on a summer stream&lt;br&gt; And I gotta close my eyes to protect me.&lt;br&gt; Can you take my hand and lead me from here please?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah,yeah&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I love to be loved-&lt;br&gt; I need to be loved -&lt;br&gt; I love to be loved by you.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I know they're gonna say&lt;br&gt; Our love's not strong enough tO last forever.&lt;br&gt; And I know they're gonna say that we'll give up&lt;br&gt; Because of heavy weather.&lt;br&gt; But how can they understand&lt;br&gt; That our love is just heaven-sent,&lt;br&gt; We keep on going on and on&lt;br&gt; Cause this is where we both belong.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I love to be loved -&lt;br&gt; I need, yes I need to be loved -&lt;br&gt; I love to be loved by you.&lt;br&gt; Yes, I love to be loved by you.</Lyrics>
</Song>
