<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>My Love</Title>
    <Artist>Justin Timberlake ft. T.I.</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/8/6/86ee8117664b8d96ae27f7465704f731_1393307832.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;My Love&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Justin Timberlake,T.I.&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDIlMkYxJTJGNyUyRjE3Mzg4YTNhOWY2MTA5ZWUyOWFhNTg0NzNmMzZiZmUzLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Ain't another woman that can take your spot my-&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If I wrote you a symphony,&lt;br&gt; Just to say how much you mean to me (what would you do?)&lt;br&gt; If I told you you were beautiful&lt;br&gt; Would you date me on the regular (tell me, would you?)&lt;br&gt; Well, baby I've been around the world&lt;br&gt; But I ain't seen myself another girl (like you)&lt;br&gt; This ring here represents my heart&lt;br&gt; But there's just one thing I need from you (say &quot;I do&quot;)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; Yeah, because&lt;br&gt; I can see us holding hands&lt;br&gt; Walking on the beach, our toes in the sand&lt;br&gt; I can see us on the countryside&lt;br&gt; Sitting on the grass, laying side by side&lt;br&gt; You could be my baby, let me make you my lady&lt;br&gt; Girl, you amaze me&lt;br&gt; Ain't gotta do nothing crazy&lt;br&gt; See, all I want you to do is be my love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ooooh, girl&lt;br&gt; My love&lt;br&gt; My love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Now, if I wrote you a love note&lt;br&gt; And made you smile with every word I wrote (what would you do?)&lt;br&gt; Would that make you want to change your scene&lt;br&gt; And wanna be the one on my team (tell me, would you?)&lt;br&gt; See, what's the point of waiting anymore?&lt;br&gt; Cause girl I've never been more sure (that baby, it's you)&lt;br&gt; This ring here represents my heart&lt;br&gt; And everything that you've been waiting for (just say &quot;I do&quot;)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; Yeah, because&lt;br&gt; I can see us holding hands&lt;br&gt; Walking on the beach, our toes in the sand&lt;br&gt; I can see us on the countryside&lt;br&gt; Sitting on the grass, laying side by side&lt;br&gt; You could be my baby, let me make you my lady&lt;br&gt; Girl, you amaze me&lt;br&gt; Ain't gotta do nothing crazy&lt;br&gt; See, all I want you to do is be my love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) My love&lt;br&gt; (So don't give away) Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ooooh, girl&lt;br&gt; My love&lt;br&gt; My love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [T.I.'s rap:]&lt;br&gt; Alright it's time to get it JT&lt;br&gt; I don't know why she hesitates for man&lt;br&gt; Shorty, cool as a fan&lt;br&gt; On the new once again&lt;br&gt; But, still has fan from Peru to Japan&lt;br&gt; Listen baby, I don't wanna ruin your plan&lt;br&gt; If you got a man, try to lose him if you can&lt;br&gt; Cause the girls worldwide throw their hands up high&lt;br&gt; When they wanna come kick it wit a stand up guy&lt;br&gt; (Trust me) You don't really wanna let the chance go by&lt;br&gt; 'cause you ain't been seen wit a man so fly&lt;br&gt; Baby friends so fly I can go fly&lt;br&gt; Private, cause I handle my B.I.&lt;br&gt; They call me candle guy, simply because I am on fire&lt;br&gt; I hate to have to cancel my vacation so you can't deny&lt;br&gt; I'm patient, but I ain't gonna try&lt;br&gt; You don't come, I ain't gonna die&lt;br&gt; Hold up, what you mean, you can't go why?&lt;br&gt; Me and your boyfriend we ain't no tie&lt;br&gt; You say you wanna kick it when I ain't so high?&lt;br&gt; Well, baby it's obvious that I ain't your guy&lt;br&gt; Ain't gon' lie, I feel your space&lt;br&gt; But forget your face, I swear I will&lt;br&gt; St. Bart, St. Bulla anywhere I chill&lt;br&gt; Just bring wit me a pair, I will&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; I can see us holding hands&lt;br&gt; Walking on the beach, our toes in the sand&lt;br&gt; I can see us on the countryside&lt;br&gt; Sitting on the grass, laying side by side&lt;br&gt; You could be my baby, let me make you my lady&lt;br&gt; Girl, you amaze me&lt;br&gt; Ain't gotta do nothing crazy&lt;br&gt; See, all I want you to do is be my love&lt;br&gt; (Love) My love&lt;br&gt; (Love) My love&lt;br&gt; (Love) Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love&lt;br&gt; (Love) My love&lt;br&gt; (Love) My love&lt;br&gt; (Love) Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ooooh, girl&lt;br&gt; My love&lt;br&gt; My love</Lyrics>
</Song>
