<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Stronger</Title>
    <Artist>Kanye West</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/d/9/d99119ca42e35bfa7fbc7fba9ab1d88a_1377568784.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Stronger&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Kanye West&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEwJTJGMDIlMkY1JTJGMSUyRjUxMDQ5ZmRmYjI4ZDgwMGI0OWUwZWFjNjFhZjhkM2RjLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Stronger&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Work it, make it, do it,&lt;br&gt; Makes us harder, better, faster, stronger!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [played in background, continuously:]&lt;br&gt; Work it harder, make it better,&lt;br&gt; do it faster, makes us stronger,&lt;br&gt; more than ever, never over,&lt;br&gt; Our work here is never over.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; N- n- now th- that don't kill me&lt;br&gt; Can only make me stronger&lt;br&gt; I need you to hurry up now&lt;br&gt; 'cause I can't wait much longer&lt;br&gt; I know I got to be right now&lt;br&gt; 'cause I can't get much wronger&lt;br&gt; Man I've been waitin' all night now&lt;br&gt; That's how long I've been on you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need you right now&lt;br&gt; I need you right now&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Let's get lost tonight&lt;br&gt; You could be my black Kate Moss tonight&lt;br&gt; Play secretary, I'm the boss tonight&lt;br&gt; And you don't give a fuck what they all say right?&lt;br&gt; Awesome, the Christian and Christian Dior&lt;br&gt; Damn, they don't make 'em like this anymore&lt;br&gt; I ask 'cause I'm not sure&lt;br&gt; Do anybody make real shit anymore?&lt;br&gt; Bow in the presence of greatness&lt;br&gt; 'cause right now thou has forsaken us&lt;br&gt; You should be honored by my lateness&lt;br&gt; That I would even show up to this fake shit&lt;br&gt; So go ahead go nuts go ape shit&lt;br&gt; Especially in my pastel on my bape shit&lt;br&gt; Act like you can't tell who made this&lt;br&gt; New gospel homey, take six, and take this, haters&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need you right now&lt;br&gt; I need you right now&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Me likey&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I don't know if you got a man or not,&lt;br&gt; If you made plans or not&lt;br&gt; God put me in the plans or not&lt;br&gt; I'm trippin' this drink got me sayin' a lot&lt;br&gt; But I know that God put you in front of me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So how the hell could you front on me?&lt;br&gt; There's a thousand you's, there's only one of me&lt;br&gt; I'm trippin', I'm caught up in the moment right?&lt;br&gt; This is Louis Vuitton Don night&lt;br&gt; So we gonna do everything that Kan like&lt;br&gt; Heard they'd do anything for a Klondike&lt;br&gt; Well I'd do anything for a blonde-dike&lt;br&gt; And she'll do anything for the limelight&lt;br&gt; And we'll do anything when the time's right&lt;br&gt; Ugh, baby, you're makin' it (harder, better, faster, stronger)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need you right now&lt;br&gt; I need you right now&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You know how long I've been on you?&lt;br&gt; Since Prince was on Apollonia&lt;br&gt; Since OJ had Isotoners&lt;br&gt; Don't act like I never told you [x6]&lt;br&gt; Baby, you're making it (harder, better, faster, stronger)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I need you right now [x4]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You know how long I've been on you?&lt;br&gt; Since Prince was on Apollonia&lt;br&gt; Since OJ had Isotoners&lt;br&gt; Don't act like I never told you&lt;br&gt; Never told you [x4]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Never over [x8]</Lyrics>
</Song>
