<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Beautiful.</Title>
    <Artist>Eminem</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/0/a0538a67982e1ef3e3bd2922cb6dd9ce_1383013435.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Beautiful.&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Eminem&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMyUyRjEwJTJGMTclMkY4JTJGZiUyRjhmNWNlZjc0YjRmZjM1ZGZhYjM0OTNiMmMxMDdkODI5Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Crack A Bottle&quot;&lt;br&gt; (feat. Dr. Dre, 50 Cent)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ooww Ladies and gentlemen&lt;br&gt; The moment you've all been waiting for..&lt;br&gt; In this corner: weighing 175 pounds,&lt;br&gt; With a record of 17 rapes, 400 assaults, and 4 murders,&lt;br&gt; The undisputed, most diabolical villain in the world:&lt;br&gt; Slim Shady!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; So crack a bottle, let your body waddle&lt;br&gt; Don't act like a snobby model you just hit the lotto&lt;br&gt; O-oh o-oh, bitches hopping in my Tahoe&lt;br&gt; Got one riding shotgun and no not one of em got clothes&lt;br&gt; Now where's the rubbers? Whose got the rubbers?&lt;br&gt; I notice there's so many of em&lt;br&gt; And there's really not that many of us.&lt;br&gt; Ladies love us and my posse's kicking up dust.&lt;br&gt; It's on till the break of dawn&lt;br&gt; And we're starting this party from dusk&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; OK... let's go&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Back wit Andre, the giant, mister elephant tusk&lt;br&gt; Fix your musk, you'll just be another one bit the dust&lt;br&gt; Just one of my mothers son who got thrown under the bus&lt;br&gt; Kiss my butt. Lick the fumunda cheese from under my nuts&lt;br&gt; It disgusts me to see the game the way that it looks&lt;br&gt; It's a must I redeem my name n haters get mushed.&lt;br&gt; Bitches lust. Man they love me when I lay in the cut.&lt;br&gt; Fist the cup. The lady gave her eighty some paper cut.&lt;br&gt; Now picture us. it's ridiculous you curse at the thought&lt;br&gt; Cause when I spit the verse the sh-t&lt;br&gt; Gets worse then Worcestershire sauce&lt;br&gt; If I could fit the words as picture perfect, works every time&lt;br&gt; Every verse, every line, as simple as nursery rhymes&lt;br&gt; It's elementary. The elephants have entered the room.&lt;br&gt; I venture to say we're the center of attention it's true&lt;br&gt; Not to mention back with a vengeance so here's the signal&lt;br&gt; Of the bat symbol. The platinum trio's back on you hoes.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus: Eminem]&lt;br&gt; So crack a bottle, let your body waddle&lt;br&gt; Don't act like a snobby model you just hit the lotto&lt;br&gt; O-oh o-oh, bitches hopping in my Tahoe&lt;br&gt; Got one riding shotgun and no not one of em got clothes&lt;br&gt; Now where's the rubbers? Whose got the rubbers?&lt;br&gt; I notice there's so many of em&lt;br&gt; And there's really not that many of us.&lt;br&gt; Ladies love us and my posse's kicking up dust.&lt;br&gt; It's on till the break of dawn&lt;br&gt; And we're starting this party from dusk&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ladies and gentlemen, Dr. Dre&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Dr. Dre]&lt;br&gt; They see that low rider go by they're, like Oh my!&lt;br&gt; You ain't got to tell me why you're sick cause I know why.&lt;br&gt; I dip through in that six trey like sick em Dre.&lt;br&gt; I'm an itch that they can't scratch, they're sick of me.&lt;br&gt; But hey, what else can I say? I love LA.&lt;br&gt; Cause over and above all, it's just another day&lt;br&gt; And this one begins where the last one ends.&lt;br&gt; Pick up where we left off and get smashed again.&lt;br&gt; I'll be dammed, just f*cked around and crashed my Benz.&lt;br&gt; Driving around with a smashed front end&lt;br&gt; Lets cash that one in.&lt;br&gt; Grab another one from out the stable&lt;br&gt; The Monte Carlo, El Camino or the El Dorado&lt;br&gt; The hell if I know.&lt;br&gt; Do I want leather seats or vinyl?&lt;br&gt; Decisions, decisions&lt;br&gt; Garage looks like Precision Collision.&lt;br&gt; Or Maaco beats quake like Waco&lt;br&gt; Just keep the bass low speakers away from your face though&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So crack a bottle, let your body waddle&lt;br&gt; Don't act like a snobby model you just hit the lotto&lt;br&gt; O-oh o-oh, bitches hopping in my Tahoe&lt;br&gt; Got one riding shotgun and no not one of em got clothes&lt;br&gt; Now where's the rubbers? Whose got the rubbers?&lt;br&gt; I notice there's so many of em&lt;br&gt; And there's really not that many of us.&lt;br&gt; Ladies love us and my posse's kicking up dust.&lt;br&gt; It's on till the break of dawn&lt;br&gt; And we're starting this party from dusk&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And I take great pleasure in introducing: 50 Cent&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [50 Cent]&lt;br&gt; It's bottle after bottle&lt;br&gt; The money ain't a thing when you party with me&lt;br&gt; It's what we into it's simple&lt;br&gt; We ball out of control like you wouldn't believe&lt;br&gt; I'm the napalm the bomb the don I'm King Kong&lt;br&gt; Get rolled on wrapped up and reigned on&lt;br&gt; I'm so calm through Vietnam ring the alarm&lt;br&gt; Bring the shaun dawn burn marajaun do what you want&lt;br&gt; Nigga on and on till the break of what&lt;br&gt; Get the paper man I'm caking you know I don't give a fuck&lt;br&gt; I spend it like it don't mean nothing&lt;br&gt; Blow it like it's supposed to be blown&lt;br&gt; Mother fucker I'm grown&lt;br&gt; I stunt I style I flash the shit&lt;br&gt; I gets what the fuck I want so what I trick&lt;br&gt; Fat ass burgundy bags classy shit Jimmy Choos shoes&lt;br&gt; I say move a bitch move&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So crack a bottle, let your body waddle&lt;br&gt; Don't act like a snobby model you just hit the lotto&lt;br&gt; O-oh o-oh, bitches hopping in my Tahoe&lt;br&gt; Got one riding shotgun and no not one of em got clothes&lt;br&gt; Now where's the rubbers? Whose got the rubbers?&lt;br&gt; I notice there's so many of em&lt;br&gt; And there's really not that many of us.&lt;br&gt; Ladies love us and my posse's kicking up dust.&lt;br&gt; It's on till the break of dawn&lt;br&gt; And we're starting this party from dusk &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
