<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Remember The Name</Title>
    <Artist>Fort Minor</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/9/4/9414776efd3676868636d206013f8343_1288098591.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Remember The Name&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Fort Minor&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjAzJTJGMTIlMkY1JTJGOCUyRjU4NzNmNDBlNWJjNDgxYTdlNGEyYjI4MDNlYWRiZmQwLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>You ready?! Let's go!&lt;br&gt; Yeah, for those of you that want to know what we're all about&lt;br&gt; It's like this y'all (c'mon!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; This is ten percent luck, twenty percent skill&lt;br&gt; Fifteen percent concentrated power of will&lt;br&gt; Five percent pleasure, fifty percent pain&lt;br&gt; And a hundred percent reason to remember the name!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Mike! - He doesn't need his name up in lights&lt;br&gt; He just wants to be heard whether it's the beat or the mic&lt;br&gt; He feels so unlike everybody else, alone&lt;br&gt; In spite of the fact that some people still think that they know him&lt;br&gt; But fuck em, he knows the code&lt;br&gt; It's not about the salary&lt;br&gt; It's all about reality and making some noise&lt;br&gt; Making the story - making sure his clique stays up&lt;br&gt; That means when he puts it down Tak's picking it up! Let's go!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Who the hell is he anyway?&lt;br&gt; He never really talks much&lt;br&gt; Never concerned with status but still leaving them star struck&lt;br&gt; Humbled through opportunities given despite the fact&lt;br&gt; That many misjudge him because he makes a living from writing raps&lt;br&gt; Put it together himself, now the picture connects&lt;br&gt; Never asking for someone's help, or to get some respect&lt;br&gt; He's only focused on what he wrote, his will is beyond reach&lt;br&gt; And now it all unfolds, the skill of an artist&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This is twenty percent skill&lt;br&gt; Eighty percent beer&lt;br&gt; Be a hundred percent clear cause Ryu is ill&lt;br&gt; Who would've thought that he'd be the one to set the west in flames&lt;br&gt; And I heard him wreck it with The Crystal Method, &quot;Name Of The Game&quot;&lt;br&gt; Came back dropped Megadef, took em to church&lt;br&gt; I like bleach man, why you had the stupidest verse?&lt;br&gt; This dude is the truth, now everybody's giving him guest spots&lt;br&gt; His stock's through the roof I heard he's fuckin' with S. Dot!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; They call him Ryu, he's sick&lt;br&gt; And he's spitting fire&lt;br&gt; And mike got him out the dryer he's hot&lt;br&gt; Found him in Fort Minor with Tak&lt;br&gt; What a fuckin' nihilist porcupine&lt;br&gt; He's a prick, he's a cock&lt;br&gt; The type woman want to be with, and rappers hope he get shot&lt;br&gt; Eight years in the making, patiently waiting to blow&lt;br&gt; Now the record with Shinoda's taking over the globe&lt;br&gt; He's got a partner in crime, his shit is equally dope&lt;br&gt; You wont believe the kind of shit that comes out of this kid's throat&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Tak! - He's not your everyday on the block&lt;br&gt; He knows how to work with what he's got&lt;br&gt; Making his way to the top&lt;br&gt; He often gets a comment on his name&lt;br&gt; People keep asking him was it given at birth&lt;br&gt; Or does it stand for an acronym?&lt;br&gt; No he's living proof, got him rocking the booth&lt;br&gt; He'll get you buzzing quicker than a shot of vodka with juice&lt;br&gt; Him and his crew are known around as one of the best&lt;br&gt; Dedicated to what they do and give a hundred percent&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Forget Mike - Nobody really knows how or why he works so hard&lt;br&gt; It seems like he's never got time&lt;br&gt; Because he writes every note and he writes every line&lt;br&gt; And I've seen him at work when that light goes on in his mind&lt;br&gt; It's like a design is written in his head every time&lt;br&gt; Before he even touches a key or speaks in a rhyme&lt;br&gt; And those motherfuckers he runs with,&lt;br&gt; The kids that he signed?&lt;br&gt; Ridiculous, without even trying,&lt;br&gt; How did he do it?!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - repeat 2x]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Outro - Mike Shinoda:]&lt;br&gt; Yeah! Fort Minor&lt;br&gt; M. Shinoda - Styles of Beyond&lt;br&gt; Ryu! Takbir! Machine Shop!</Lyrics>
</Song>
