<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Low</Title>
    <Artist>Flo Rida ft. T-Pain</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/e/d/edf5f0a5182634fc280551e0b3910804_1345220131.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Low&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Flo Rida,T-Pain&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMDglMkY3JTJGOSUyRjc5NThlN2M3ZjFkODRlYzA4ZmE4NTA4ZWE5NjhkNDMzLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&lt;br&gt; &quot;Low&quot;&lt;br&gt; (feat. T-Pain)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Intro - T-Pain]&lt;br&gt; Mmmmmmmm&lt;br&gt; Let me talk to 'em&lt;br&gt; Let me talk to 'em&lt;br&gt; Mmmmmmm&lt;br&gt; Let me talk to 'em&lt;br&gt; C'mon!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (T-Pain):]&lt;br&gt; Shawty had them apple bottom jeans (jeans)&lt;br&gt; Boots with the fur (with the fur)&lt;br&gt; The whole club was looking at her&lt;br&gt; She hit the floor (she hit the floor)&lt;br&gt; Next thing you know&lt;br&gt; Shawty got low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low&lt;br&gt; Them baggy sweat pants&lt;br&gt; And the Reebok's with the straps (with the straps)&lt;br&gt; She turned around and gave that big booty a smack (hey)&lt;br&gt; She hit the floor (she hit the floor)&lt;br&gt; Next thing you know&lt;br&gt; Shawty got low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Flo-Rida]&lt;br&gt; I ain't never seen something that'll make me go&lt;br&gt; This crazy all night spending my doe&lt;br&gt; Had the million dollar vibe and a body to go&lt;br&gt; Them birthday cakes they stole the show&lt;br&gt; So sexual&lt;br&gt; She was flexible professional&lt;br&gt; Drinking X&amp;amp;O&lt;br&gt; Hold up, wait a minute, do I see what I think? Whoa&lt;br&gt; Did her thing seen shawty get low&lt;br&gt; Ain't the same when it's up that close&lt;br&gt; Make it rain I'm making it snow&lt;br&gt; Work the pole I gotta bank roll&lt;br&gt; I'm gonna say that I prefer the no clothes&lt;br&gt; I'm in to that I love women exposed&lt;br&gt; She threw it back at me I gave her mo&lt;br&gt; Cash ain't a problem I know where it go&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (T-Pain)]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Flo-Rida]&lt;br&gt; Hey shawty what I gotta do to get you home&lt;br&gt; My jeans filled with guap and they're ready for showing&lt;br&gt; Cadillacs laid back for the sexy grown&lt;br&gt; Patron on the rocks that'll make you moan&lt;br&gt; One stack (come on), two stacks (come on), three stacks (come on)&lt;br&gt; Now that's three grand&lt;br&gt; What you think I'm playing baby girl I'm the man&lt;br&gt; I'm dealing rubber bands&lt;br&gt; That's when I threw her legs on my shoulders&lt;br&gt; I knew it was over&lt;br&gt; That heny and Cola got me like a soldier&lt;br&gt; She ready for Rover, I couldn't control her&lt;br&gt; So lucky on me I was just like clover&lt;br&gt; Shawty was hot like a toaster&lt;br&gt; Sorry but I had to fold her&lt;br&gt; Like a pornography poster&lt;br&gt; She showed her&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (T-Pain)]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Flo-Rida]&lt;br&gt; Whoa shawty yeah she was worth the money&lt;br&gt; Little mama took my cash&lt;br&gt; And I ain't want it back&lt;br&gt; The way she bent that back&lt;br&gt; Got all them paper stacks&lt;br&gt; Tattoo above her crack&lt;br&gt; I had to handle that&lt;br&gt; I was zoned in sexy woman&lt;br&gt; Let me show it make me want it&lt;br&gt; Two in the morning I'm zoned in&lt;br&gt; Them rosee bottles foaming&lt;br&gt; She wouldn't stop&lt;br&gt; Made it drop&lt;br&gt; Shawty dipped that pop and lock&lt;br&gt; Had to break her off that guap&lt;br&gt; Gal was fine just like my glock&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (T-Pain)] &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
