<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>If I Were A Boy</Title>
    <Artist>Beyoncé</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/2/b28c7b0a3201fa58c672b988dcd19dd0_1416815243.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;If I Were A Boy&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Beyonc\u00e9&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMjAlMkYxJTJGNSUyRjE1Y2MyNWNiZDI2YjJiZTlkMWM2ZmQwODcyNTdmNzkxLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Verse]&lt;br&gt; If I were a boy&lt;br&gt; Even just for a day&lt;br&gt; I’d roll outta bed in the morning&lt;br&gt; And throw on what I wanted then go&lt;br&gt; Drink beer with the guys&lt;br&gt; And chase after girls&lt;br&gt; I’d kick it with who I wanted&lt;br&gt; And I’d never get confronted for it.&lt;br&gt; Cause they’d stick up for me.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; If I were a boy&lt;br&gt; I think I could understand&lt;br&gt; How it feels to love a girl&lt;br&gt; I swear I’d be a better man.&lt;br&gt; I’d listen to her&lt;br&gt; Cause I know how it hurts&lt;br&gt; When you lose the one you wanted&lt;br&gt; Cause he’s taken you for granted&lt;br&gt; And everything you had got destroyed&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse]&lt;br&gt; If I were a boy&lt;br&gt; I would turn off my phone&lt;br&gt; Tell everyone it’s broken&lt;br&gt; So they’d think that I was sleepin’ alone&lt;br&gt; I’d put myself first&lt;br&gt; And make the rules as I go&lt;br&gt; Cause I know that she’d be faithful&lt;br&gt; Waitin’ for me to come home (to come home)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; If I were a boy&lt;br&gt; I think I could understand&lt;br&gt; How it feels to love a girl&lt;br&gt; I swear I’d be a better man.&lt;br&gt; I’d listen to her&lt;br&gt; Cause I know how it hurts&lt;br&gt; When you lose the one you wanted (wanted)&lt;br&gt; Cause he’s taken you for granted (granted)&lt;br&gt; And everything you had got destroyed&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge]&lt;br&gt; It’s a little too late for you to come back&lt;br&gt; Say its just a mistake&lt;br&gt; Think I’d forgive you like that&lt;br&gt; If you thought I would wait for you&lt;br&gt; You thought wrong&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus 2]&lt;br&gt; But you’re just a boy&lt;br&gt; You don’t understand&lt;br&gt; Yeah you don’t understand&lt;br&gt; How it feels to love a girl someday&lt;br&gt; You wish you were a better man&lt;br&gt; You don’t listen to her&lt;br&gt; You don’t care how it hurts&lt;br&gt; Until you lose the one you wanted&lt;br&gt; Cause you’ve taken her for granted&lt;br&gt; And everything you have got destroyed&lt;br&gt; But you’re just a boy</Lyrics>
</Song>
