<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Billionaire</Title>
    <Artist>Travie McCoy ft. Bruno Mars</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/e/3e9f2da3abf9193d7fcbf9917e9284d9_1336385739.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Billionaire&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Travie McCoy,Bruno Mars&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjEyJTJGMDQlMkZhJTJGYSUyRmFhMTNiZjM1MWU5ZmNmNDZjMWE4ODlmNjg4NTQxZDE5Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I wanna be a billionaire so freakin' bad.&lt;br&gt; Buy all of the things I never had.&lt;br&gt; Uh.&lt;br&gt; I wanna be on the cover of Forbes magazine,&lt;br&gt; Smiling next to Oprah and the Queen.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh every time I close my eyes,&lt;br&gt; I see my name in shinin' lights.&lt;br&gt; Yeah, a different city every night.&lt;br&gt; Oh I, I swear, the world better prepare for when I'm a billionaire.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah, I would have a show like Oprah.&lt;br&gt; I would be the host of, everyday Christmas.&lt;br&gt; Give Artie a wish list.&lt;br&gt; I'd probably pull an Angelina and Brad Pitt,&lt;br&gt; And adopt a bunch of babies that ain't never had shit.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Give away a few Mercedes like &quot;here lady, have this&quot;,&lt;br&gt; And last but not least grant somebody their last wish.&lt;br&gt; It's been a couple months since I've single so,&lt;br&gt; You can call me Travie Claus minus the Ho Ho.&lt;br&gt; Haa, get it?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'd probably visit where Katrina hit,&lt;br&gt; And damn sure do a lot more than FEMA did.&lt;br&gt; Yeah, can't forget about me stupid,&lt;br&gt; Everywhere I go Imma have my own theme music.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh, every time I close my eyes,&lt;br&gt; (what chu see, what chu see bro?)&lt;br&gt; I see my name in shiny lights.&lt;br&gt; (uh huh).&lt;br&gt; Ahh, yeah yeah.&lt;br&gt; (what else?)&lt;br&gt; A different city every night.&lt;br&gt; Oh I, I swear, the world better prepare..&lt;br&gt; (for what?)&lt;br&gt; For when I'm a billionaire.&lt;br&gt; (yeah!) &lt;br&gt; Oh oooh oh oooh,&lt;br&gt; When I'm a Billionaire.&lt;br&gt; Oh oooh oh oooh.&lt;br&gt; (let's go)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'll be playing basketball with the President,&lt;br&gt; Dunking on his delegates.&lt;br&gt; Then I'll compliment him on his political etiquette.&lt;br&gt; Toss a couple million in the air just for the heck of it.&lt;br&gt; But keep the fives, twentys, tens and bens completely separate.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah, I'll be in a whole new tax bracket.&lt;br&gt; We in recession but let me take a crack at it.&lt;br&gt; I'll probably take whatevers left and just split it up.&lt;br&gt; So everybody that I love can have a couple bucks.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And, not a single tummy around me would know what hungry was.&lt;br&gt; Eating good, sleeping soundly.&lt;br&gt; I know we all have a similar dream.&lt;br&gt; Go in your pocket, pull out your wallet, put it in the air and sing...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna be a billionaire so freakin' bad.&lt;br&gt; (So bad)&lt;br&gt; Buy all of the things I never had.&lt;br&gt; (Buy everything, haa)&lt;br&gt; Uh.&lt;br&gt; I wanna be on the cover of Forbes magazine.&lt;br&gt; Smiling next to Oprah and the Queen.&lt;br&gt; (What up Oprah? Haaa!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh every time I close my eyes,&lt;br&gt; (what chu see, what chu see bro?)&lt;br&gt; I see my name in shinin' lights.&lt;br&gt; (uh huh).&lt;br&gt; Ahh, yeah yeah.&lt;br&gt; (what else?)&lt;br&gt; A different city every night.&lt;br&gt; Oh (yeah yeah yeah)&lt;br&gt; I - I swear, the world better prepare..&lt;br&gt; (for what?)&lt;br&gt; For when I'm a billionaire.&lt;br&gt; (yeah!) &lt;br&gt; Oh oooh oh oooh,&lt;br&gt; (Sing it)&lt;br&gt; When I'm a Billionaire.&lt;br&gt; Oh oooh oh oooh.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna be a billionaire&lt;br&gt; so freakin' bad.</Lyrics>
</Song>
