<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Whatcha Say.</Title>
    <Artist>Jason DeRulo</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/a/3ac9682aa237b4ac1b0db6d04c463cbf_1397791653.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Whatcha Say.&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Jason DeRulo&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjExJTJGMTIlMkZkJTJGOCUyRmQ4YmQ1ZDFjZDMyYjc4YmFkNDlkMTllNzFmYzhiMGIwLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Chorus]&lt;br&gt; wha- wha- what did she say&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmm that you only meant well?&lt;br&gt; well of course you did&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmmm that it´s all for the best?&lt;br&gt; of course it is&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1]&lt;br&gt; I was so wrong for so long&lt;br&gt; only tryin´ to please myself (myself)&lt;br&gt; girl i was caught up in her lust&lt;br&gt; when i don´t really want no one else&lt;br&gt; so no i know i should of treated you better&lt;br&gt; but me and you were meant to last forever&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; s o let me in (let me in) give me another chance (another chance)&lt;br&gt; to really be your man&lt;br&gt; cause when the roof cave in and the truth came out&lt;br&gt; i just didn´t know what to do&lt;br&gt; but when i become a star we´ll be living so large&lt;br&gt; i´ll do anything for you&lt;br&gt; so tell me girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; Mm mm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmm that you only meant well?&lt;br&gt; well of course you did&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say (whatcha say)&lt;br&gt; Mmmm that it´s all for the best?&lt;br&gt; of course it is&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmm that you only meant well?&lt;br&gt; well of course you did&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say (whatcha say)&lt;br&gt; wha- wha- wha- wha- what did she say&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2]&lt;br&gt; how could i live with myself&lt;br&gt; knowing that i let our love go (love go)&lt;br&gt; and ooh when i do with one chance&lt;br&gt; i just gotta let you know&lt;br&gt; i know what i did wasn´t clever&lt;br&gt; but me and you we´re meant to be together&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; so let me in (let me in) give me another chance (another chance)&lt;br&gt; to really be your man&lt;br&gt; cause when the roof cave in and the truth came out&lt;br&gt; i just didn´t know what to do&lt;br&gt; but when i become a star we´ll be living so large&lt;br&gt; i´ll do anything for you&lt;br&gt; so tell me girl&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; Mm mm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmm that you only meant well?&lt;br&gt; well of course you did&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say (whatcha say whatcha say)&lt;br&gt; Mmmm that it´s all for the best?&lt;br&gt; of course it is&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmm that you only meant well?&lt;br&gt; well of course you did&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say (whatcha say whatcha say)&lt;br&gt; wha- wha- wha- wha- what did she say&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 3]&lt;br&gt; girl tell me whatcha said (said)&lt;br&gt; i don´t want you to leave me&lt;br&gt; though you caught me cheatin´&lt;br&gt; tell me tell me whatcha said (said)&lt;br&gt; i really need you in my life&lt;br&gt; cuz things ain´t right girl&lt;br&gt; tell me tell me whatcha said (said)&lt;br&gt; i don´t want you to leave me&lt;br&gt; though you caught me cheatin´&lt;br&gt; tell me tell me whatcha said (said)&lt;br&gt; i really need you in my life&lt;br&gt; cuz things ain´t right&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; cau se when the roof cave in and the truth came out&lt;br&gt; i just didn´t know what to do&lt;br&gt; but when i become a star we´ll be living so large&lt;br&gt; i´ll do anything for you&lt;br&gt; so baby watcha say!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; Mm mm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmm that you only meant well?&lt;br&gt; well of course you did&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say (whatcha say whatcha say)&lt;br&gt; Mmmm that it´s all for the best?&lt;br&gt; of course it is&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say&lt;br&gt; Mmm that you only meant well?&lt;br&gt; well of course you did&lt;br&gt; Mmmm whatcha say (whatcha say whatcha say)&lt;br&gt; wha- wha- wha- wha- what did she say</Lyrics>
</Song>
