<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>I Need A Doctor</Title>
    <Artist>Dr. Dre ft. Eminem ft. Skylar Grey</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/2/b/2b93443254439424dfdecc536fae33f9_1298095155.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;I Need A Doctor&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Dr. Dre,Eminem,Skylar Grey&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjAyJTJGMDglMkY2JTJGOCUyRjY4MTE1OTY4NjBjZDcxMGYzNTQyMmVkNjJkMTAxMmJmLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Skylar Grey]&lt;br&gt; I'm about to lose my mind&lt;br&gt; you've been gone for so long&lt;br&gt; I'm running out of time&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor&lt;br&gt; call me a doctor&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor, doctor&lt;br&gt; to bring me back to life&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Eminem]&lt;br&gt; I told the world one day I would pay it back&lt;br&gt; say it on tape, and lay it, record it&lt;br&gt; so that one day I could play it back&lt;br&gt; but I don't even know if I believe it when I'm saying that&lt;br&gt; ya'll starting to creep in, everyday it's just so grey and black&lt;br&gt; Hope - I just need a ray of that&lt;br&gt; 'Cause no one sees my vision when I play it for 'em&lt;br&gt; They just say it's wack&lt;br&gt; they don't know what dope is&lt;br&gt; and I don't know if I was awake or asleep&lt;br&gt; when I wrote this,&lt;br&gt; all I know is you came to me when I was at my lowest&lt;br&gt; you picked me up, breathing life in me&lt;br&gt; I owe my life to you&lt;br&gt; but for the life of me, I don't see why you don't see like I do&lt;br&gt; but it just dawned on me you lost a son&lt;br&gt; daemons fighting you, it's dark.&lt;br&gt; let me turn on the lights and brighten me and enlighten you&lt;br&gt; I don't think you realize what you mean to me&lt;br&gt; not the slightest clue&lt;br&gt; 'Cause me and you were like a crew&lt;br&gt; I was like your sidekick&lt;br&gt; you gon either wanna fight me when I get off this fucking mic&lt;br&gt; or you gon hug me&lt;br&gt; But I'm out of options, there's nothing else I can do 'cause&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Skylar Grey]&lt;br&gt; I'm about to lose my mind&lt;br&gt; you've been gone for so long&lt;br&gt; I'm running out of time&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor&lt;br&gt; call me a doctor&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor, doctor&lt;br&gt; to bring me back to life&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Eminem]&lt;br&gt; It hurts when I see you struggle&lt;br&gt; you come to me with ideas&lt;br&gt; You say they're just pieces so I'm puzzled&lt;br&gt; 'Cause the shit I hear is crazy&lt;br&gt; But you're either getting lazy or you don't believe in you no more&lt;br&gt; seems like your own opinion's not one you can form&lt;br&gt; Can't make a decision you keep questioning yourself&lt;br&gt; Second guessing and it's almost like you're begging for my help&lt;br&gt; like I'm your leader&lt;br&gt; your supposed to fucking be my mentor&lt;br&gt; I can endure no more,&lt;br&gt; I demand you remember who you are&lt;br&gt; it was you who believed in me&lt;br&gt; when everyone was telling you don't sign me&lt;br&gt; Everyone at the fucking label, let's tell the truth&lt;br&gt; you risked your career for me&lt;br&gt; I know it as well as you&lt;br&gt; nobody wanted to fuck with the white boy&lt;br&gt; Dre, I'm crying in this booth&lt;br&gt; You saved my life, now maybe it's my turn to save yours&lt;br&gt; but I can never repay you, what you did for me is way more&lt;br&gt; but I ain't giving up faith and you ain't giving up on me&lt;br&gt; Get up Dre, I'm dying, I need you, come back for fuck's sake 'cause&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Skylar Grey]&lt;br&gt; I'm about to lose my mind&lt;br&gt; you've been gone for so long&lt;br&gt; I'm running out of time&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor&lt;br&gt; call me a doctor&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor, doctor&lt;br&gt; to bring me back to life&lt;br&gt; bring me back to life&lt;br&gt; bring me back to life&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (I need a doctor, doctor&lt;br&gt; to bring me back to life)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Dr Dre]&lt;br&gt; It literally feels like a lifetime ago&lt;br&gt; but I still remember the shit like it was just yesterday though&lt;br&gt; you walked in, yellow jump suit&lt;br&gt; whole room, cracked jokes&lt;br&gt; once you got inside the booth, told you, like smoke&lt;br&gt; went through friends, some of them I put on&lt;br&gt; but they just left, they said they was riding to the death&lt;br&gt; But where the fuck are they now?&lt;br&gt; now that I need them, I don't see none of them&lt;br&gt; all I see is Slim&lt;br&gt; fuck all you fair-weather friends&lt;br&gt; all I need is him&lt;br&gt; fucking backstabbers&lt;br&gt; when the chips were down you just laughed at us&lt;br&gt; Now you 'bout to feel the fucking wrath of Aftermath, faggots&lt;br&gt; you gon see us in our lab jackets and ask us where the fuck we been?&lt;br&gt; You can kiss my indecisive ass crack, maggots, and the cracker's ass&lt;br&gt; Little Cracker Jack, beat-making wackass backwards producers&lt;br&gt; I'm back, bastards&lt;br&gt; one more CD and then I'm packing up my bags and as I'm leaving&lt;br&gt; I'll guarantee they scream, Dre don't leave us like that man 'cause&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Skylar Grey]&lt;br&gt; I'm about to lose my mind&lt;br&gt; you've been gone for so long&lt;br&gt; I'm running out of time&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor&lt;br&gt; call me a doctor&lt;br&gt; I need a doctor, doctor&lt;br&gt; to bring me back to life</Lyrics>
</Song>
