<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Coming Home</Title>
    <Artist>Diddy Dirty Money ft. Skylar Grey</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/8/3/83e5e82e6aae0a9bf670891f9764eca6_1292984734.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Coming Home&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Diddy Dirty Money,Skylar Grey&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMjMlMkZkJTJGNyUyRmQ3NGYxMDMzYjk4ZmZiZTI3ZjhkOGQ3YTdlZDUzZmU1Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Dirty Money - Chorus]&lt;br&gt; I’m coming home&lt;br&gt; I’m coming home&lt;br&gt; tell the World I’m coming home&lt;br&gt; Let the rain wash away all the pain of yesterday&lt;br&gt; I know my kingdom awaits and they’ve forgiven my mistakes&lt;br&gt; I’m coming home, I’m coming home&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; tell the World that I’m coming&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Diddy]&lt;br&gt; Back where I belong, yeah I never felt so strong&lt;br&gt; (I’m back baby)&lt;br&gt; I feel like there’s nothing that I can’t try&lt;br&gt; and if you with me put your hands high&lt;br&gt; (put your hands high)&lt;br&gt; If you ever lost a light before, this ones for you&lt;br&gt; and you, the dreams are for you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I hear “The Tears of a Clown”&lt;br&gt; I hate that song&lt;br&gt; I feel like they talking to me when it comes on&lt;br&gt; another day another Dawn&lt;br&gt; another Keisha, nice to meet ya, get the math I’m gone&lt;br&gt; what am I ‘posed to do when the club lights come on&lt;br&gt; its easy to be Puff, its harder to be Sean&lt;br&gt; what if the twins ask why I aint marry their mom (why, damn!)&lt;br&gt; how do I respond?&lt;br&gt; what if my son stares with a face like my own&lt;br&gt; and says he wants to be like me when he’s grown&lt;br&gt; sh-t! But I aint finished growing&lt;br&gt; another night the inevitible prolongs&lt;br&gt; another day another Dawn&lt;br&gt; just tell Taneka and Taresha I’ll be better in the morn’&lt;br&gt; another lie that I carry on&lt;br&gt; I need to get back to the place I belong&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Dirty Money - Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Diddy - Verse 2]&lt;br&gt; “A house is Not a Home“, I hate this song&lt;br&gt; is a house really a home when your loved ones are gone&lt;br&gt; and n-ggas got the nerve to blame you for it&lt;br&gt; and you know you woulda took the bullet if you saw it&lt;br&gt; but oyu felt it and still feel it&lt;br&gt; and money can’t make up for it or conceal it&lt;br&gt; but you deal with it and you keep ballin’&lt;br&gt; pour out some liquor, play ball and we keep ballin’&lt;br&gt; baby we’ve been living in sin ’cause we’ve been really in love&lt;br&gt; but we’ve been living as friends&lt;br&gt; so you’ve been a guest in your own home&lt;br&gt; it’s time to make your house your home&lt;br&gt; pick up your phone, come on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Dirty Money - Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Diddy - Verse 3]&lt;br&gt; “Ain’t No Stopping Us Now“, I love that song&lt;br&gt; whenever it comes on it makes me feel strong&lt;br&gt; I thought I told y’all that we won’t stop&lt;br&gt; we back cruising through Harlem, Viso blocks&lt;br&gt; it’s what made me, saved me, drove me crazy&lt;br&gt; drove me away than embraced me&lt;br&gt; forgave me for all of my shortcomings&lt;br&gt; welcome to my homecoming&lt;br&gt; yeah it’s been a long time coming&lt;br&gt; lot of fights, lot of scars, lot of bottles&lt;br&gt; lot of cars, lot of ups, lot of downs&lt;br&gt; made it back, lost my dog (I miss you BIG)&lt;br&gt; and here I stand, a better man! (a better man)&lt;br&gt; Thank you Lord (Thank you Lord)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Dirty Money - Chorus]&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
