<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Wake Up Call</Title>
    <Artist>Maroon 5</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/e/1/e1b9354eb2baf21f844023e5c526b479_1406601346.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Wake Up Call&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Maroon 5&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMjIlMkZjJTJGNSUyRmM1NjIwZTc4NzU5MjIxY2E2NmY5N2M3MmM0M2UzYWI1Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Verse]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I didn't hear what you were saying.&lt;br&gt; I live on raw emotion baby&lt;br&gt; I answer questions never maybe&lt;br&gt; And I'm not kind if you betray me.&lt;br&gt; So who the hell are you to say we&lt;br&gt; Never would have made it babe.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If you needed love&lt;br&gt; Well then ask for love&lt;br&gt; Could have given love&lt;br&gt; Now I’m taking love&lt;br&gt; And it’s not my fault&lt;br&gt; Cause you both deserve&lt;br&gt; What is coming now&lt;br&gt; So don’t say a word&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wake up call&lt;br&gt; Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed&lt;br&gt; Don't you care about me anymore?&lt;br&gt; Don’t you care about me? I don't think so.&lt;br&gt; Six foot tall&lt;br&gt; Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead&lt;br&gt; He won't come around here anymore&lt;br&gt; Come around here? I don't think so.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Breakdown]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Would have bled to make you happy&lt;br&gt; You didn't need to treat me that way&lt;br&gt; And now you beat me at my own game&lt;br&gt; And now I find you sleeping soundly&lt;br&gt; And your lovers screaming loudly&lt;br&gt; Hear a sound and hit the ground&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If you needed love&lt;br&gt; Well then ask for love&lt;br&gt; Could have given love&lt;br&gt; Now I’m taking love&lt;br&gt; And it’s not my fault&lt;br&gt; Cause you both deserve&lt;br&gt; What’s coming now&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So don’t say a word&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wake up call&lt;br&gt; Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed&lt;br&gt; Don't you care about me anymore?&lt;br&gt; Don’t you care about me? I don't think so.&lt;br&gt; Six foot tall&lt;br&gt; Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead&lt;br&gt; He won't come around here anymore&lt;br&gt; Come around here?&lt;br&gt; I don’t feel so bad, I don’t feel so bad, I don’t feel so bad&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Breakdown]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm so sorry darling&lt;br&gt; Did I do the wrong thing?&lt;br&gt; Oh, what was I thinking?&lt;br&gt; Is his heart still beating?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Woah oh ohh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wake up call&lt;br&gt; Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed&lt;br&gt; Don't you care about me anymore?&lt;br&gt; Don’t you care about me? I don't think so.&lt;br&gt; Six foot tall&lt;br&gt; Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead&lt;br&gt; He won't come around here anymore&lt;br&gt; Come around here anymore? I don’t feel so bad&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Wake up call&lt;br&gt; Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed&lt;br&gt; Don’t you care about me anymore?&lt;br&gt; Don’t you care about me? I don’t think so.&lt;br&gt; Six foot tall&lt;br&gt; Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead&lt;br&gt; He won’t come around here anymore&lt;br&gt; No, he won’t come around here. I don’t feel so bad&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I don’t feel so bad (Wake up call)&lt;br&gt; I don’t feel so bad (Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed)&lt;br&gt; I don’t feel so bad (Don’t you care about me anymore?)&lt;br&gt; Care about me? I don’t feel so bad.&lt;br&gt; Wake up call&lt;br&gt; Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed&lt;br&gt; Don't you care about me anymore?</Lyrics>
</Song>
