<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Baby</Title>
    <Artist>Justin Bieber ft. Ludacris</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/b/8/b8903886038c34761df8dc86d3d951ba_1366022708.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Baby&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Justin Bieber,Ludacris&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjExJTJGMTMlMkY2JTJGNSUyRjY1MjViYTIyZjNhYWNhNTAyMDRhMTBjYWJlMjJmOTU4Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Baby&quot;&lt;br&gt; (feat. Ludacris)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ohh wooaah [x3]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You know you love me, I know you care&lt;br&gt; Just shout whenever, and I'll be there&lt;br&gt; You want my love, you want my heart&lt;br&gt; And we will never ever ever be apart&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Are we an item? Girl quit playing&lt;br&gt; We're just friends, what are you saying&lt;br&gt; Say there's another and look right in my eyes&lt;br&gt; My first love broke my heart for the first time&lt;br&gt; And I was like...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby nooo&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; I thought you'd always be mine (mine)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby nooo&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; I thought you'd always be mine (mine)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; For you, I would have done whatever&lt;br&gt; And I just can't believe we ain't together&lt;br&gt; And I wanna play it cool, but I'm losin' you&lt;br&gt; I'll buy you anything, I'll buy you any ring&lt;br&gt; And I'm in pieces, baby fix me&lt;br&gt; And just shake me til' you wake me from this bad dream&lt;br&gt; I'm going down, down, down, down&lt;br&gt; And I just can't believe my first love won't be around&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And I'm like&lt;br&gt; Baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby nooo&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; I thought you'd always be mine (mine)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby nooo&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; I thought you'd always be mine (mine)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Ludacris:]&lt;br&gt; Luda! When I was 13, I had my first love,&lt;br&gt; There was nobody that compared to my baby&lt;br&gt; and nobody came between us, or could ever come above&lt;br&gt; She had me going crazy, oh I was star-struck,&lt;br&gt; she woke me up daily, don’t need no Starbucks.&lt;br&gt; She made my heart pound, I skip a beat when I see her in the street and&lt;br&gt; at school on the playground but I really wanna see her on the weekend.&lt;br&gt; She knows she got me dazing coz she was so amazing&lt;br&gt; and now my heart is breaking but I just keep on saying...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby nooo&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; I thought you'd always be mine (mine)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby nooo&lt;br&gt; Like baby, baby, baby oooh&lt;br&gt; I thought you'd always be mine (mine)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm gone (Yeah Yeah Yeah, Yeah Yeah Yeah)&lt;br&gt; All I'm gone (Yeah Yeah Yeah, Yeah Yeah Yeah)&lt;br&gt; Now I'm all gone (Yeah Yeah Yeah, Yeah Yeah Yeah)&lt;br&gt; Now I'm all gone (gone, gone, gone...)&lt;br&gt; I'm gone</Lyrics>
</Song>
