<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Love The Way You Lie</Title>
    <Artist>Eminem ft. Rihanna</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/0/a0538a67982e1ef3e3bd2922cb6dd9ce_1383013435.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Eminem , Rihanna&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjExJTJGMTIlMkYwJTJGYiUyRjBiMDMxZTZhYjdkNDNlOTc5OGE1NDA2ZGRlZDA5MmRjLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&quot;Love The Way You Lie&quot;&lt;br&gt; (feat. Rihanna)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Rihanna:]&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and watch me burn&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I like the way it hurts&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and hear me cry&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Eminem]&lt;br&gt; I can't tell you what it really is&lt;br&gt; I can only tell you what it feels like&lt;br&gt; And right now it's a steel knife in my windpipe&lt;br&gt; I can't breathe but I still fight while I can fight&lt;br&gt; As long as the wrong feels right it's like I'm in flight&lt;br&gt; High off of love, drunk from my hate,&lt;br&gt; It's like I'm huffing pain and I love it the more I suffer, I suffocate&lt;br&gt; And right before I'm about to drown, she resuscitates me&lt;br&gt; She fucking hates me and I love it.&lt;br&gt; Wait! Where you going?&lt;br&gt; &quot;I'm leaving you&quot;&lt;br&gt; No you ain't. Come back we're running right back.&lt;br&gt; Here we go again&lt;br&gt; It's so insane cause when it's going good, it's going great&lt;br&gt; I'm Superman with the wind at his back, she's Lois Lane&lt;br&gt; But when it's bad it's awful, I feel so ashamed I snapped&lt;br&gt; Who's that dude? I don't even know his name&lt;br&gt; I laid hands on her, I'll never stoop so low again&lt;br&gt; I guess I don't know my own strength&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Rihanna:]&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and watch me burn&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I like the way it hurts&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and hear me cry&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Eminem]&lt;br&gt; You ever love somebody so much you can barely breathe&lt;br&gt; When you're with 'em&lt;br&gt; You meet and neither one of you even know what hit 'em&lt;br&gt; Got that warm fuzzy feeling&lt;br&gt; Yeah, them chills you used to get 'em&lt;br&gt; Now you're getting fucking sick of looking at 'em&lt;br&gt; You swore you'd never hit 'em; never do nothing to hurt 'em&lt;br&gt; Now you're in each other's face spewing venom in your words when you spit them&lt;br&gt; You push pull each other's hair, scratch claw hit 'em&lt;br&gt; Throw 'em down pin 'em&lt;br&gt; So lost in the moments when you're in them&lt;br&gt; It's the rage that took over it controls you both&lt;br&gt; So they say you're best to go your separate ways&lt;br&gt; Guess if they don't know you 'cause today that was yesterday&lt;br&gt; Yesterday is over, it's a different day&lt;br&gt; Sound like broken records playing over but you promised her&lt;br&gt; Next time you show restraint&lt;br&gt; You don't get another chance&lt;br&gt; Life is no Nintendo game&lt;br&gt; But you lied again&lt;br&gt; Now you get to watch her leave out the window&lt;br&gt; Guess that's why they call it window pane&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Rihanna:]&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and watch me burn&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I like the way it hurts&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and hear me cry&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Eminem]&lt;br&gt; Now I know we said things, did things that we didn't mean&lt;br&gt; And we fall back into the same patterns, same routine&lt;br&gt; But your temper's just as bad as mine is&lt;br&gt; You're the same as me&lt;br&gt; But when it comes to love you're just as blinded&lt;br&gt; Baby, please come back&lt;br&gt; It wasn't you, baby it was me&lt;br&gt; Maybe our relationship isn't as crazy as it seems&lt;br&gt; Maybe that's what happens when a tornado meets a volcano&lt;br&gt; All I know is I love you too much to walk away though&lt;br&gt; Come inside, pick up your bags off the sidewalk&lt;br&gt; Don't you hear sincerity in my voice when I talk&lt;br&gt; I told you this is my fault&lt;br&gt; Look me in the eyeball&lt;br&gt; Next time I'm pissed, I'll aim my fist at the drywall&lt;br&gt; Next time. There won't be no next time&lt;br&gt; I apologize even though I know its lies&lt;br&gt; I'm tired of the games I just want her back&lt;br&gt; I know I'm a liar&lt;br&gt; If she ever tries to fucking leave again&lt;br&gt; Im'a tie her to the bed and set this house on fire&lt;br&gt; I'm just gonna&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus - Rihanna:]&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and watch me burn&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I like the way it hurts&lt;br&gt; Just gonna stand there and hear me cry&lt;br&gt; But that's alright because I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; I love the way you lie&lt;br&gt; I love the way you lie</Lyrics>
</Song>
