<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>All I Want For Christmas Is You</Title>
    <Artist>Mariah Carey</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/e/5e9228a226baf71430428de40b220cc3_1400574169.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;All I Want For Christmas Is You&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Mariah Carey&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjAyJTJGMjIlMkY3JTJGMSUyRjcxZGJkN2NlZWVlMTNjMDRjODZhMzliM2RlYzcxYmQ2Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I don't want a lot for Christmas&lt;br&gt; There is just one thing I need&lt;br&gt; I don't care about the presents&lt;br&gt; Underneath the Christmas tree&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I just want you for my own&lt;br&gt; More than you could ever know&lt;br&gt; Make my wish come true&lt;br&gt; All I want for Christmas&lt;br&gt; Is you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I don't want a lot for Christmas&lt;br&gt; There is just one thing I need&lt;br&gt; And I don't care about the presents&lt;br&gt; Underneath the Christmas tree&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I don't need to hang my stocking&lt;br&gt; There upon the fireplace&lt;br&gt; Santa Claus won't make me happy&lt;br&gt; With a toy on Christmas Day&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I just want you for my own&lt;br&gt; More than you could ever know&lt;br&gt; Make my wish come true&lt;br&gt; All I want for Christmas is you&lt;br&gt; You baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh I won't ask for much this Christmas&lt;br&gt; I won't even wish for snow&lt;br&gt; And I'm just gonna keep on waiting&lt;br&gt; Underneath the mistletoe&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I won't make a list and send it&lt;br&gt; To the North Pole for Saint Nick&lt;br&gt; I won't even stay awake to&lt;br&gt; Hear those magic reindeer click&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'Cause I just want you here tonight&lt;br&gt; Holding on to me so tight&lt;br&gt; What more can I do?&lt;br&gt; Baby all I want for Christmas is you&lt;br&gt; You&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh all the lights are shining&lt;br&gt; So brightly everywhere&lt;br&gt; And the sound of children's&lt;br&gt; Laughter fills the air&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And everyone is singing&lt;br&gt; I hear those sleigh bells ringing&lt;br&gt; Santa won't you bring me the one I really need?&lt;br&gt; Won't you please bring my baby to me?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh I don't want a lot for Christmas&lt;br&gt; This is all I'm asking for&lt;br&gt; I just want to see my baby&lt;br&gt; Standing right outside my door&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh I just want you for my own&lt;br&gt; More than you could ever know&lt;br&gt; Make my wish come true&lt;br&gt; Baby all I want for Christmas is&lt;br&gt; You baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; All I want for Christmas is you baby&lt;br&gt; All I want for Christmas is you baby&lt;br&gt; All I want for Christmas is you baby&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
