<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>My Humps</Title>
    <Artist>The Black Eyed Peas</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/9/6/9615bfb6fc13a2c7973300f3c257254d_1334551926.png</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;My Humps&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;The Black Eyed Peas&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMjIlMkYwJTJGMyUyRjAzZDM0ODFlMmQ3NzQ3YjY4NmUwMDNkNmY5NTk5MzhhLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>What you gon' do with all that junk?&lt;br&gt; All that junk inside your trunk?&lt;br&gt; I'ma get, get, get, get, you drunk,&lt;br&gt; Get you love drunk off my hump.&lt;br&gt; My hump, my hump, my hump, my hump, my hump,&lt;br&gt; My hump, my hump, my hump, my lovely little lumps (Check it out)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I drive these brothers crazy,&lt;br&gt; I do it on the daily,&lt;br&gt; They treat me really nicely,&lt;br&gt; They buy me all these ices.&lt;br&gt; Dolce &amp;amp; Gabbana,&lt;br&gt; Fendi and that Donna&lt;br&gt; Karan, they be sharin'&lt;br&gt; All their money got me wearin' fly&lt;br&gt; Brother I ain't askin,&lt;br&gt; They say they love my ass ‘n,&lt;br&gt; Seven Jeans, True Religion's,&lt;br&gt; I say no, but they keep givin'&lt;br&gt; So I keep on takin'&lt;br&gt; And no I ain't taken&lt;br&gt; We can keep on datin'&lt;br&gt; I keep on demonstrating.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My love (love), my love, my love, my love (love)&lt;br&gt; You love my lady lumps (love),&lt;br&gt; My hump, my hump, my hump (love),&lt;br&gt; My humps they got you,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; She's got me spending.&lt;br&gt; (Oh) Spendin' all your money on me and spending time on me.&lt;br&gt; She's got me spendin'.&lt;br&gt; (Oh) Spendin' all your money on me, up on me, on me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What you gon' do with all that junk?&lt;br&gt; All that junk inside that trunk?&lt;br&gt; I'ma get, get, get, get, you drunk,&lt;br&gt; Get you love drunk off my hump.&lt;br&gt; What you gon' do with all that ass?&lt;br&gt; All that ass inside them jeans?&lt;br&gt; I'm a make, make, make, make you scream&lt;br&gt; Make you scream, make you scream.&lt;br&gt; Cos of my hump (ha), my hump, my hump, my hump (what).&lt;br&gt; My hump, my hump, my hump (ha), my lovely lady lumps (Check it out)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I met a girl down at the disco.&lt;br&gt; She said hey, hey, hey yea let's go.&lt;br&gt; I could be your baby, you can be my honey&lt;br&gt; Let's spend time not money.&lt;br&gt; I mix your milk wit my cocoa puff,&lt;br&gt; Milky, milky cocoa,&lt;br&gt; Mix your milk with my cocoa puff, milky, milky riiiiiiight.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; They say I'm really sexy,&lt;br&gt; The boys they wanna sex me.&lt;br&gt; They always standing next to me,&lt;br&gt; Always dancing next to me,&lt;br&gt; Tryin' a feel my hump, hump.&lt;br&gt; Lookin' at my lump, lump.&lt;br&gt; You can look but you can't touch it,&lt;br&gt; If you touch it I'ma start some drama,&lt;br&gt; You don't want no drama,&lt;br&gt; No, no drama, no, no, no, no drama&lt;br&gt; So don't pull on my hand boy,&lt;br&gt; You ain't my man, boy,&lt;br&gt; I'm just tryn'a dance boy,&lt;br&gt; And move my hump.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; My hump, my hump, my hump, my hump,&lt;br&gt; My hump, my hump, my hump, my hump, my hump, my hump.&lt;br&gt; My lovely lady lumps (lumps)&lt;br&gt; My lovely lady lumps (lumps)&lt;br&gt; My lovely lady lumps (lumps)&lt;br&gt; In the back and in the front (lumps)&lt;br&gt; My lovin' got you,&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; She's got me spendin'.&lt;br&gt; (Oh) Spendin' all your money on me and spending time on me.&lt;br&gt; She's got me spendin'.&lt;br&gt; (Oh) Spendin' all your money on me, up on me, on me.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What you gon' do with all that junk?&lt;br&gt; All that junk inside that trunk?&lt;br&gt; I'ma get, get, get, get you drunk,&lt;br&gt; Get you love drunk off my hump.&lt;br&gt; What you gon' do with all that ass?&lt;br&gt; All that ass inside them jeans?&lt;br&gt; I'ma make, make, make, make you scream&lt;br&gt; Make you scream, make you scream.&lt;br&gt; What you gon' do with all that junk?&lt;br&gt; All that junk inside that trunk?&lt;br&gt; I'ma get, get, get, get you drunk,&lt;br&gt; Get you love drunk off this hump.&lt;br&gt; What you gon' do wit all that breast?&lt;br&gt; All that breast inside that shirt?&lt;br&gt; I'ma make, make, make, make you work&lt;br&gt; Make you work, work, make you work.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (A-ha, a-ha, a-ha, a-ha) [x4]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; She's got me spendin'.&lt;br&gt; (Oh) Spendin' all your money on me and spendin' time on me&lt;br&gt; She's got me spendin'.&lt;br&gt; (Oh) Spendin' all your money on me, up on me, on me.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Will.i.am]&lt;br&gt; So real [x17]&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
