<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Your Love Is A Lie</Title>
    <Artist>Simple Plan</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/2/b/2bf896c2555b981def5f369cba04b723_1305000735.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Your Love Is A Lie&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Simple Plan&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMjMlMkY3JTJGMSUyRjcxYzMxYzI2NzY0MTdkODk5ZDYyMWY5NGFjOTZhMWNkLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I fall asleep by the telephone&lt;br&gt; It's 2 O'clock and I'm waiting up alone&lt;br&gt; Tell me where have you been?&lt;br&gt; I found a note with another name&lt;br&gt; You blow a kiss, but it just don't feel the same&lt;br&gt; Cause I can feel that you're gone&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can't bite my tongue forever&lt;br&gt; While you try to play it cool&lt;br&gt; You can hide behind your stories&lt;br&gt; But don't take me for a fool&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can tell me that there's nobody else&lt;br&gt; (But I feel it)&lt;br&gt; You can tell me that you're home by yourself&lt;br&gt; (But I see it)&lt;br&gt; You can look into my eyes and pretend all you want&lt;br&gt; But I know&lt;br&gt; Your love is just a lie&lt;br&gt; (Lie)&lt;br&gt; It's nothing but a lie&lt;br&gt; (Lie)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You look so innocent&lt;br&gt; But the guilt in your voice gives you away&lt;br&gt; Yeah you know what I mean&lt;br&gt; How does it feel when you kiss when you know that i trust you&lt;br&gt; And do you think about me when he fucks you?&lt;br&gt; Could you be more obscene?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So don't try to say you're sorry&lt;br&gt; Or try to make it right&lt;br&gt; Don't waste your breath because it's too late, it's too late.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can tell me that there's nobody else&lt;br&gt; (But I feel it)&lt;br&gt; You can tell me that you're home by yourself&lt;br&gt; (But I see it)&lt;br&gt; You can look into my eyes and pretend all you want&lt;br&gt; But I know, I know,&lt;br&gt; Your love is just a lie&lt;br&gt; (Lie)&lt;br&gt; It's nothing but a lie&lt;br&gt; (Lie)&lt;br&gt; You're nothing but a lie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can tell me that there's nobody else&lt;br&gt; (But I feel it)&lt;br&gt; You can tell me that you're home by yourself&lt;br&gt; (But I see it)&lt;br&gt; You can look into my eyes and pretend all you want&lt;br&gt; But I know, I know&lt;br&gt; Your love is just a lie&lt;br&gt; (Lie)&lt;br&gt; I know you're nothing but a lie&lt;br&gt; (Lie)&lt;br&gt; Lie&lt;br&gt; (Lie)&lt;br&gt; Lie&lt;br&gt; You're nothing but a lie&lt;br&gt; Lie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Your love is just a lie&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
