<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>We Belong Together</Title>
    <Artist>Mariah Carey</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/e/5e9228a226baf71430428de40b220cc3_1400574169.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;We Belong Together&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Mariah Carey&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjAyJTJGMjIlMkYxJTJGYiUyRjFiZTZjMDgxOGM3NTA0ZGFkNTkzM2RjYmM5MmZkMmI4Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I didn't mean it&lt;br&gt; When I said I didn't love you so&lt;br&gt; I should have held on tight&lt;br&gt; I never should've let you go&lt;br&gt; I didn't know nothing&lt;br&gt; I was stupid&lt;br&gt; I was foolish&lt;br&gt; I was lying to myself&lt;br&gt; I couldn't have fathomed that I would ever&lt;br&gt; Be without your love&lt;br&gt; Never imagined I'd be&lt;br&gt; Sitting here beside myself&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; 'Guess I didn't know you&lt;br&gt; 'Guess I didn't know me&lt;br&gt; But I thought I knew everything&lt;br&gt; I never felt&lt;br&gt; The feeling that I'm feeling&lt;br&gt; Now that I don't&lt;br&gt; Hear your voice&lt;br&gt; Or have your touch and kiss your lips&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I don't have a choice&lt;br&gt; Oh, what I wouldn't give&lt;br&gt; To have you lying by my side&lt;br&gt; Right here, 'cause baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus:]&lt;br&gt; When you left&lt;br&gt; I lost a part of me&lt;br&gt; It's still so hard to believe&lt;br&gt; Come back baby please, 'cause&lt;br&gt; We belong together&lt;br&gt; Who else am I gonna lean on&lt;br&gt; When times get rough?&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna talk to me on the phone&lt;br&gt; Till the sun comes up?&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna take your place?&lt;br&gt; There ain't nobody better&lt;br&gt; Oh baby, baby&lt;br&gt; We belong together&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I can't sleep at night&lt;br&gt; When you are on my mind&lt;br&gt; Bobby Womack's on the radio&lt;br&gt; Singing to me&lt;br&gt; 'If you think you're lonely now'&lt;br&gt; Wait a minute&lt;br&gt; This is too deep, too deep&lt;br&gt; I gotta change the station&lt;br&gt; So I turn the dial&lt;br&gt; Trying to catch a break&lt;br&gt; And then I hear Babyface&lt;br&gt; I only think of you&lt;br&gt; And it's breaking my heart&lt;br&gt; I'm trying to keep it together&lt;br&gt; But I'm falling apart&lt;br&gt; I'm feeling all out of my element&lt;br&gt; I'm throwing things&lt;br&gt; Crying&lt;br&gt; Trying to figure out&lt;br&gt; Where the hell I went wrong&lt;br&gt; The pain reflected in this song&lt;br&gt; Ain't even half of what&lt;br&gt; I'm feeling inside&lt;br&gt; I need you&lt;br&gt; Need you back in my life (in my life, in my life), baby&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Repeat chorus]&lt;br&gt; When you left&lt;br&gt; I lost a part of me&lt;br&gt; It's still so hard to believe&lt;br&gt; Come back, baby, please, 'cause&lt;br&gt; We belong together&lt;br&gt; Who am I gonna lean on&lt;br&gt; When times get rough?&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna talk to me&lt;br&gt; Till the sun comes up?&lt;br&gt; Who's gonna take your place?&lt;br&gt; There ain't nobody better.&lt;br&gt; Oh baby, baby&lt;br&gt; We belong together&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
