<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Where Is The Love?</Title>
    <Artist>The Black Eyed Peas</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/9/6/9615bfb6fc13a2c7973300f3c257254d_1334551926.png</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Where Is The Love?&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;The Black Eyed Peas&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMjIlMkYwJTJGNyUyRjA3YWNlZDMzMDJmMWZhNmM1ZGMwMDUzYTlhMDYyYjcxLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>What's wrong with the world, mama&lt;br&gt; People livin' like they ain't got no mamas&lt;br&gt; I think the whole world addicted to the drama&lt;br&gt; Only attracted to things that'll bring you trauma&lt;br&gt; Overseas, yeah, we try to stop terrorism&lt;br&gt; But we still got terrorists here livin'&lt;br&gt; In the USA, the big CIA&lt;br&gt; The Bloods and The Crips and the KKK&lt;br&gt; But if you only have love for your own race&lt;br&gt; Then you only leave space to discriminate&lt;br&gt; And to discriminate only generates hate&lt;br&gt; And when you hate then you're bound to get irate, yeah&lt;br&gt; Madness is what you demonstrate&lt;br&gt; And that's exactly how anger works and operates&lt;br&gt; Man, you gotta have love just to set it straight&lt;br&gt; Take control of your mind and meditate&lt;br&gt; Let your soul gravitate to the love, y'all, y'all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; People killin', people dyin'&lt;br&gt; Children hurt and you hear them cryin'&lt;br&gt; Can you practice what you preach&lt;br&gt; And would you turn the other cheek&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Father, Father, Father help us&lt;br&gt; Send some guidance from above&lt;br&gt; 'Cause people got me, got me questionin'&lt;br&gt; Where is the love (Love)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Where is the love (The love)&lt;br&gt; Where is the love (The love)&lt;br&gt; Where is the love&lt;br&gt; The love, the love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It just ain't the same, always unchanged&lt;br&gt; New days are strange, is the world insane&lt;br&gt; If love and peace is so strong&lt;br&gt; Why are there pieces of love that don't belong&lt;br&gt; Nations droppin' bombs&lt;br&gt; Chemical gasses fillin' lungs of little ones&lt;br&gt; With ongoin' sufferin' as the youth die young&lt;br&gt; So ask yourself is the lovin' really gone&lt;br&gt; So I could ask myself really what is goin' wrong&lt;br&gt; In this world that we livin' in people keep on givin'&lt;br&gt; in&lt;br&gt; Makin' wrong decisions, only visions of them dividends&lt;br&gt; Not respectin' each other, deny thy brother&lt;br&gt; A war is goin' on but the reason's undercover&lt;br&gt; The truth is kept secret, it's swept under the rug&lt;br&gt; If you never know truth then you never know love&lt;br&gt; Where's the love, y'all, come on (I don't know)&lt;br&gt; Where's the truth, y'all, come on (I don't know)&lt;br&gt; Where's the love, y'all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; People killin', people dyin'&lt;br&gt; Children hurt and you hear them cryin'&lt;br&gt; Can you practice what you preach&lt;br&gt; And would you turn the other cheek&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Father, Father, Father help us&lt;br&gt; Send some guidance from above&lt;br&gt; 'Cause people got me, got me questionin'&lt;br&gt; Where is the love (Love)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Where is the love (The love)&lt;br&gt; Where is the love (The love)&lt;br&gt; Where is the love (The love)&lt;br&gt; Where is the love (The love)&lt;br&gt; Where is the love, the love, the love?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I feel the weight of the world on my shoulder&lt;br&gt; As I'm gettin' older, y'all, people gets colder&lt;br&gt; Most of us only care about money makin'&lt;br&gt; Selfishness got us followin' our wrong direction&lt;br&gt; Wrong information always shown by the media&lt;br&gt; Negative images is the main criteria&lt;br&gt; Infecting the young minds faster than bacteria&lt;br&gt; Kids wanna act like what they see in the cinema&lt;br&gt; Yo', whatever happened to the values of humanity&lt;br&gt; Whatever happened to the fairness in equality&lt;br&gt; Instead of spreading love we're spreading animosity&lt;br&gt; Lack of understanding, leading lives away from unity&lt;br&gt; That's the reason why sometimes I'm feelin' under&lt;br&gt; That's the reason why sometimes I'm feelin' down&lt;br&gt; There's no wonder why sometimes I'm feelin' under&lt;br&gt; Gotta keep my faith alive till love is found&lt;br&gt; Now ask yourself&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Where is the love?&lt;br&gt; Where is the love?&lt;br&gt; Where is the love?&lt;br&gt; Where is the love?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Father, Father, Father help us&lt;br&gt; Send some guidance from above&lt;br&gt; 'Cause people got me, got me questionin'&lt;br&gt; Where is the love?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Sing wit me y'all:&lt;br&gt; One world, one world (We only got)&lt;br&gt; One world, one world (That's all we got)&lt;br&gt; One world, one world&lt;br&gt; And something's wrong wit it (Yeah)&lt;br&gt; Something's wrong wit it (Yeah)&lt;br&gt; Something's wrong wit the wo-wo-world, yeah&lt;br&gt; We only got&lt;br&gt; (One world, one world)&lt;br&gt; That's all we got&lt;br&gt; (One world, one world)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
