<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Smooth Criminal</Title>
    <Artist>Michael Jackson</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/7/a7f3d5a06940bf15e6b44a788fee7123_1341065342.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Smooth Criminal&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Michael Jackson&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjExJTJGMTIlMkY0JTJGOCUyRjQ4OTdkZDIzMWVjYTYyZmY1MTEyMzBlOTYzOWQxNzI3Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>As He Came Into The Window&lt;br&gt; It Was The Sound Of A Crescendo&lt;br&gt; He Came Into Her Apartment&lt;br&gt; He Left The Bloodstains On The Carpet&lt;br&gt; She Ran Underneath The Table&lt;br&gt; He Could See She Was Unable&lt;br&gt; So She Ran Into The Bedroom&lt;br&gt; She Was Struck Down, It Was Her Doom&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok, Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok, Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok, Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok, Are You Ok, Annie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (Annie Are You Ok)&lt;br&gt; (Will You Tell Us That You're Ok)&lt;br&gt; (There's A Sign In The Window)&lt;br&gt; (That He Struck You-A Crescendo Annie)&lt;br&gt; (He Came Into Your Apartment)&lt;br&gt; (He Left The Bloodstains On The Carpet)&lt;br&gt; (Then You Ran Into The Bedroom)&lt;br&gt; (You Were Struck Down)&lt;br&gt; (It Was Your Doom)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok Annie&lt;br&gt; You've Been Hit By&lt;br&gt; You've Been Hit By-&lt;br&gt; A Smooth Criminal&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So They Came Into The Outway&lt;br&gt; It Was Sunday-What A Black Day&lt;br&gt; Mouth To Mouth Resus-Citation&lt;br&gt; Sounding Heartbeats-Intimidations&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok Annie&lt;br&gt; Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; So, Annie Are You Ok&lt;br&gt; Are You Ok Annie&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (Annie Are You Ok)&lt;br&gt; (Will You Tell Us That You're Ok)&lt;br&gt; (There's A Sign In The Window)&lt;br&gt; (That He Struck You-A Crescendo Annie)&lt;br&gt; (He Came Into Your Apartment)&lt;br&gt; (He Left The Bloodstains On The Carpet)&lt;br&gt; (Then You Ran Into The Bedroom)&lt;br&gt; (You Were Struck Down)&lt;br&gt; (It Was Your Doom)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (Annie Are You Ok)&lt;br&gt; (So, Annie Are You Ok)&lt;br&gt; (Are You Ok Annie)&lt;br&gt; (You've Been Hit By)&lt;br&gt; (You've Been Struck By-&lt;br&gt; Welcome to Yeucahat.com&lt;br&gt; A Smooth Criminal)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Okay, I Want Everybody&lt;br&gt; To Clear The Area Right Now!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Aaow!&lt;br&gt; (Annie Are You Ok)&lt;br&gt; I Don't Know!&lt;br&gt; (Will You Tell Us, That You're Ok)&lt;br&gt; I Don't Know!&lt;br&gt; (There's A Sign In The Window)&lt;br&gt; I Don't Know!&lt;br&gt; (That He Struck You-A Crescendo Annie)&lt;br&gt; I Don't Know!&lt;br&gt; (He Came Into Your Apartment)&lt;br&gt; I Don't Know!&lt;br&gt; (Left Bloodstains On The Carpet)&lt;br&gt; I Don't Know Why Baby!&lt;br&gt; (Then You Ran Into The Bedroom)&lt;br&gt; I Don't Know!&lt;br&gt; (You Were Struck Down)&lt;br&gt; (It Was Your Doom-Annie!)&lt;br&gt; (Annie Are You Ok)&lt;br&gt; Dad Gone It-Baby!&lt;br&gt; (Will You Tell Us, That You're Ok)&lt;br&gt; Dad Gone It-Baby!&lt;br&gt; (There's A Sign In The Window)&lt;br&gt; Dad Gone It-Baby!&lt;br&gt; (That He Struck You-A Crescendo Annie)&lt;br&gt; Hoo! Hoo!&lt;br&gt; (He Came Into Your Apartment)&lt;br&gt; Dad Gone It!&lt;br&gt; (Left Bloodstains On The Carpet)&lt;br&gt; Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!&lt;br&gt; (Then You Ran Into The Bedroom)&lt;br&gt; Dad Gone It!&lt;br&gt; (You Were Struck Down)&lt;br&gt; (It Was Your Doom-Annie!)&lt;br&gt; Aaow!!!</Lyrics>
</Song>
