<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Mockingbird</Title>
    <Artist>Eminem</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/0/a0538a67982e1ef3e3bd2922cb6dd9ce_1383013435.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Mockingbird&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Eminem&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjExJTJGMTQlMkZiJTJGZCUyRmJkZmQ2ZjJkMjEyZDI4NDA2MGQ5YzgzMjUxNDRlYjVlLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Yeah&lt;br&gt; I know sometimes things may not always make sense to you right now&lt;br&gt; But hey, what daddy always tell you?&lt;br&gt; Straighten up little soldier&lt;br&gt; Stiffen up that upper lip&lt;br&gt; What you crying about?&lt;br&gt; You got me&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hailie I know you miss your mom and I know you miss your dad&lt;br&gt; Well I'm gone but I'm trying to give you the life that I never had&lt;br&gt; I can see you're sad, even when you smile, even when you laugh&lt;br&gt; I can see it in your eyes, deep inside you want to cry&lt;br&gt; Cause you're scared, I ain't there?&lt;br&gt; Daddy's with you in your prayers&lt;br&gt; No more crying, wipe them tears&lt;br&gt; Daddy's here, no more nightmares&lt;br&gt; We gon' pull together through it, we gon' do it&lt;br&gt; Laney uncles crazy, ain't he?&lt;br&gt; Yeah but he loves you girl and you better know it&lt;br&gt; We're all we got in this world&lt;br&gt; When it spins, when it swirls&lt;br&gt; When it whirls, when it twirls&lt;br&gt; Two little beautiful girls&lt;br&gt; Lookin' puzzled, in a daze&lt;br&gt; I know it's confusing you&lt;br&gt; Daddy's always on the move, mamma's always on the news&lt;br&gt; I try to keep you sheltered from it but somehow it seems&lt;br&gt; The harder that I try to do that, the more it backfires on me&lt;br&gt; All the things growing up his daddy that he had to see&lt;br&gt; Daddy don't want you to see but you see just as much as he did&lt;br&gt; We did not plan it to be this way, your mother and me&lt;br&gt; But things have gotten so bad between us&lt;br&gt; I don't see us ever being together ever again&lt;br&gt; Like we used to be when we was teenagers&lt;br&gt; But then of course everything always happens for a reason&lt;br&gt; I guess it was never meant to be&lt;br&gt; But it's just something we have no control over and that's what destiny is&lt;br&gt; But no more worries, rest your head and go to sleep&lt;br&gt; Maybe one day we'll wake up and this will all just be a dream&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; Now hush little baby, don't you cry&lt;br&gt; Everything's gonna be alright&lt;br&gt; Stiffen that upper lip up little lady, I told ya&lt;br&gt; Daddy's here to hold ya through the night&lt;br&gt; I know mommy's not here right now and we don't know why&lt;br&gt; We feel how we feel inside&lt;br&gt; It may seem a little crazy, pretty baby&lt;br&gt; But I promise momma's gon' be alright&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's funny&lt;br&gt; I remember back one year when daddy had no money&lt;br&gt; Mommy wrapped the Christmas presents up&lt;br&gt; And stuck 'em under the tree and said some of 'em were from me&lt;br&gt; Cause daddy couldn't buy 'em&lt;br&gt; I'll never forget that Christmas I sat up the whole night crying&lt;br&gt; Cause daddy felt like a bum, see daddy had a job&lt;br&gt; But his job was to keep the food on the table for you and mom&lt;br&gt; And at the time every house that we lived in&lt;br&gt; Either kept getting broken into and robbed&lt;br&gt; Or shot up on the block and your mom was saving money for you in a jar&lt;br&gt; Tryna start a piggy bank for you so you could go to college&lt;br&gt; Almost had a thousand dollars till someone broke in and stole it&lt;br&gt; And I know it hurt so bad it broke your momma's heart&lt;br&gt; And it seemed like everything was just startin' to fall apart&lt;br&gt; Mom and dad was arguin' a lot so momma moved back&lt;br&gt; On the Chalmers in the flat one bedroom apartment&lt;br&gt; And dad moved back to the other side of 8 Mile on Novara&lt;br&gt; And that's when daddy went to California with his CD and met Dr. Dre&lt;br&gt; And flew you and momma out to see me&lt;br&gt; But daddy had to work, you and momma had to leave me&lt;br&gt; Then you started seeing daddy on the T.V. and momma didn't like it&lt;br&gt; And you and Laney were to young to understand it&lt;br&gt; Papa was a rollin' stone, momma developed a habit&lt;br&gt; And it all happened too fast for either one of us to grab it&lt;br&gt; I'm just sorry you were there and had to witness it first hand&lt;br&gt; Cause all I ever wanted to do was just make you proud&lt;br&gt; Now I'm sitting in this empty house, just reminiscing&lt;br&gt; Lookin' at your baby pictures, it just trips me out&lt;br&gt; To see how much you both have grown, it's almost like you're sisters now&lt;br&gt; Wow, guess you pretty much are and daddy's still here&lt;br&gt; Laney I'm talkin' to you too, daddy's still here&lt;br&gt; I like the sound of that, yeah&lt;br&gt; It's got a ring to it don't it?&lt;br&gt; Shh, momma's only gone for the moment&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And if you ask me too&lt;br&gt; Daddy's gonna buy you a mockingbird&lt;br&gt; I'mma give you the world&lt;br&gt; I'mma buy a diamond ring for you&lt;br&gt; I'mma sing for you&lt;br&gt; I'll do anything for you to see you smile&lt;br&gt; And if that mockingbird don't sing and that ring don't shine&lt;br&gt; I'mma break that birdies neck&lt;br&gt; I'll go back to the jeweler who sold it to ya&lt;br&gt; And make him eat every carat don't fuck with dad (haha)</Lyrics>
</Song>
