<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Dead And Gone</Title>
    <Artist>T.I. ft. Justin Timberlake</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/e/5e382bfdd6eb36b92a10f46fb465a8e1_1351440400.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Dead And Gone&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;T.I.,Justin Timberlake&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjAxJTJGMDElMkZmJTJGNSUyRmY1ZDgxMWU0MDhjMjNlMTkwZGVlZTk1ZTY2ZTU2NzA5Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>[Spoken - T.I.]&lt;br&gt; Ay&lt;br&gt; Let me kick it to you right quick, man&lt;br&gt; That on some gangsta shit man, on some real shit&lt;br&gt; Anybody done been through the same thing, I'm sure you feel the same way&lt;br&gt; Big Phil&lt;br&gt; This for you pimpin'&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (Justin Timberlake (T.I.)):]&lt;br&gt; Oh (eyyy)&lt;br&gt; I've been travellin' on this road too long (too long)&lt;br&gt; Just tryna find my way back home (back home)&lt;br&gt; The old me is dead and gone, dead and gone&lt;br&gt; And oh (eyyy)&lt;br&gt; I've been travellin' on this road too long (too long)&lt;br&gt; Just tryna find my way back home (back home)&lt;br&gt; The old me is dead and gone, dead and gone, dead and gone&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1 - T.I.]&lt;br&gt; Ever had one of them days wish would've stayed home&lt;br&gt; Run into a group of niggas who gettin' they hate on&lt;br&gt; You walk by&lt;br&gt; They get wrong&lt;br&gt; You reply then shit get blown&lt;br&gt; Way outta proportion&lt;br&gt; Way past discussion&lt;br&gt; Just you against them, pick one then rush 'em&lt;br&gt; Figure you'll get jumped, hell that's nothing&lt;br&gt; They don't wanna stop there now they bussin'&lt;br&gt; Now you gushin', ambulance rushin'&lt;br&gt; You to the hospital with a bad concussion&lt;br&gt; Plus ya hit 4 times&lt;br&gt; Plus it hit ya spine&lt;br&gt; Paralyzed waist down now ya wheel chair bound&lt;br&gt; Nevermind that now you lucky to be alive&lt;br&gt; Just think it all started you fussin' with 3 guys&lt;br&gt; Now ya pride in the way, but ya pride is the way&lt;br&gt; You could fuck around, get shot, die anyday&lt;br&gt; Niggas die everyday&lt;br&gt; All over bull shit, dope money, dice game, ordinary hood shit&lt;br&gt; Could this be 'cos of hip hop music?&lt;br&gt; Or did the ones with the good sense not use it?&lt;br&gt; Usually niggas don't know what to do when their back against the wall so they just start shootin'&lt;br&gt; For red or for blue or for blo I guess&lt;br&gt; From Bankhead or from your projects&lt;br&gt; No more stress, now I'm straight, now I get it, now I take&lt;br&gt; Time to think, before I make mistakes just for my family's sake&lt;br&gt; That part of me left yesterday&lt;br&gt; The heart of me is strong today&lt;br&gt; No regrets I'm blessed to say&lt;br&gt; The old me dead and gone away&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (Justin Timberlake (T.I.))]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2 - T.I.]&lt;br&gt; I ain't never been scared, I lived through tragedy&lt;br&gt; Situation could've been dead lookin' back at it&lt;br&gt; Most of that shit didn't even have to happen&lt;br&gt; But you don't think about it when you out there trappin'&lt;br&gt; In apartments, hangin', smokin', and rappin'&lt;br&gt; Niggas start shit, next thing ya know we cappin'&lt;br&gt; Get locked up then didn't even get mad&lt;br&gt; Now think about damn what a life I had&lt;br&gt; Most of that shit, look back, just laugh&lt;br&gt; Some shit still look back get sad&lt;br&gt; Maybe my homboy still be around&lt;br&gt; Had I not hit the nigga in the mouth that time&lt;br&gt; I won that fight&lt;br&gt; I lost that war&lt;br&gt; I can still see my nigga walkin' out that door&lt;br&gt; Who'da thought I'd never see Philant no more?&lt;br&gt; Got enough dead homies I don't want no more&lt;br&gt; Cost a nigga his job&lt;br&gt; Cost me more&lt;br&gt; I'd took that ass-whooping now for sure&lt;br&gt; Now think before I risk my life&lt;br&gt; Take them chances to get my stripe&lt;br&gt; A nigga put his hands on me alright&lt;br&gt; Otherwise stand there talk shit all night&lt;br&gt; 'Cos I hit you, you sue me,&lt;br&gt; I shoot you, get locked up, who me?&lt;br&gt; No more stress, now I'm straight, now I get it, now I take&lt;br&gt; Time to think, before I make mistakes just for my family's sake&lt;br&gt; That part of me left yesterday&lt;br&gt; The heart of me is strong today&lt;br&gt; No regrets I'm blessed to say&lt;br&gt; The old me dead and gone away&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (Justin Timberlake (T.I.))]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook - Justin Timberlake]&lt;br&gt; I turn my head to the East&lt;br&gt; I don't see nobody by my side&lt;br&gt; I turn my head to the West&lt;br&gt; Still nobody in sight&lt;br&gt; So I turn my head to the North&lt;br&gt; Swallow that pill that they call pride&lt;br&gt; That old me is dead and gone&lt;br&gt; But that new me will be alright&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I turn my head to the East&lt;br&gt; I don't see nobody by my side&lt;br&gt; I turn my head to the West&lt;br&gt; Still nobody in sight&lt;br&gt; So I turn my head to the North&lt;br&gt; Swallow that pill that they call pride&lt;br&gt; That old me is dead and gone&lt;br&gt; But that new me will be alright&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus (Justin Timberlake (T.I.))]</Lyrics>
</Song>
