<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Lonely</Title>
    <Artist>Akon</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/3/a3a04658e84dd182ba00d123e35c2f12_1384157159.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Lonely&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Akon&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjExJTJGMTclMkY2JTJGNyUyRjY3Yjg4M2U5MTg0ZmYxZDAxNzBlNmQ5MzMyNjhmNzZiLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Lonely lyrics&lt;br&gt; Songwriters: Allen, Gene; Vinton, Bobby; Thiam, Aliaune;&lt;br&gt; Lonely&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm so lonely&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; I'm so lonely&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yo, this one here&lt;br&gt; Goes out to all my playas out there, man, ya know&lt;br&gt; That got that one good girl, lord&lt;br&gt; That's always been there man like&lt;br&gt; Took all the bull****&lt;br&gt; And then one day she can't take it no more&lt;br&gt; And decide to leave&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yeah, I woke up in the middle of the night&lt;br&gt; And I noticed my girl wasn't by my side&lt;br&gt; Coulda sworn I was dreamin'&lt;br&gt; For her I was feenin'&lt;br&gt; So I had to take a little ride&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Backtracking on these few years&lt;br&gt; Tryna figure out what I do to make it go bad&lt;br&gt; Cuz ever since my girl left me&lt;br&gt; My whole life came crashin' an' I'm so&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own girl)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own girl)&lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Can't believe I had a girl like you&lt;br&gt; And I just let you walk right outta my life&lt;br&gt; After all I put you through you still&lt;br&gt; Stuck around and stayed by my side&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; What really hurt me is I broke your heart, baby&lt;br&gt; You a good girl and I had no right&lt;br&gt; I really wanna make things right&lt;br&gt; Cuz without you in my life girl I'm so&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own girl)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own girl)&lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Been all about the world ain't never met a girl&lt;br&gt; That can take the things that you been through&lt;br&gt; Never thought the day would come&lt;br&gt; Where you'd get up and run&lt;br&gt; And I would be out chasing you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Cuz ain't nowhere in the globe I'd rather be&lt;br&gt; Ain't no one in the globe I'd rather see&lt;br&gt; Than the girl of my dreams that made me be&lt;br&gt; So happy but now I'm so lonely&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own no)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own girl)&lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Never thought that I'd be alone&lt;br&gt; (Be alone)&lt;br&gt; I didn't think you'd be gone this long&lt;br&gt; (Gone so long)&lt;br&gt; I just want you to call my phone&lt;br&gt; So stop playing girl and come on home&lt;br&gt; (Come on home)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby girl I didn't mean to shout&lt;br&gt; I want me and you to work it out&lt;br&gt; (Work it out baby)&lt;br&gt; I never wished that I would hurt my baby&lt;br&gt; (Hurt my baby)&lt;br&gt; And it's drivin' me crazy cuz I'm so&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own no)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; I'm Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Mr. Lonely)&lt;br&gt; I have nobody&lt;br&gt; (I have nobody)&lt;br&gt; For my own&lt;br&gt; (To call my own girl)&lt;br&gt; I am so lonely&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So lonely&lt;br&gt; (Lonely)&lt;br&gt; So lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; Mr. Lonely&lt;br&gt; (Lonely)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; So lonely&lt;br&gt; (Lonely)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So lonely&lt;br&gt; (So lonely)&lt;br&gt; So lonely&lt;br&gt; Mr. Lonely</Lyrics>
</Song>
