<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Hurt</Title>
    <Artist>Christina Aguilera</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/f/c/fcdbe5da63126e344a254b5fc1dcdf96_1352258087.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Hurt&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Christina Aguilera&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjEyJTJGMDQlMkZiJTJGMCUyRmIwYzRhZTk4MmQwYzIzMjE2M2U1NGNhMDM4MzQzZDk1Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Seems like it was yesterday when I saw your face&lt;br&gt; You told me how proud you were but I walked away&lt;br&gt; If only I knew what I know today&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I would hold you in my arms&lt;br&gt; I would take the pain away&lt;br&gt; Thank you for all you've done&lt;br&gt; Forgive all your mistakes&lt;br&gt; There's nothing I wouldn't do&lt;br&gt; To hear your voice again&lt;br&gt; Sometimes I want to call you but I know you won't be there&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm sorry for blaming you for everything I just couldn't do&lt;br&gt; And I've hurt myself by hurting you&lt;br&gt; Some days I feel broke inside but I won't admit&lt;br&gt; Sometimes I just want to hide 'cause it's you I miss&lt;br&gt; You know it's so hard to say goodbye when it comes to this&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Would you tell me I was wrong?&lt;br&gt; Would you help me understand?&lt;br&gt; Are you looking down upon me?&lt;br&gt; Are you proud of who I am?&lt;br&gt; There's nothing I wouldn't do&lt;br&gt; To have just one more chance&lt;br&gt; To look into your eyes and see you looking back&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm sorry for blaming you for everything I just couldn't do&lt;br&gt; And I've hurt myself&lt;br&gt; If I had just one more day, I would tell you how much that&lt;br&gt; I've missed you since you've been away&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Oh, it's dangerous&lt;br&gt; It's so out of line to try to turn back time&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I'm sorry for blaming you for everything I just couldn't do&lt;br&gt; And I've hurt myself&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; By hurting you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
