<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>When I'm Gone.</Title>
    <Artist>Eminem</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/a/0/a0538a67982e1ef3e3bd2922cb6dd9ce_1383013435.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;When I'm Gone.&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Eminem&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMCUyRjExJTJGMTQlMkY2JTJGYyUyRjZjNmNkOGE2MmI5MjA1ZjI0NTUxMzcwNTJjMjA0MGI3Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&lt;br&gt; &quot;When I'm Gone&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Introduction]&lt;br&gt; Yeah...&lt;br&gt; It's my life...&lt;br&gt; My own words I guess...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 1]&lt;br&gt; Have you ever loved someone so much, you'd give an arm for?&lt;br&gt; Not the expression, no, literally give an arm for?&lt;br&gt; When they know they're your heart&lt;br&gt; And you know you were their armour&lt;br&gt; And you will destroy anyone who would try to harm 'her&lt;br&gt; But what happens when karma, turns right around and bites you?&lt;br&gt; And everything you stand for, turns on you to spite you?&lt;br&gt; What happens when you become the main source of her pain?&lt;br&gt; &quot;Daddy look what I made&quot;, Dad's gotta go catch a plane&lt;br&gt; &quot;Daddy where's Mommy? I can't find Mommy where is she?&quot;&lt;br&gt; I don't know go play Hailie, baby, your Daddy's busy&lt;br&gt; Daddy's writing a song, this song ain't gonna write itself&lt;br&gt; I'll give you one underdog then you gotta swing by yourself&lt;br&gt; Then turn right around in that song and tell her you love her&lt;br&gt; And put hands on her mother, who's a spitting image of her&lt;br&gt; That's Slim Shady, yeah baby, Slim Shady's crazy&lt;br&gt; Shady made me, but tonight Shady's rocka-by-baby...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; And when I'm gone, just carry on, don't mourn&lt;br&gt; Rejoice every time you hear the sound of my voice&lt;br&gt; Just know that I'm looking down on you smiling&lt;br&gt; And I didn't feel a thing, So baby don't feel my pain&lt;br&gt; Just smile back&lt;br&gt; And when I'm gone, just carry on, don't mourn&lt;br&gt; Rejoice every time you hear the sound of my voice&lt;br&gt; Just know that I'm looking down on you smiling&lt;br&gt; And I didn't feel a thing, So baby don't feel no pain&lt;br&gt; Just smile back...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 2]&lt;br&gt; I keep having this dream, I'm pushin' Hailie on the swing&lt;br&gt; She keeps screaming, she don't want me to sing&lt;br&gt; &quot;You're making Mommy cry, why? Why is Mommy crying?&quot;&lt;br&gt; Baby, Daddy ain't leaving no more, &quot;Daddy you're lying&lt;br&gt; &quot;You always say that, you always say this is the last time&lt;br&gt; &quot;But you ain't leaving no more, Daddy you're mine&quot;&lt;br&gt; She's piling boxes in front of the door trying to block it&lt;br&gt; &quot;Daddy please, Daddy don't leave, Daddy - no stop it!&quot;&lt;br&gt; Goes in her pocket, pulls out a tiny necklace locket&lt;br&gt; It's got a picture, &quot;this'll keep you safe Daddy, take it withcha'&quot;&lt;br&gt; I look up, it's just me standing in the mirror&lt;br&gt; These fuckin' walls must be talking, cuz man I can hear 'em&lt;br&gt; They're saying &quot;You've got one more chance to do right&quot; - and it's tonight&lt;br&gt; Now go out there and show that you love 'em before it's too late&lt;br&gt; And just as I go to walk out of my bedroom door&lt;br&gt; It's turns to a stage, they're gone, and this spotlight is on&lt;br&gt; And I'm singing...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus]&lt;br&gt; And when I'm gone, just carry on, don't mourn&lt;br&gt; Rejoice every time you hear the sound of my voice&lt;br&gt; Just know that I'm looking down on you smiling&lt;br&gt; And I didn't feel a thing, So baby don't feel my pain&lt;br&gt; Just smile back&lt;br&gt; And when I'm gone, just carry on, don't mourn&lt;br&gt; Rejoice every time you hear the sound of my voice&lt;br&gt; Just know that I'm looking down on you smiling&lt;br&gt; And I didn't feel a thing, So baby don't feel no pain&lt;br&gt; Just smile back...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Verse 3]&lt;br&gt; Sixty thousand people, all jumping out their seat&lt;br&gt; The curtain closes, they're throwing roses at my feet&lt;br&gt; I take a bow and thank you all for coming out&lt;br&gt; They're screaming so loud, I take one last look at the crowd&lt;br&gt; I glance down, I don't believe what I'm seeing&lt;br&gt; &quot;Daddy it's me, help Mommy, her wrists are bleeding,&quot;&lt;br&gt; But baby we're in Sweden, how did you get to Sweden?&lt;br&gt; &quot;I followed you Daddy, you told me that you weren't leavin'&lt;br&gt; &quot;You lied to me Dad, and now you make Mommy sad&lt;br&gt; &quot;And I bought you this coin, it says 'Number One Dad'&lt;br&gt; &quot;That's all I wanted, I just want to give you this coin&lt;br&gt; &quot;I get the point - fine, me and Mommy are going&quot;&lt;br&gt; But baby wait, &quot;it's too late Dad, you made the choice&lt;br&gt; &quot;Now go out there and show 'em that you love 'em more than us&quot;&lt;br&gt; That's what they want, they want you Marshall, they keep.. screamin' your name&lt;br&gt; It's no wonder you can't go to sleep, just take another pill&lt;br&gt; Yeah, I bet you will. You rap about it, yeah, word, k-keep it real&lt;br&gt; I hear applause, all this time I couldn't see&lt;br&gt; How could it be, that the curtain is closing on me&lt;br&gt; I turn around, find a gun on the ground, cock it&lt;br&gt; Put it to my brain and scream &quot;die Shady&quot; and pop it&lt;br&gt; The sky darkens, my life flashes, the plane that I was supposed to be on crashes and burns to ashes&lt;br&gt; That's when I wake up, alarm clock's ringin', there's birds singin'&lt;br&gt; It's Spring and Hailie's outside swinging, I walk right up to Kim and kiss her&lt;br&gt; Tell her I miss her, Hailie just smiles and winks at her little sister&lt;br&gt; Almost as if to say..&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Chorus/Outro]&lt;br&gt; And when I'm gone, just carry on, don't mourn&lt;br&gt; Rejoice every time you hear the sound of my voice&lt;br&gt; Just know that I'm looking down on you smiling&lt;br&gt; And I didn't feel a thing, So baby don't feel my pain&lt;br&gt; Just smile back&lt;br&gt; And when I'm gone, just carry on, don't mourn&lt;br&gt; Rejoice every time you hear the sound of my voice&lt;br&gt; Just know that I'm looking down on you smiling&lt;br&gt; And I didn't feel a thing, So baby don't feel no pain&lt;br&gt; Just smile back...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Curtains closing and sounds of clapping] &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
