<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Party Rock Anthem</Title>
    <Artist>LMFAO</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/d/2/d20f3c0b1adfc6c79b26bd3bcf8a2337_1288193829.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Party Rock Anthem&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;LMFAO&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA1JTJGMDYlMkYyJTJGMCUyRjIwZmM2YTlkMjEwMmVkMGRjMDNlYTg5YjUxMzYzNGM0Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>PART ROCK&lt;br&gt; Yeah!!&lt;br&gt; Woooh!!!&lt;br&gt; Let's go!&lt;br&gt; Party rock is in the house tonight&lt;br&gt; Everybody just have a good time&lt;br&gt; And we gonna make you lose your mind&lt;br&gt; Everybody just have a good time [X2]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We just wanna see yaa!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Shake That !&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; In the club party rock look up on your girl&lt;br&gt; She on my jock non stop when we in the spot&lt;br&gt; Booty move away like she on the block&lt;br&gt; What the track I gots to know&lt;br&gt; Top jeans tatto cause I’m rock and roll&lt;br&gt; Half black half white diamino&lt;br&gt; Gane the money out the door&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yoooo!!&lt;br&gt; I’m runnin through these hoes like drano&lt;br&gt; I got that devilish flow rock and roll no halo&lt;br&gt; We party rock yea! that’s the crew that I’m reppin&lt;br&gt; On the rise to the top no led in our zeppelin&lt;br&gt; Hey!!!&lt;br&gt; Party rock is in the house tonight&lt;br&gt; Everybody just have a good time&lt;br&gt; And we gonna make you lose your mind&lt;br&gt; Everybody just have a good time [X2]&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We just wanna see yaa!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Everyday I’m shuffelin&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Shuffelin shuffelin&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Step up fast and be the first girl to make me throw this cash&lt;br&gt; We get money don’t be mad now stop hatein is bad&lt;br&gt; Welcome to Yeucahat.com&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; One more shot for us&lt;br&gt; Another round&lt;br&gt; Please fill up my cup&lt;br&gt; Don’t mess around&lt;br&gt; We just wanna see&lt;br&gt; You shake it now&lt;br&gt; Now you wanna be&lt;br&gt; Your naked now&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Get up get down put your hands up to the sound [X3]&lt;br&gt; Put your hands up to the sound [X2]&lt;br&gt; Get up [X9]&lt;br&gt; Put your hands up to the sound&lt;br&gt; To the sound&lt;br&gt; Put your hands up !!!!!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Party rock is in the house tonight&lt;br&gt; Everybody just have a good time&lt;br&gt; And we gonna make you lose your mind&lt;br&gt; Everybody just have a good good good time&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ohhhhh!!Ohhhhhh!!!Ohhhhhh!!!Ohh..!</Lyrics>
</Song>
