<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Why Don't We Just Dance</Title>
    <Artist>Josh Turner</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/d/3/d3cafa22ce661d91cf5c6f3cae7b1a9c_1336154592.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Why Don't We Just Dance&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Josh Turner&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA3JTJGMDYlMkY5JTJGMiUyRjkyZTYwOGUwMTYzYTZkMDlhZGRmNGY0NTNiOWMyNTcxLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&lt;br&gt; Why Don't We Just Dance Lyrics&lt;br&gt; Artist(Band):Josh Turner&lt;br&gt; Review The Song (0)&lt;br&gt; Print the Lyrics&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Send &quot;Why Don't We Just Dance&quot; Ringtones to Cell &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby, why don't we just turn that TV off?&lt;br&gt; 315 channels of nothing but bad news on,&lt;br&gt; Well it might be me&lt;br&gt; But the way I see it,&lt;br&gt; The whole wide world has gone crazy.&lt;br&gt; So baby, why don't we just dance?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This little bit of living room aint gonna look like much &lt;br&gt; But when the lights go down and we move the couch,&lt;br&gt; It's gonna be more than enough&lt;br&gt; For my two left feet&lt;br&gt; And our two hearts beatin'&lt;br&gt; Nobody's gonna see us go crazy.&lt;br&gt; So baby, why don't we just dance&lt;br&gt; Down the hall,&lt;br&gt; Maybe straight up the stairs?&lt;br&gt; Bouncing off the walls,&lt;br&gt; Floating on air,&lt;br&gt; Baby, why don't we just dance?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby, why don't you go put your best dress on,&lt;br&gt; And those high heeled shoes you love to lose&lt;br&gt; As soon as the tunes come on?&lt;br&gt; On second thought,&lt;br&gt; Just the way you are&lt;br&gt; Is already driving me crazy.&lt;br&gt; So baby, why don't we just dance&lt;br&gt; Down the hall&lt;br&gt; Maybe straight up the stairs?&lt;br&gt; Bouncing off the walls,&lt;br&gt; Floating on air,&lt;br&gt; Baby, why don't we just dance?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Well it might be me&lt;br&gt; But the way I see it,&lt;br&gt; The whole wide world has gone crazy.&lt;br&gt; So baby, why don't we just dance [Bouncing off the walls, floating on air]&lt;br&gt; Oh baby [baby], why don't we just dance?</Lyrics>
</Song>
