<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Mambo Italiano</Title>
    <Artist>Various Artists</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/7/3/73688444a73a76169d03b689a7e785cf_1404904575.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Mambo Italiano&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Various Artists&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA2JTJGMjElMkYwJTJGZSUyRjBlNTNjZGQ2MDgxYTJmN2U2MDRmYWNlOWRlN2FiMDJkLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>A girl went back to Napoli&lt;br&gt; Because she missed the scenery&lt;br&gt; The native dances and the charming songs&lt;br&gt; But wait a minute, something's wrong&lt;br&gt; Hey, mambo! Mambo italiano!&lt;br&gt; Hey, mambo! Mambo italiano&lt;br&gt; Go, go, go you mixed up sicialiano&lt;br&gt; All you calabraise-a do the mambo like a crazy with a&lt;br&gt; Hey mambo, don't wanna tarantella&lt;br&gt; Hey mambo, no more a mozzarella&lt;br&gt; Hey mambo! Mambo italiano!&lt;br&gt; Try an enchilada with da fish a bac a lab and then a&lt;br&gt; Hey goombah, I love a how you dance a rhumbah&lt;br&gt; But take a some advice paisano&lt;br&gt; Learn how to mambo&lt;br&gt; If you gonna be a square&lt;br&gt; You ain't a gonna go nowhere&lt;br&gt; Hey mambo! mambo italiano!&lt;br&gt; Hey mambo! mambo italiano!&lt;br&gt; Go, go, Joe, shake like a Giovanno&lt;br&gt; Hello kess-a-deetch-a you getta happy in the feets a&lt;br&gt; When you mambo italiano&lt;br&gt; Shake-a Baby shake-a cause i love a when you take a me&lt;br&gt; Mama say &quot;stop-a or I'm gonna go to papa&quot;&lt;br&gt; And a hey ja drool you don't a have to go to school&lt;br&gt; Just make-a wid da beat bambino&lt;br&gt; It's a like a vino&lt;br&gt; Kid you good a lookin' but you don't a-know what's cookin' till you&lt;br&gt; Hey mambo, Mambo italiano&lt;br&gt; Hey mambo, Mambo italiano&lt;br&gt; Ho, ho, ho, you mixed up Siciliano&lt;br&gt; it's a so delish a ev'rybody come copisha&lt;br&gt; How to mambo italianoooooo!&lt;br&gt; 'Ats nice!&lt;br&gt; UNH!</Lyrics>
</Song>
