<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Beautiful Hangover</Title>
    <Artist>BIGBANG</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/c/0/c01e8906d5b2b8f08e680b644a08f23a_1414577702.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Beautiful Hangover&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;BIGBANG&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA1JTJGMzAlMkY4JTJGYiUyRjhiMGE2NGY1YWQyOWFmNzBlODE1NjgzNDI4MzQzOWIzLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>kimi wa my beautiful hangover&lt;br&gt; hangover yeah&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; kagayaku headlight nemuranai machi e are you ready?&lt;br&gt; Koko kara ga shoubu ase-razu ni genkai made zenkai de ikou!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Nagareru radio chijimeru kyori wo oh oh oh&lt;br&gt; yukisaki wa mada ienai yo&lt;br&gt; honey close your eyes&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; we’re gonna get down down down!&lt;br&gt; Gimme love love love! Sagashi motometeta lady&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; dare ni motomerarenai making love kiga sumumate go!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Kimi wa my beautiful hangover&lt;br&gt; hangover yeah&lt;br&gt; kimi wa my beautiful hangover hangover&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; it’s me g.d (i know you love me)&lt;br&gt; ma-ma-ma-ma-ma my beautiful girl&lt;br&gt; 1,2,3 to the 4-sho one like you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; there ain’t nobody can do them things you do&lt;br&gt; so true&lt;br&gt; i’m so excited delighted&lt;br&gt; i won’t deny it nor fight it&lt;br&gt; baby you got what i need&lt;br&gt; got me jumpin’ jumpin’ off my feet&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; baby there’s no playin’ delayin’&lt;br&gt; always got me feelin’ that healin’&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; everyday i’m smilin’ and wildin’&lt;br&gt; when i think about you&lt;br&gt; think about you&lt;br&gt; got me flyin’ so high ‘n&lt;br&gt; and i won’t stop bringin’ and bringin’ that (bang!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; B.i.g (bang!) T.o.p (bang!)&lt;br&gt; Baby that’s how it be&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; we’re gonna get down down down!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Gimme love love love! Sagashi motometeta lady&lt;br&gt; dare ni motomerarenai making love honoo no yo ni atsui&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; kimi wa my beautiful hangover&lt;br&gt; hangover yeah&lt;br&gt; kimi wa my beautiful hangover hangover&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; you got my heart love game&lt;br&gt; make me crazy baby&lt;br&gt; kiss my lips kuruwa se 360°&lt;br&gt; mou naru you ni naru shikanai&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; we’re gonna get down down down!&lt;br&gt; Gimme love love love! Sagashi motometeta lady&lt;br&gt; dare ni motomerarenai making love kiga sumumate go!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Kimi wa my beautiful hangover&lt;br&gt; hangover yeah&lt;br&gt; kimi wa my beautiful hangover hangover&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; beautiful my baby</Lyrics>
</Song>
