<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Zombie</Title>
    <Artist>The Cranberries</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/2/6/26db9cae3c443deacbd67a3b07f406c9_1288510213.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Zombie&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;The Cranberries&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA2JTJGMjMlMkZjJTJGNiUyRmM2MzEwM2YxMzE3ZmM1NmQ1NjBiOWNhZmQzODE0YjBhLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>&lt;br&gt; &quot;Zombie&quot;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Another head hangs lowly, &lt;br&gt; Child is slowly taken. &lt;br&gt; And the violence caused such silence, &lt;br&gt; Who are we mistaken? &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; But you see, it's not me, it's not my family. &lt;br&gt; In your head, in your head they are fighting, &lt;br&gt; With their tanks and their bombs, &lt;br&gt; And their bombs and their guns. &lt;br&gt; In your head, in your head, they are crying... &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; In your head, in your head, &lt;br&gt; Zombie, zombie, zombie, &lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey. What's in your head, &lt;br&gt; In your head, &lt;br&gt; Zombie, zombie, zombie? &lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, dou, dou, dou, dou, dou... &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Another mother's breakin', &lt;br&gt; Heart is taking over. &lt;br&gt; When the vi'lence causes silence, &lt;br&gt; We must be mistaken. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It's the same old theme since nineteen-sixteen. &lt;br&gt; In your head, in your head they're still fighting, &lt;br&gt; With their tanks and their bombs, &lt;br&gt; And their bombs and their guns. &lt;br&gt; In your head, in your head, they are dying... &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; In your head, in your head, &lt;br&gt; Zombie, zombie, zombie, &lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey. What's in your head, &lt;br&gt; In your head, &lt;br&gt; Zombie, zombie, zombie? &lt;br&gt; Hey, hey, hey, hey, oh, oh, oh, &lt;br&gt; Oh, oh, oh, oh, hey, oh, ya, ya-a... &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
