<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>From This Moment On</Title>
    <Artist>Shania Twain</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/6/d/6ddeaf555e5ec56e9d7c2b18d89e81a9_1324229121.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;From This Moment On&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Shania Twain&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMSUyRjA4JTJGMTglMkY3JTJGMCUyRjcwZjgzZTA3MzNkYjMxZmZlZDBjYjZiM2FjYjE2MWRjLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>(I do swear that I'll always be there.&lt;br&gt; I'd give anything and everything and I will always care.&lt;br&gt; Through weakness and strength, happiness and sorrow,&lt;br&gt; for better for worse, I will love you with&lt;br&gt; every beat of my heart.)&lt;br&gt; From this moment life has begun&lt;br&gt; From this moment you are the one&lt;br&gt; Right beside you is where I belong&lt;br&gt; From this moment on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; From this moment I have been blessed&lt;br&gt; I live only for your happiness&lt;br&gt; And for your love I'd give my last breath&lt;br&gt; From this moment on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I give my hand to you with all my heart&lt;br&gt; Can't wait to live my life with you, can't wait to start&lt;br&gt; You and I will never be apart&lt;br&gt; My dreams came true because of you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; From this moment as long as I live&lt;br&gt; I will love you, I promise you this&lt;br&gt; There is nothing I wouldn't give&lt;br&gt; From this moment on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You're the reason I believe in love&lt;br&gt; And you're the answer to my prayers from up above&lt;br&gt; All we need is just the two of us&lt;br&gt; My dreams came true because of you&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; From this moment as long as I live&lt;br&gt; I will love you, I promise you this&lt;br&gt; There is nothing I wouldn't give&lt;br&gt; From this moment&lt;br&gt; I will love you as long as I live&lt;br&gt; From this moment on&lt;br&gt;</Lyrics>
</Song>
