<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>I Like To Move It</Title>
    <Artist>Crazy Frog</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/6/1/61ca1aef608e77f0992db8296c030e3b_1289905513.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;I Like To Move It&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Crazy Frog&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjAxJTJGMDclMkZiJTJGOSUyRmI5MGZkNmU2YTEyNTcxYjMxYjZiYjY0YTM1MTgxODdmLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>!)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; And we don't party hardly&lt;br&gt; (No!)&lt;br&gt; We just party hard&lt;br&gt; (Yeah!)&lt;br&gt; And not because we bored&lt;br&gt; (No!)&lt;br&gt; We party 'cause we born to party&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We gonna move our bodies&lt;br&gt; With our hands in the air&lt;br&gt; And wave 'em all around&lt;br&gt; Like we just don't care&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (Yeah!)&lt;br&gt; Moto Moto in the house&lt;br&gt; (Yeah!)&lt;br&gt; I'm about to turn it out&lt;br&gt; (Yeah!)&lt;br&gt; And you know it's going down&lt;br&gt; I'm physically, physically, physically round&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; We like to move it!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; She like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; We like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; We like to move it!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Party ain't done, party ain't done&lt;br&gt; Party this belly got started, Act I&lt;br&gt; It just begun, big action&lt;br&gt; Pump up the volume, speaker blastin'&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Shake up the ground, shake up the ground&lt;br&gt; Shake like a earthquake quake up the ground&lt;br&gt; Play to make a sound, play to make a sound&lt;br&gt; Play to make a, play to make a, play to make a sound&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; So I can do my little dance, do my little dance&lt;br&gt; Do my little, do my little, do my little dance&lt;br&gt; Ants in my pants, got ants in my pants&lt;br&gt; Ants in my, ants in my, ants in my pants&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; That's why I keep on movin'&lt;br&gt; Yes, that's why I keep on groovin'&lt;br&gt; Yes, that's why I keep on doin'&lt;br&gt; Doin' what I'm doin', y'all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; First name Moto, last name Moto&lt;br&gt; Here's how you spell it, M-O-T-O M-O-T-O&lt;br&gt; When I step in all the girls want a photo&lt;br&gt; Ya know, hey, yo&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Moto Moto in the house&lt;br&gt; I'm about to turn it out&lt;br&gt; And you know it's goin' down&lt;br&gt; I'm physically, physically, physically round&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; We like to move it!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; She like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; We like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; We like to move it!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I like to party, party&lt;br&gt; He like to party, party&lt;br&gt; They like to party, party&lt;br&gt; We like to party!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; She like to shake it, shake it&lt;br&gt; She like to shake it, shake it&lt;br&gt; He like to shake it? Yo!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Somebody say ho!&lt;br&gt; (Ho!)&lt;br&gt; Say ho ho!&lt;br&gt; (Ho ho!)&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Yo! Somebody say yeah!&lt;br&gt; (Yeah!)&lt;br&gt; Say yeah yeah!&lt;br&gt; (Yeah yeah!)&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Back it up, back it up&lt;br&gt; Gimme room, gimme room&lt;br&gt; Gimme room 'cuz, huh!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; I like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; We like to move it!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; She like to shake it, shake it&lt;br&gt; She like to shake it, shake it&lt;br&gt; She like to shake it, shake it&lt;br&gt; Yeah, shake it girl, huh!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We like to party, party&lt;br&gt; We like to party, party&lt;br&gt; We like to party, party&lt;br&gt; We like to party!&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; He like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; They like to move it, move it&lt;br&gt; Move it, move it, move it, move it&lt;br&gt; Move it</Lyrics>
</Song>
