<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Read All About It, Pt. III</Title>
    <Artist>Emeli Sande</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/b/3be5b4de96a4cbf0acbf6b62bad1a720_1351442977.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Read All About It, Pt. III&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Emeli Sande&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjAyJTJGMTglMkYyJTJGMCUyRjIwMjNiZTEyNTYyODA2MGI4ZDVmMzllMjQwMzQ2N2FlLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>You've got the words to change a nation&lt;br&gt; but you're biting your tongue&lt;br&gt; You've spent a life time stuck in silence&lt;br&gt; afraid you'll say something wrong&lt;br&gt; If no one ever hears it how we gonna learn your song?&lt;br&gt; So come on, come on&lt;br&gt; Come on, come on&lt;br&gt; You've got a heart as loud as lions&lt;br&gt; So why let your voice be tamed?&lt;br&gt; Baby we're a little different&lt;br&gt; there's no need to be ashamed&lt;br&gt; You've got the light to fight the shadows&lt;br&gt; so stop hiding it away&lt;br&gt; Come on, Come on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna sing, I wanna shout&lt;br&gt; I wanna scream till the words dry out&lt;br&gt; so put it in all of the papers,&lt;br&gt; I'm not afraid&lt;br&gt; they can read all about it&lt;br&gt; read all about it oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh &lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; o h-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; At night we're waking up the neighbours&lt;br&gt; while we sing away the blues&lt;br&gt; making sure that we remember yeah&lt;br&gt; cause we all matter too&lt;br&gt; if the truth has been forbidden&lt;br&gt; then we're breaking all the rules&lt;br&gt; so come on, come on&lt;br&gt; come on, come on,&lt;br&gt; lets get the tv and the radio&lt;br&gt; to play our tune again&lt;br&gt; its 'bout time we got some airplay of our version of events&lt;br&gt; there's no need to be afraid&lt;br&gt; I will sing with you my friend&lt;br&gt; Come on, come on&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna sing, I wanna shout&lt;br&gt; I wanna scream till the words dry out&lt;br&gt; so put it in all of the papers,&lt;br&gt; I'm not afraid&lt;br&gt; they can read all about it&lt;br&gt; read all about it oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh &lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; o h-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Ye ah we're all wonderful, wonderful people&lt;br&gt; so when did we all get so fearful?&lt;br&gt; Now we're finally finding our voices&lt;br&gt; so take a chance, come help me sing this&lt;br&gt; Yeah we're all wonderful, wonderful people&lt;br&gt; so when did we all get so fearful?&lt;br&gt; and now we're finally finding our voices&lt;br&gt; so take a chance, come help me sing this&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna sing, I wanna shout&lt;br&gt; I wanna scream till the words dry out&lt;br&gt; so put it in all of the papers,&lt;br&gt; I'm not afraid&lt;br&gt; they can read all about it&lt;br&gt; read all about it oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh &lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; o h-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; oh-oh-oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna sing, I wanna shout&lt;br&gt; I wanna scream till the words dry out&lt;br&gt; so put it in all of the papers,&lt;br&gt; I'm not afraid&lt;br&gt; they can read all about it&lt;br&gt; read all about it oh</Lyrics>
</Song>
