<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>You've Got A Friend</Title>
    <Artist>Stacey Kent</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/e/d/ed016b96c386a3e3ac6dda2b38c1ffa7_1336290660.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;You've Got A Friend&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Stacey Kent&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjA0JTJGMTUlMkZjJTJGMCUyRmMwNTNmZDBiMDliZDNmOWRmYzU4OTM0YmE3NTZmNjMyLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>When youre down and troubled &lt;br&gt; And you need a helping hand &lt;br&gt; And nothing, whoa nothing is going right. &lt;br&gt; Close your eyes and think of me &lt;br&gt; And soon I will be there &lt;br&gt; To brighten up even your darkest nights. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You just call out my name, &lt;br&gt; And you know whereever I am &lt;br&gt; Ill come running, oh yeah baby &lt;br&gt; To see you again. &lt;br&gt; Winter, spring, summer, or fall, &lt;br&gt; All you have to do is call &lt;br&gt; And Ill be there, yeah, yeah, yeah. &lt;br&gt; Youve got a friend. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If the sky above you &lt;br&gt; Should turn dark and full of clouds &lt;br&gt; And that old north wind should begin to blow &lt;br&gt; Keep your head together and call my name out loud &lt;br&gt; And soon I will be knocking upon your door. &lt;br&gt; You just call out my name and you know where ever I am &lt;br&gt; Ill come running to see you again. &lt;br&gt; Winter, spring, summer or fall &lt;br&gt; All you got to do is call &lt;br&gt; And Ill be there, yeah, yeah, yeah. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hey, aint it good to know that youve got a friend? &lt;br&gt; People can be so cold. &lt;br&gt; Theyll hurt you and desert you. &lt;br&gt; Well theyll take your soul if you let them. &lt;br&gt; Oh yeah, but dont you let them. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You just call out my name and you know wherever I am &lt;br&gt; Ill come running to see you again. &lt;br&gt; Oh babe, dont you know that, &lt;br&gt; Winter spring summer or fall, &lt;br&gt; Hey now, all youve got to do is call. &lt;br&gt; Lord, Ill be there, yes I will. &lt;br&gt; Youve got a friend. &lt;br&gt; Youve got a friend. &lt;br&gt; Aint it good to know youve got a friend. &lt;br&gt; Aint it good to know youve got a friend. &lt;br&gt; Youve got a friend.</Lyrics>
</Song>
