<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Dance Again</Title>
    <Artist>Jennifer Lopez ft. Pitbull</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/5/f/5f9b6313c8973a63775c0dad37e3d436_1403150582.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Dance Again&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Jennifer Lopez,Pitbull&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjAzJTJGMzElMkY1JTJGNyUyRjU3MjcwYWRiOWFkOGZlYjEwMTkwOWI0ZGVlN2QwMzQwLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Dance, yes (RedOne)&lt;br&gt; Love, next&lt;br&gt; Dance, yes (J.Lo)&lt;br&gt; Love, next&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Shimmy Shimmy yah, Shimmy yam&lt;br&gt; Shimmy yay&lt;br&gt; I'm a ol' dirty dog all day&lt;br&gt; No way Jose&lt;br&gt; Your girl only go one way, ay mi madre&lt;br&gt; You should check that out&lt;br&gt; Maybe you ain't turn her out&lt;br&gt; Maybe it's none of my business&lt;br&gt; But for now work it out&lt;br&gt; Let's get this, dale&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Nobody knows what i'm feeling inside&lt;br&gt; I find it so stupid&lt;br&gt; So why should I hide&lt;br&gt; That I love to make love to you baby&lt;br&gt; (yeah make love to me)&lt;br&gt; So many ways wanna touch you tonight&lt;br&gt; I'm a big girl got no secrets this time&lt;br&gt; Yeah I love to make love to you baby&lt;br&gt; (yeah make love to me)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If this would be a perfect world&lt;br&gt; We'd be together then&lt;br&gt; (let's do it do it do it)&lt;br&gt; Only got just one life this i've learned&lt;br&gt; Who cares what they're gonna say&lt;br&gt; (let's do it do it do it)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna dance, and love, and dance again&lt;br&gt; I wanna dance, and love, and dance again&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Dance, yes&lt;br&gt; Love, next&lt;br&gt; Dance, yes&lt;br&gt; Love, next&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Baby your fire is lighting me up&lt;br&gt; The way that you move boy is reason enough&lt;br&gt; That I love to make love to you baby&lt;br&gt; (yeah make love to me)&lt;br&gt; I can't behave&lt;br&gt; Oh I want you so much&lt;br&gt; Your lips taste like heaven&lt;br&gt; So why should I stop?&lt;br&gt; Yeah I love to make love to you baby&lt;br&gt; (yeah make love to me)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If this would be a perfect world&lt;br&gt; We'd be together then&lt;br&gt; (let's do it do it do it)&lt;br&gt; Only got just one life this i've learned&lt;br&gt; Who cares what they're gonna say&lt;br&gt; (let's do it do it do it)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna dance, and love, and dance again&lt;br&gt; I wanna dance, and love, and dance again&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Mr Worldwide, and the world's most beautiful woman&lt;br&gt; Modern day Hugh Hef (uh, yes)&lt;br&gt; Playboy to the death (uh, yes)&lt;br&gt; Is he really worldwide? (uh, yes)&lt;br&gt; Mami let me open your treasure chest&lt;br&gt; Play dates, we play mates&lt;br&gt; I'm the king at snatching queens, checkmate&lt;br&gt; What you think?&lt;br&gt; It's a rumor&lt;br&gt; I'm really out of this world&lt;br&gt; Moon, luna&lt;br&gt; Make woman comfortable&lt;br&gt; Call me bloomer&lt;br&gt; Can't even show love cause they'll sue ya&lt;br&gt; But I told them, 'hallelujah, have a blessed day'&lt;br&gt; So ahead of myself&lt;br&gt; Everyday's yesterday&lt;br&gt; Want the recipe? it's real simple&lt;br&gt; Little bit of voli, and she'll open sesame&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Now dance yes&lt;br&gt; Love next&lt;br&gt; Dance yes&lt;br&gt; Love next&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; If this would be a perfect world&lt;br&gt; We'd be together then&lt;br&gt; (let's do it do it do it)&lt;br&gt; Only got just one life this i've learned&lt;br&gt; Who cares what they're gonna say&lt;br&gt; (let's do it do it do it)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I wanna dance, and love, and dance again&lt;br&gt; I wanna dance, and love, and dance again</Lyrics>
</Song>
