<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Good Girl</Title>
    <Artist>Carrie Underwood</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/3/2/32d3ca5e23f4ccf1e4c8660c40e75f33_1335323175.png</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Good Girl&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Carrie Underwood&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjAyJTJGMjQlMkZiJTJGYiUyRmJiNDY2ODYwNTkyNDEzNDc0ODYxODg2NDM0MjU1NDc1Lm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Hey, good girl&lt;br&gt; With your head in the clouds&lt;br&gt; I bet you I can tell you&lt;br&gt; What you’re thinkin' about&lt;br&gt; You'll see a good boy&lt;br&gt; Gonna give you the world&lt;br&gt; But he’s gonna leave you cryin'&lt;br&gt; With your heart in the dirt&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; His lips are dropping honey&lt;br&gt; But he’ll sting you like a bee&lt;br&gt; So lock up all your loving&lt;br&gt; Go and throw away the key&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Hey good girl&lt;br&gt; Get out while you can&lt;br&gt; I know you think you got a good man&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; Whyyyy, why you gotta be so bliiiind?&lt;br&gt; Won’t you open your eeeyes?&lt;br&gt; It’s just a matter of time 'till you find&lt;br&gt; He’s no good, girl&lt;br&gt; No good for you&lt;br&gt; You better get to getting on your goodbye shoes and go, go, go...&lt;br&gt; Better listen to me&lt;br&gt; He’s low, low, low...&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Carrie Underwood]&lt;br&gt; Hey, good girl&lt;br&gt; You got a heart of gold&lt;br&gt; You want a white wedding&lt;br&gt; And a hand you can hold&lt;br&gt; Just like you should, girl&lt;br&gt; Like every good girl does&lt;br&gt; Want a fairytale ending, somebody to love&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; But he’s really good at lying girl&lt;br&gt; Yeah, he’ll leave you in the dust&lt;br&gt; 'Cause when he says forever&lt;br&gt; Well, it don’t mean much&lt;br&gt; Hey good girl&lt;br&gt; So good for him&lt;br&gt; Better back away honey&lt;br&gt; You don’t know where he’s been&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook]&lt;br&gt; Whyyyy, why you gotta be so bliiiind?&lt;br&gt; Won’t you open your eeeyes?&lt;br&gt; It’s just a matter of time 'till you find&lt;br&gt; He’s no good, girl&lt;br&gt; No good for you&lt;br&gt; You better get to getting on your goodbye shoes and go, go, go...&lt;br&gt; Yeah yeah yeah, he’s low&lt;br&gt; Yeah yeah yeah&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Bridge]&lt;br&gt; He’s no good, girl&lt;br&gt; Why can’t you see?&lt;br&gt; He’ll take your heart and break it&lt;br&gt; Listen to me, yeah&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; [Hook/Outro]&lt;br&gt; Whyyyy, why you gotta be so bliiiind?&lt;br&gt; Won’t you open your eeeeyes?&lt;br&gt; It’s just a matter of time 'till you find&lt;br&gt; He’s no good, he’s no good&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Won’t you open up your eeeeyes?&lt;br&gt; It’s just a matter of time 'till you find&lt;br&gt; He’s no good, girl&lt;br&gt; He’s no good for you&lt;br&gt; You better get to getting on your goodbye shoes</Lyrics>
</Song>
