<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>The Winner Takes It All</Title>
    <Artist>Susan Wong</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/8/8/88174438b948067c60d7ef7a585017f5_1332584110.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;The Winner Takes It All&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;Susan Wong&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjAzJTJGMjglMkZiJTJGNCUyRmI0ZjUyYzYzOGFkYmFkYjk3YTM4Y2NiNzZhNGZhMjIyLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>I don’t wanna talk&lt;br&gt; About the things we’ve gone through&lt;br&gt; Though it’s hurting me&lt;br&gt; Now it’s history&lt;br&gt; I’ve played all my cards&lt;br&gt; And that’s what you’ve done too&lt;br&gt; Nothing more to say&lt;br&gt; No more ace to play&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The winner takes it all&lt;br&gt; The loser standing small&lt;br&gt; Beside the victory&lt;br&gt; That’s her destiny&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I was in your arms&lt;br&gt; Thinking I belonged there&lt;br&gt; I figured it made sense&lt;br&gt; Building me a fence&lt;br&gt; Building me a home&lt;br&gt; Thinking I’d be strong there&lt;br&gt; But I was a fool&lt;br&gt; Playing by the rules&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The gods may throw a dice&lt;br&gt; Their minds as cold as ice&lt;br&gt; And someone way down here&lt;br&gt; Loses someone dear&lt;br&gt; The winner takes it all&lt;br&gt; The loser has to fall&lt;br&gt; It’s simple and it’s plain&lt;br&gt; Why should I complain.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; But tell me does she kiss&lt;br&gt; Like I used to kiss you? &lt;br&gt; Does it feel the same&lt;br&gt; When she calls your name? &lt;br&gt; Somewhere deep inside&lt;br&gt; You must know I miss you&lt;br&gt; But what can I say&lt;br&gt; Rules must be obeyed&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The judges will decide&lt;br&gt; The likes of me abide&lt;br&gt; Spectators of the show&lt;br&gt; Always staying low&lt;br&gt; The game is on again&lt;br&gt; A lover or a friend&lt;br&gt; A big thing or a small&lt;br&gt; The winner takes it all&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I don’t wanna talk&lt;br&gt; If it makes you feel sad&lt;br&gt; And I understand&lt;br&gt; You’ve come to shake my hand&lt;br&gt; I apologize&lt;br&gt; If it makes you feel bad&lt;br&gt; Seeing me so tense&lt;br&gt; No self-confidence&lt;br&gt; But you see&lt;br&gt; The winner takes it all&lt;br&gt; The winner takes it all......</Lyrics>
</Song>
