<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Song xmlns="http://yourplaylist.tk/Schema">
    <Title>Blue</Title>
    <Artist>BIGBANG</Artist>
    <AlbumArt>http://image.mp3.zdn.vn/thumb/165_165/avatars/c/0/c01e8906d5b2b8f08e680b644a08f23a_1414577702.jpg</AlbumArt>
    <Source>{&quot;data&quot;:[{&quot;type&quot;:&quot;audio&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;Blue&quot;,&quot;performer&quot;:&quot;BIGBANG&quot;,&quot;source&quot;:&quot;http:\/\/m.mp3.zing.vn\/xml\/song-load\/MjAxMiUyRjAyJTJGMjIlMkY5JTJGOSUyRjk5NjljYjQzODk5ZjQ4YTlmMWI0MTdlOTY4MmIyMTAzLm1wMyU3QzI=&quot;,&quot;hq&quot;:&quot;require vip&quot;}]}</Source>
    <Lyrics>Music and Lyrics by: TEDDY, G-DRAGON&lt;br&gt; Additional rap written by: T.O.P. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; When winter ends and spring comes, we wither&lt;br&gt; In longing, my heart is bruised&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) used to the blue tears blue sadness&lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) love that I let go to the drifting clouds oh oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Same sky, different place, it’s dangerous for us so I’m letting you go&lt;br&gt; From lovers to strangers. It’s cowardly, but I’m hiding because I’m worthless&lt;br&gt; No words, not even those made out of love, can comfort a cruel parting&lt;br&gt; This is probably the last melo in my life&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I met you and loved you to death&lt;br&gt; My heart is stained blue and frozen, I can’t feel you even when I close my eyes&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; When winter ends and spring comes, we wither&lt;br&gt; In longing, my heart is bruised &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) used to the blue tears blue sadness&lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) love that I let go to the drifting clouds oh oh&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; It feels like my heart stopped, the war ended but you and I are still frozen in that place&lt;br&gt; The trauma is inscribed in my mind, once my tears dry, hopefully I’ll remember my love&lt;br&gt; I’m not in pain, I’m not lonely, happiness is simply talking to myself, and I can’t stand anything more complicated&lt;br&gt; I don’t care, I’m ok. People, who can’t do anything about it, wander here and there&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I met you and loved you to death&lt;br&gt; My heart has stained blue and frozen, you left but I’m still here&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; When winter ends and spring comes, we wither&lt;br&gt; In longing, our hearts are bruised&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; I’ll fall asleep under the blue moon all alone again tonight&lt;br&gt; Even in my dreams, I’ll be looking for you, singing this song&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) used to the blue tears blue sadness&lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) love that I let go to the drifting clouds oh oh&lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) used to the blue tears blue sadness&lt;br&gt; (I’m singing my blues) love that I let go to the drifting clouds oh oh</Lyrics>
</Song>
